Come to the night, the car is laid out for show
Star shine is so bright, watch the secret sun fall
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
The rhythm, yeah, yeah, yeah, flow
Hearts in the balance, every card an open door
Feel the romance in every arcane lord
So now I have a lot of my music downloaded to like some websites and so I can take it off of this
I'm gonna do
like I can have just a certain amount of stuff on my
On my media stuff my media slots and so I'm gonna be replacing all of it with like
organized
Planned stuff so I can play the videos and stuff on
the stream, I can play it and share my screen or just upload it right and so I don't need to like
clog up these sections with that and I can do cool stuff on them so I believe that will
go well let me see um just take I think I'll just start over start just take up everything
I'll just do custom stuff how are you guys doing
Hope you're having a nice day. It is now, what is it, September 9, 9? Wow, it's 9, 9.
99. Okay, so I woke up this morning, like the first thing I noticed when I got up this morning,
oh, there's a new triptych video and then, so last night the conversation with Christine got
I feel bad now, because I didn't think that she would...
So I've heard her talking to Crystal before, and Crystal is like, you know, saying that Christine heard her dog and stuff.
I mean, it's like just ridiculous stuff, and it's been like, you know, that's also a clip I'm sure.
And then, and Christine was just like, you know, good at defending herself, and like, oh, Crystal, you know.
So I was wanting her to come on that night, but Crystal is being outrageous, and it's like, when someone's being outrageous...
sometimes it's kind of funny to like let them be outrageous you know if anyone
took it seriously then like I'm sure Christine never you know her to fly
right it's like but you know Crystal was a Crystal who's having some ideas I
don't know it was it seemed like she was like Crystal was like also like not
really talking about Christine she was like using Christine's name but she was
like
Then she started talking about Chris K and like I mean it's like different maybe she's talking about Chris K the whole time
I don't know
But I'm sorry Christine like I don't know but don't be mad at me. I don't mean it's like
but she's short to
be mad over it
This is like other people being involved. Okay, so let me see. Oh, yeah, okay, so I do have some I
Have some audio, okay
So yeah, I'll just test up the audio file later though
Uh-oh, I don't want that one.
Maybe it's fine.
Two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, eight.
Oh shit, hard to tell what it is.
Okay, so guys, let me see.
Let me just tell a joke.
See, I need to look a lot.
Okay guys, so here's a test of the audio
Knock okay, let's see. What did the fish say? No, that's the dumb one. That's really dumb
Okay, what do you call a can opener that doesn't work a can't opener
I know, I mean it's like Detective Crystal Marie, I mean it's like, it really is X-Files, I mean it's like, I think it's one of the weirder cases I've ever seen on X-Files, Mulder and Scope, it's like, this is like a serious, I mean it was very serious, I mean if anyone took it seriously, I mean it would be considered like, you know, but she even uses her last name, she even says she was a nurse, she said she was like a first aid person or something like that.
Maybe you should talk about it like somebody else takes one from the red cross or something. I don't know
Poor pristine poor a psyche
Christine's fine. Christine's getting plenty of oh, I'm so sorry. That's like I'm getting oh
How could you do that to Christine?
That person that's not mad at me is
Well everyone's mad at me. I don't know. Maybe Crystal's not mad at me. It probably is now
I didn't need to call my name, but I mean it was pretty ridiculous. I mean, but I keep thinking.
But anyway, you guys can, oh, you want to watch it though? You can watch it on a trip.
It's kind of more a really wonka stuff. I think it's funny.
I think I'm going to be like all the scenes. I'm going to remake the movie with me.
Here we go, Christina's not happy about Crystal Marie's
allocations, gets mad at Psyche, oh yeah.
Hey, okay, guys, I didn't say it, Crystal Marie said it, right?
So it's like, why am I getting,
why do I always get yelled at?
Here, here, open up.
You can watch what happened.
Here's what happened last night.
You missed it.
Mine now.
Christine, are you there?
Yes, I'm here.
Christine, what is that about?
Oh, let me tell you what that is about.
How dare you?
How?
Fucking dare you. You don't see me going other channels talking shit about you
But you have a delusional fucking drunk up there
Saying that shit about me and then yours now. No, not our Christine and then oh, she's a nurse
Fuck you psych
you
No, no, no, no, no, you don't get to make excuses. I said he sat here and I watched the bullshit you've been doing and I've not said bullshit to you or about you at any of these other chats.
You can go straight to hell and you keep your little drunks and your little druggies and your little bulls in your chat because
People like me that have supported you for all these months will never support you again ever
Okay, well, why are you so mad why?
Wow, you know something you made yourself look down
Don't make excuses don't make excuses do not make excuses
You've been going after everybody saying they're threatening you they're saying bad things about you and you're a fucking drunk up here
talking about faggitry and Christine killed kids. And she said, I listen to it site. You
can go to f**king hell. That tree is talking about. Do you understand me? No, I don't understand
you because you're trying to say it.
I hung up on her because she told me to go to hell and
All kind of stuff. Yeah, I don't I don't know if that was like, you know, I was like letting
Chris is all like ridiculous because I thought she was and I thought nobody like believed it but
It's like Christine obviously
A lot I can't I can't tell if comes out of her mouth, you know, I was like actually
I was literally talk because it's a look worth whatever
Burp and so much
Don't give me she don't give me
And it's already been a long time ago, so it's like I'm, whatever, you mad at me?
I didn't say shit!
Why are you mad at me for people saying stuff?
It's like, why are you mad at people saying stuff and be this channel about me, like what
they do all day?
And how I'm just like this trash human being?
I know, it was gross, it was gross on me.
Hey Loki.
Loki.
I'm sorry if you don't got blocked. I saw a lot of people were blocked. I got blocked
I'm scared with Mason. I think I will take away her wrench because she doesn't seem very nice to me
I know I know what you guys it was like she might go rogue
Oh, please.
Christine.
I told her it was the car that did it.
I didn't say it was her car.
Yeah, I don't know that lady.
I remember being really mean to me one time.
I don't get it guys. Can anyone control crystals mouth? I don't know what you're saying
All I know is that it was a funny
Oh, Christopher is always a meanie
Yeah, I was trying to figure out what you were talking about
But, uh, like, Christopher really means a meanie
Yeah, I will, I will, I will, because you've gone nuts
Oh, shit, that's so loud
You dropped it before
The car is named Christine, that's what we've seen the same time
It's a killer car
But no, but that's that's that's not like a dodge. No, what kind of car was uh, I feel like I knew that trivia
Christian don't get mad at me Christian. It was funny to me because it was so off the wall
No, I'm believable. It's like you think it was something that believable. I don't think it was. I think it was obviously like
Goldman crystal Christine
She's like she's trying to get
crystals young blood
She's trying like she needs like she's trying to get
Yeah, she definitely had some like, I think she got the section shit done.
Christine, Christine.
Pumped into your lips.
Are you okay, Christine?
Hold on.
Christine, the chat.
Are you okay, Christine?
How is the car named Christine, and a nurse?
Fuck me a second.
Okay, because if you always said you were named after the car, and a nurse, and a nurse,
and a nurse, and a nurse, and a nurse, and a nurse, and a nurse, and a nurse, and a nurse,
Well, I know I am but I was like I was actually thought it was gonna funny
Which is using ridiculous things and or obviously not true
It's like there's it about me that are obviously not true. I get mad too. I understand
People in the chat were saying actually Type-V or something
Don't donate to Psyche. You wasted all this money on
on clapping people and you could have just saved that well
And everyone's saying that the whole time, right? Just to fuck with you
You finally believed it, right? It's not fun to do
Yeah isn't it funny Christine isn't it funny isn't it funny I was just on my
my best friend is spunky and I was saying it too and or like you know
laughing about it you know I mean obviously he's not true so why would I
get upset about it like that upset I mean it was annoying at first but it's
like it's obviously not true not gonna be offended it's just some idiots Christine
you know where you need to come from all right Christine
Okay, let's look at let's turn against each other person. Let's turn against each other someone that actually loves you like
Let's turn against me
And again another relationship out of like this try against me
Yeah, so anyway
That's that's like other people try it like she like because of something crystal said that that affects Christina
I think it's like
All these third parties are of course. I'm a host of a show so I'll have the third parties on it'll say it things on my show
People can't keep getting mad at me. Like I like you know, I'm I'm working on getting over it
Like I'm not in too many other chats where they're like really mean to me, but it's I'm working on like, you know my
Not feeding the trolls and stuff like that
You know, it's not always easy, but uh, because we know we're human beings, we get our feelings
sort of, but at the end of the day there's feelings, you know, it's more important to
have friendships.
I mean, if I had like malice, or like if I was like honestly like, you know, presenting
it like a serious thing, I'd understand, oh, you know, to get mad, but just because Crystal's
She was talking about so much that it didn't make any sense just getting different gangs and you know white supremacist gangs
I don't even know what she's talking about. It was just
It's kind of funny and I got neck on clip. So obviously it was kind of funny
but oh
Well
Okay, so I'm gonna make the same offer guys if you would like okay, whoever would like a reading I got this new deck
Let me just take off this. I want to show you this deck because this deck is very cool
Check out this deck.
It's still sealed, I can kind of see it.
It's by like this German artist,
his name is Felix Knacht, or something.
Yeah, believe me, Knacht or something, Felix Knacht.
And it's called The Something Dream.
But look at it, it's really trippy.
You can see like, it goes straight there,
but it's like at her face.
So if you would like the first reading from this deck,
it is still sealed, it is still sealed, right?
$10, I will open the deck, give you the first reading, and then you can pick two more people
for a reading.
So that's like three, and they'll be longer readings, and there will be three readings
within this deck, basically for ten bucks, and you'll be the hero.
If anyone's interested, I'll put my cash up then.
But I'm not opening it until I get a sponsor to open that deck. Maybe I'll use a different deck, but that's the cash up right there.
I think it's pretty reasonable.
But also, I will do like free readings. Anyone wants a free reading, of course. I'll continue to do free reading.
This works well.
I need to do this.
that. Yeah, there you go. There's a link to it. Thank you, Nightbot. Okay, perfect.
Okay. Oh yeah, it worked anyway. Okay, so that's that. Yep, it was just, yeah, it was
just crystal bad. It was like, yeah. But I do apologize, she brought up Christine the
same, but I've heard her talk to Christine before, like, I'll play this other clip and
to find a triple kick, three. It's really funny. It might be on the Rumble channel, though.
It's a big vibe, actually. It might be on the Rumble channel, though. It says Christine
is a psyche mod. She was a mod at one time, but she's like, I don't know why she was
And then Gita, Blogger, Awakens, Terra, oh my god.
Trishalicious, oh, oh, here, okay, it's this one.
Do you want to see it?
This is, is that Eldo?
I don't know if that is, hold on, look.
Thank you for being great.
Oh, oh, oh, yeah.
Travel down the road, back again.
Hey, so we started from the bottom, now we're here, girl.
Oh, yeah.
Well, and I come better.
There's my mark right here.
Hallelujah, I wish I could just like love your whole life, you know
Yeah, you're so not nice though. I know how
Manipulated or people are
We can have manipulative
100%
Man, I know you don't like me. You know, that's okay. I do
I like you. I love you. Even I don't like you. I've always been nice to you
Oh, I'm getting all the messages I've always I've always liked you. I think you're like you're you're funny
You're you know a little bit a little bit
Unpredictable. I don't think you do. I don't really think you know who I am actually
Actually, I don't
I'm a mind reader, and you are not a good, uh, actually, you don't think goodly, you
don't, you actually are not very nice to a lot of people.
You know what?
I don't give a fuck of what you could, because you don't even know who I am.
Where you don't even know who I am you're fucking wrong on everything in life
You're dead on everything in life. You have no fucking control on everything in life
And you've died on everything in life, and you have no control and everything in life, and you have no life
I'm telling you I'm telling you you are you do not know
And I wish I could tell you more
But I would never tell anybody more than they could handle
Oh, sorry, I mean, he's Louise. What did I do?
Therapy within 10 minutes crystal really
Talking about before he's stupid bitch, are you stupid or he's dog?
This bitch don't know what the fuck she's talking about, she just wants to just slap her fucking gums and act like she matters.
Crystal, go to bed, you're making a fool out of yourself again.
Oh shut up, Christine. Oh Christine, hey, why don't we get the teams that match each other before we talk to us?
Hey, how about two blonde hairs that like...
Bleach?
What?
I did two blonde hairs of bleach.
Why would I do two blonde hairs of bleach?
Christine, Christine, figure it out.
Christine, go to bed, go to bed,
and figure out when a fucking two hairs blow a fucking die
of two hairs of bleach.
Oh, my gosh, Christina, Christine, you need to go to bed.
Wake up.
One cup of coffee.
Two hairs and a bleach.
You're making a fool out of yourself.
Again.
Oh, my gosh.
This bitch is trying to say I'm making a fool out of myself.
When she's fucking fooling her, she's fucking shit all over the fucking blaze.
She's fooling herself in three different counties of America
Three different counties over America. Oh, yeah
Bullying all of us Christine has been bullying like every female and every male like
She was like bullying people that didn't even need it birds. I got birds all over this. I got
I think that bird is chirping.
What?
Is the popo still watching us today?
Oh, oh, which ones we don't know you every time I come in here you say the popo's watching us
Dude, I never said the popo's are watching you dude. You're fucking tripping
Every time
You crack-core bitch!
I never said like the fucking pop-up of the ride
that you're launching.
That's my summer baby!
I love summer.
One second, she'll catch up very soon, I'm sure.
Christine, shut the fuck up, crack-core.
Christine's a crack-core and fucking talking about my girl,
fucking summer like she can fucking like,
she even has a fucking right to fuck around girls.
Excuse me?
I had no clue you just battled.
Don't you ever talk about how it goes, I really like that.
I'll talk about that all at once.
Fuck you.
Shut up, bitch.
Who are you telling shut up?
My girl, Summer. Shut up.
Irvi, you know I don't have to fight over Summer, right?
No, I'm not sure apparently doesn't know, you know that right, you know why I would never
Ammo like you did
Yeah, I feel like she abused her dog
I'll crystal you don't be ridiculous. You're not see my dog. You see how beautiful my dog is
My dog is far from beautiful your dog is and it seems to be used
Oh, yeah, Fawzi's really abused.
Yeah, you abuse a fuck out of it.
Hey, hey, hey.
Crystal, Crystal, Crystal, Crystal, Crystal.
I'm gonna smash you for fucking Fawzi.
Crystal, Crystal, Crystal, Crystal, Crystal, no threats.
Don't you dare.
Crystal.
I know.
She's an abused Fawzi.
Excuse me. Crystal, are you seriously losing your mind? She is.
Even my chickens live in a five-star resort, right? Yeah, only your chickens, but not Fawzi.
I think that dog is the happiest dog. He wrestles with the cat. I came up, Christine.
So what's your cost by resort is a full perm
Fucking print yourself for the last 10 weeks
She's never moving herself
Oh, no, myself.
Well, she was trying to make everybody else be in me now,
so now come and she can prove herself.
Well, she is like my best friend in her life,
so I kind of know who she is.
Oh, gosh.
Well, the guy doesn't matter right now.
That's why I said, she said,
I'll never have your love, I'm thinking why.
No, I said it doesn't matter.
I said it doesn't matter.
I've had some in the world.
You understand that it fucking doesn't matter.
Somewhere I love, I love the way that you are,
These other people, I cannot do it
because they're so fucking retarded.
They are not themselves.
They fake themselves, okay?
Okay, they fake.
Okay, this bitch acts like me.
I was just talking about Christine.
She's pretty honest, she is.
Oh, you don't lie, Christine.
Yeah, she's a liar bitch,
unless it's what I'm curious about.
I know her whole life, like offline.
Well, you might not know her as well as I do, then.
Okay, here we go.
I guess you know her like you know Marcy, right?
Well, these bitches do weird shit on the internet.
It's fucking weird, dude.
I don't know what the fuck is going on.
I can tell you, but I know every move Christine's made on the internet in the last four years.
Well, okay. Oh, she has to have a cat. Well, you need to put me on game. This is my friend a secret
You want you want a bus now right now? She's got all my
I need some excitement today. I've had a long week
Nah, that Christine chick, I don't like that that fucking backhanded
Compliment shit. I don't like people that do that stuff that backhanded fucking compliment bullshit. You know what I say
Exactly how I feel and I don't want to talk to you again
What it means when it means that you suck
Not suck thick I
Suck
No, you're being a bad friend to be that
Then you're being a bad friend to our girl
Chris I heard you say horrible horrible horrible
Wait, I've heard you say a really bad thing.
I've never even said it.
Because Bita likes to go behind the scenes.
I don't like people that goes behind the scenes.
Crystal, Crystal, I've heard you say horrible things to Bita.
I've never said anything.
I might have said the B word, like, one time.
And then, oh!
And then I never said it.
And then, I was, it's fine, it's fine.
I don't care what I was saying.
I heard you went crazy on Mother's Day
when you left them on panels.
be like somebody else thank you is i don't like these people i don't like the people that go out
for people to hurt people and like are like dirty disgusting humans like this guy
he gives me bad
The birds
Look at his fucking face dude, he looks like he's got to take a big huge shit. Can we see your face?
Go you're fucking can we see your face you have to take a shit everybody knows that we see it on your face
I just did like we see that shit on your face. Why are you in the bird? Why are you trying to hurt my friend?
Just to piss you off
I just talked to God. I got off the phone with him. He said fuck Chris
to all of you which in Japan, so you're proud of that.
No, no, no, no, Crystal, Crystal, Crystal, Crystal, Crystal.
Oh, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Who's trying to hurt your friend now with those tears?
That guy, that guy is, that guy is both of those.
Look at his face.
How are you going to answer my question, that guy?
Like, you're not answering my question.
That guy in the middle.
Do you know who you're talking to, bird lady?
That weirdo in the middle, that weirdo sicko in the middle.
that weirdo sicko. You know who he is. Everybody knows who he is. We all see who he is. He's
put in a big ol' shiny fucking, he's shining his fucking, he's shining his fucking rock.
Dude, your head is as big as a boulder. Everybody can see from a mile fucking way. We all know
who you are.
Is it too big for my body?
100% damn
Oh, girls just don't want to have fun
The phone rings in the middle of the night
But what the hell's what you gonna do with your life?
Oh daddy diggin' though you still know
how was it? I thought it was pretty funny. But Christine was laughing then and she was saying
even worse thing. I don't know. I don't know. So I thought she was funny again, but maybe not.
Maybe she had to be there. She was talking about Christine from the band of the opera,
I think, Christine Di-A, not the Christine we all know about. Okay, is that better? I don't know.
I don't know.
So, uh, there's a banner of the opera, Christine, I love that opera, let's see, I'm gonna go
to my, so I have things, I was trying to post things on SoundCloud but I couldn't, I put
it on MixCloud, and then it's like, I didn't try to transfer it to my Spotify, and it didn't
And I tried taking the title and then the title wasn't working either, so I don't know what's wrong, but I'm trying to, like, see, oh, AI 2.0?
Okay, let's see. Mixed Cloud. Here we go.
Ooh, I have followers. Ooh.
Oh, my God. Somebody followed my song. I'll play it.
Like my song, okay
Roll side of the panel
My son he let someone like my song. I feel like wow
The dashboard
Tracks
Five total plays five minutes listen, okay?
There's rules my tracks, okay, what do you like you liked?
Oh, a troll side of the panel.
Is that what he likes?
Troll side of the panel or is he like the troll song?
It's a good song.
Troll side of the panel.
Okay.
It is a good song.
I feel like,
I feel like I've been locked out.
Spent my soul in a way I shouldn't have thought out.
A part of my brain
Mason
psych yeah
Hey, so it's like so we're still cool
Yeah
It's like so why'd you get on earlier though? I thought you know we get on like at night
No, I was I woke up at like 7 30 this morning
So I was like I'll go on because I was already on a strip kick video this morning
I was like I was going
So it's like it's like you normally don't go on it's like you normally don't go on this early though, right?
I do sometimes if I feel like it like I just like you're like streaming right now. It's like a little bit of a
Slow day, and I'm just have my coffee and so might as well
Hang out with you hang out with you guys while I'm a little energy. So it's like who is that?
Who is that you're with though where he was anybody today or last night?
today
No, I'm not with anybody just my kitty cats. Well, that was like I was playing an old show
Psych so you weren't so that was just you play it that wasn't really you like that was with the other people
I was just something you were showing that was yeah, that was that was like a few months ago
That was a Christine a few months ago
But remember last night you were on the phone with me and then you like Christine came on and you left
Why'd you leave last night? I never left what Christine was on
Yeah, I thought she scared you off the panel because she was so mad
No, Christine wasn't actually on there some other person out on there another woman, right?
Okay, I was crystal. Well, it was crystal wasn't there. It was Christine. No, it was Christine
No, but I was talking to you when he talked to that other guy last night. He said the guy named
The guy that you said they had the big huh big pipes. Mr. Big Pipe. Yeah, mr. Big Pipe
Yeah, he was on
What happened to him? I think he choked on his harmonica or something or his kazoo or something like that
What do you mean?
What do you mean he choked on his harmonica?
You know he plays he has like a harmonica and a banjo at the same time
And so when you have him look at the same time like he hit him hit the harmonica and he actually swallowed it
So you made it sound like it's like it's like you gotta be it's like you gotta be joking like breakfast. No, it's true
It was really funny. It was really funny and then he uh, then he actually he passed it
Slice, it's like who was that was there somebody else that was just talking
Right now
Yeah
No
You're here. So you're not bringing it. I don't know. I thought I heard somebody else's voice just a second ago on here
Like a woman's voice?
Yeah.
No.
I'm just hearing things.
You're hearing things.
And what, so are you laying down,
like are you like tired or are you laying down like that?
You're like almost horizontal.
Wait, I don't understand, it's like, huh?
Like you're like, honestly, this is like Mesa right now.
Like you're like, hi, hi.
I mean, it's like it's like what's wrong? I mean, what it's like what am I doing? That's wrong
That you're doing anything wrong
It's don't people in the chat are wondering if you if you're up if you're like a paraplegic because you're you're you're just laying down
What is what does that mean? It's like what does that mean a paraplegic?
Do you have it you are you know, are you in a wheelchair or do you walk?
I can walk, Charles, what do you mean?
I can walk, I can walk, I can walk, I can walk,
I can walk, I can walk, I can walk,
Yeah, this is not
It's like I don't understand though like how is that like the wheelchair what makes
His legs work cuz he's like he's laying down weird and I was like
You look like you're just like on your bed like laying down in your bed like the camera above you
It's like I don't get how that's wrong though like what's wrong
Mason are you playing are you you're just playing? You're just kidding. You're like you're like you're like way
Quicker than I think right you're even fooling me
Wait, wait, what do you mean? It's like, you know like pretending now you're playing your little innocent
You know act, but it's like you're really like you're really like a shark. You're like so smart. Hey Troy
Hey, what's up? Welcome to my kick audience. I'm just kidding. Mason. Mason, you know
Mason, are you thought about are you gonna come visit me yet or and you can try some stuff?
Yeah, yeah, okay
It's like but I'm not it's like I'm not in the wheelchair though. Why would I just know you're not
It's like it's like who would say that who would say that though who would say that I was in a wheelchair
They said
They said this may sends legs work. Why is he always laying down and then God he said oh, he's just lazy
And then Time said, no, he's acting weird.
And then the fucking Gloky said, I think it's the pillow.
And then Time said, oh, it's cool.
No judgment, just wondering.
And then Gloky's like, oh, he's hearing something.
It's like, where do you see that?
I don't see the...
In the chat.
You have to be in the regular chat, though.
It's not in the private chat.
Mason I'm just kidding like Mason. I'm not gonna we don't have to we don't have to we don't have to kiss
Huh, only if you want to
But remember I said I was like the best
Psycho bastard after talking to that Mason guy watching him. I can only think he's either playing dumb or just playing dumb
Are you playing dumb or playing dumb?
Huh, are you playing dumb or playing dumb?
I'm not playing dumb like I'm not playing dumb. I know you're not like he says so like he says maybe he fired
No, it's like he said maybe he fried his brain cells on drugs. See guys. He can read perfectly. See you got to read
You're pretty good
You knew the difference fired and fried
Hey, so like I never
It's like I never did drugs before
Just tell the chat how old you are, okay, you're like in your 30s, right? It's like I'm 35. I'm exactly
So like so like so what does it mean that I have a bit on so I'm assuming he's in a wheelchair also
You have a big bomb
That's what they said. They said I have a big one. It's like why would you say I'm a big one is that what a bit?
What is that thing on your shirt? What is that all this food all over it?
But wait, what's that your shirt or what's that? It's that white cloth on you that your blanket
Your shirt
It's like it's like I'm not understated like I have something with me. Yeah
What are you wrapped? Are you wrapped in a bandage? What is that?
What is that?
Syke, what?
What is it? Oh, hello. Oh, yeah.
Oh, my blanket.
Oh, you have pants on, right?
Yeah, Syke, what?
Oh, that's too bad.
Oh, hello.
Oh, are you happy to have me or is that a rocket in your pocket?
Syke.
Yeah. Oh, I like it.
Look at your feet. How big are your feet?
Syke.
Yeah?
I know. They look like, are those size 15? They look big.
Do you like having your toes sucked on?
It's like, what do you think? It's like, I like it. I like it.
Is that a sock on it? Or is it? Oh yeah, you're wearing socks.
That's down a little bit. Can you take off your sock? Slowly.
It's like, what? I'm just kidding.
I like it. Why are your socks so dirty? What are you even walking around in the dirt?
It's like what do you mean why they're so dirty? I thought they were black socks, but it's just dirt on them
It's like they're just socks
Yeah, it's like they're dirty. How are your feet? Are your feet like do they hurt your feet clean or they?
Yeah, that's getting a little freaky Mason Mason like you like your feet rubbed
Like the site they're not too dirty, right?
No, they're perfect. It's just perfect. Hold on a second. We have a guest.
Uh-oh. Oh, he left. It was a fake Sam Man.
We almost got a-
Psyche, was it somebody tried to do a poor bob or something like that?
Yep, it was a fake Sam Man.
I thought it was Sam Man.
No, but Psyche, look.
No, Psyche, I'm in my room, though. You see my room?
I know, I see. Okay.
Is that bed is that one of those um, one of those temp that goes beds that like, you know
Craftmatic where they like it goes up and down. Yeah. Oh, what do you do? Oh, you're pulling down here
What are you doing? But where's your hand?
Rubbing yourself. It's like it's like it's like
Like what you like the shirt. Yeah
Like what?
It's like what what was somebody poor bombing you or something or what happened? Well you your your your your mom was your feet
You want more pillows Mason?
Huh you want more pillows Mason?
Yeah, that's like this is a pillow that I'm in right now. It's like I'm in my bed. Yeah
See site. No, I always said I always said I wanted to date a Mason and here you are
It's like this is my bed cycling. That's your bed. It's a big bed
How many roommates do you have that sleep in there with you?
Just me site remember when you said the group home you like to get in bed with the guys
Yeah, but yeah, but I'm not there anymore. So like I stayed by myself now in my own place
Somebody living in that house
Huh, I'm gonna come live with you
I'll show you're bed. Yeah, like but like this side these people are saying like weird stuff about me, right?
Like I'm I'm a wheelchair stuff. Oh
I know
Like psych psych so what do you think site? Oh my god, look at that bulge
Like what?
You're both like what do you think psych? What do you think? I like it, but you just want to show me your feet and stuff
That huh like you're gonna show me your feet
So I like like what do you know? Do they have a foot fetish? Well, I like your face. I like you go like this
What do you tell me?
There you go, sorry. Oh my gosh
So like that's what you like, right? Oh you got shy, okay, it's okay. It's like I got shy. Yeah
Okay, it's okay
It's like everybody's it's like it's not gonna just be you see me right it's gonna be other people too. That's why I was yeah
Everyone saw
Like so they know that I have a bib on right psych, but it's no big
Bib on them like why are you why are you wearing it?
Like I've never had a bit
When I was like that was never a bit wrapped around your chest
There's like something that's different color than your rest of your shirt
It's like that was not a bib like that was that was a blanket. It's like that was the covers blanket
Are you are you nude under those jeans?
No, but it's like I have clothes on though. I showed you. Oh, yeah, I know I was really disappointed
Why psyche don't want me to have clothes on at least not socks. I mean, it's like you're really covered up
It's like it's like hold on. It's like look hold on somebody Hannah said that Mason is verbally spamming
I'm not spamming though. It's like how much family Hannah's. Hannah's just
Hannah's
Hello, please name
Curzon I think God says we are on our own now. Yeah
God help us all. Yeah, I
Think that's a blind. Did you see that? Yeah, it's from the Christmas carol. Like did you see somebody say?
Did you see somebody say, God help us all?
Yeah, I agree.
God, he can help.
I don't know if God can help.
But did somebody else want to come up and talk to Mason?
Maybe we'll have another room.
I would just be in, no, it's like I was just
being normal the whole time.
I mean, why would somebody think that I was?
You are normal.
I don't know why everyone's.
Why do why no, I've seen what why would they want to pick on me for though? I don't understand that
I don't think they're picking on you. I think they're picking on me for
Trying to date you
But I'm saying you're 35 years old, you know how to say the word fried in between fried and fired
You're perfectly intelligent
Sight yeah, somebody said that you're Hanna said that you're an idiot for asking for Goddy
Yeah, well, I am you know, I shouldn't have done that
But you know what? It's too late now. I already I already I already called them into the room and
What wait so we can't get it looks
Yeah, I'm here. Yeah, okay, we have a big exam and again. Hold on. Yes me. It's the real guy
First of all, no one gives a fuck what Hannah has to say, right? That's one number two
I think it's disgusting how you're trying to seduce this kid. What the fuck is going on?
Seducing this fucking kid alive on you. Is this the new format? You're just gonna seduce these fucking young kids on the show
What the fuck?
He has the mind of a child. He has the mind of a fucking
Can't see this
The
Really younger. Yes, like I'm really younger in my mind, but I can my body is like
see how old is your mind
My mind is like a like a 15 year old or 18 year old maybe more like 10. I would say 10 probably
I was a clinical psychologist for fucking 10 years. I know this shit. Yes. Yes, I fucking see the signs
Just laid lay low take it easy on the kids like you don't have to jump in bed with the guy right away
Give it a few months. What the fuck?
Yeah, yeah, just chill you don't have to fucking rape him with your eyes for God's sake. Hey, Goddy. Don't even use that word
What happened it's like, why is he saying all that stuff?
Hey, what's up Frankie?
Hi.
What's going on, Mason?
You know, Mason?
It looks like Mason.
Jay Dogg.
What's popping on me?
Hey, Jay Dogg, why is everybody picking on me for?
I mean, like, the guy, God, that just came on here.
What did I do?
I think, in all honesty, they think you're playing.
I mean, I'm going to shoot straight.
Is it cool if I talk freely, psychic?
Well, it's cool.
OK.
I don't want to disrespect your panel or anything like that.
Everybody thinks you're playing dumb. They think that you're
You know, you're you know more than what you're saying
Like they're asking if you're in a wheelchair. You're just laughing it off
like people are asking like legit questions and you're just like not you're just laughing it off and like not answering the question and
No, no
No, it's like I already told you that I'm not in the wheelchair though man, so that's the answer right there. I know
No
You know guy name what's the guy's name that we used to call him to be to show you girl
Oh Chris Hall Chris Hall
We don't know if he was like pretending or if he was like
There's another one too all over Jabroni all over Jabroni's the other one
Yeah, yeah
No, that's that was it. I got no beef with you Mason. I got no beef
Hey, psych I already gave my answer though to that
I wasn't just laughing about it psych I was really getting my real answer
Don't worry about like you know what you're fine. You're fine. You know what?
I was just kidding about the having something up there. I know you're a straight guy. You like you like like PUSSY, right?
What do you like PUSSY?
What is that?
Are you he's asking are you what what team do you go for are you on the left team?
Are you on the right team? What team are you on? That's what he's on. I'm on I'm on just like Sykes team. Yeah
Okay. All right. All right. Cool. See you psyche not night. No potential mate right here
We're playing baseball. Yeah. Okay. And amazing. So you're the catcher. I'm a pitcher, right?
Yeah
Yeah, exactly
No, hold on. That'd be like opposite teams though
I'm confused. Okay. It's okay. Jay dog. What's up? Hey, hey, Jay dog. What's up?
So what what what do you think about what the people say like about like the way things are and stuff like that?
Is there anything going on or?
About what specifically like you gotta give me like a little more specifics in that like
The one of the guys said that I had a brain of like a young person
Oh, where'd it go
You're you're absolutely wonderful. I'm fine. I don't know if people are
He's already admitted to sleeping with you know with men before so I'm assuming he's already
Also, he was cuddling then okay
Got a good cuddly buddy right there, bro. He got right there. Hell yeah
Would you be cool with Mason if he came over to stay with you and your visit for a bit?
I'm afraid he'll like come with like a suitcase. I'm like
Oh hell no, we're trying to move in like all heck
You're my new guardian, uh-oh
Well, you better make sure you get a paycheck for him if you're his new guardian cuz oh
Yeah
Yep. Hell yeah
Well, dude, that's fucking
But it's like you know, I didn't mean to come up here, bro. I'm like fuck up like you're
Your thing your thing bro. I know you and Mason got something going like
Dude the same thing happened with me and christine the other you remember when christine got mad at me
A while back maybe like a month ago because she said I was doxing when I wasn't I was given a fake name
And she said that's still doxing. So I think christine
You know, she takes a little too serious than what it is
like
Because I think that's the Marie she just talked shit. That's just how that's just you know what she does
She gets drunk comes up here and just you know makes up crap and you know, it's just for content for fun
Yeah
Don't play my meth on oh shit you probably allied master dude, that's like the main guy who's been like
Have you noticed it's the same guy Tony the conductor same fucking guy
From what I hear he's upset with you because he came out on your show and you rejected him
Is that true psychic because I don't remember that I don't remember I wasn't here for that
I was around but I didn't see that episode. I wasn't
He said it wasn't attracted to me and then
He like sort of saying that but he said he was coming out of the fall. He said he just came out of the closet
Then I heard black RG say that ally master computer was his spy for him
And he said he was he was just pretending to be gay to like get my sympathy or to get my
To get your trust. Yeah
and
that um
He um, he was probably sitting in my discord voice chat right then what she was doing like he was like always he was like
taking my the discord chats and playing them on
like our G show and through the updoor or whatever.
Oh, shit, damn, so that motherfucker was infiltrating.
He was pretending to be cool with you and stuff.
But dude, I legit, I think he really is gay, though.
Like, I think he really is like legit gay.
And I was like, what the heck?
That's crazy.
Because you know who music Biz Marty is, right?
You know he hit on music Biz Marty before.
Oh, we did yeah, yeah music, but you know music Bismarie laugh get off, you know because he's a straight guy
Like I'm a straight guy like you know like someone says something funny to me
I'm just like okay like like music Bismarie because Marty
I really liked me and Marty called me underdog and stuff and like you know Marty was like on the show and I
Send me some money, you know what do you want to know something crazy?
Thank you that I've heard more than from one person that you wouldn't you were next you were
supposedly Marty's next
Target as far as like project or however you want to call it a logo. Yeah
Yeah, I was but then he like he'd like me because I was like winning him money sports betting and so he changed his mind
Yeah, you were a cool guy. He liked you. Yeah, look at the kitty cat. It looks like tricks
Look just like it look you look like sisters and brothers
Is that your friend? Is that a girl? Oh, here, Mason's back.
Mason. Okay. Hey, Mason. Hey, psych, why did you why did you kick me off for? What did I do?
I did it. You disappeared. You accidentally kicked yourself off. Hey, Axe. Hey, crazy.
But, Mason, where are your parents? What do you mean, where's my parents? Why?
No, I was living in a grip home, but I need more but you can't you live on your own?
Yeah, where are your parents?
I'm old enough to be on my own though. It's like why would it why would I need my parents?
You still talk to them
Yeah, I still talk to my mom, but I don't really see my dad only see my mom
Someone wants to know why were you in a group home? These questions are too invasive. You know the answer
Okay, just
No, the reason no site the reason why was in a group on this because I needed
Somewhere to sleep and I didn't have a place at the time in my mom was homeless
Okay, yeah, I'm sorry. I don't mean to like
It's wondering
What's up? Hey, Jay dog
What's up?
My mom she was homeless, so I had no place to stay so that's why I went to a group home and I paid to stay there
Oh, they make you pay to stay there. I don't know how that operates like how does that operate?
You have to pay to stay there like or do you have to have like mental? Um, what do they call it?
Not mental health issues. Do you have to have a certain type of handicap?
Like is there certain requirements to live in a group home or can anybody just go over there?
I believe it. I believe anybody could go there, but you have to have like SSI if you get SSI
Bingo, that's what I'm getting at. Okay. Cool. All right. That's all I wanted to know
Yeah, did I take some of the SSI check from you Mason for the
No, but like I get a SSI check and that's why they allowed me to be at the group home
Even though I was my mom and I were both homeless
I'm glad that you're taking care of me son. It's seven
Sebastian
Hey Sebastian
Yeah, Mason to what people were thinking earlier man, and I think that too like we either get the impression that you're either
You're playing dumb or you're you're dumb. Yeah, but are you playing dumb or you you got a handicap? Tell us the truth, man
No, I have mental issues though. That's all Sebastian. It's not like that playing dumb or anything. Okay. You got mental health issues, okay
Yeah, it's like he's coming across as he's playing more dumb than he's and he actually is
He seems like a smart guy. He's well-spoken. Mason's really well-smoking. You know that he got good communication skills. So, you know, I
I don't think he's done. He's smarter than he lets on. Yes. Yes. There you go
Yeah, and even he even gets like inside jokes and stuff like that
Yeah, he's pretending to be dumb he's not that dumb I think he's
Right so I thought a pillow right now. That's what's on that's what I have behind me
Yeah, well people think I'm in a wheelchair. I'm not in a wheelchair though
You prove get wrong Mason you prove get wrong we saw you're in landing your bed you're chilling you can move your feet
You know, you're good. You're a normal guy. We'll give you the benefit of the doubt
Yeah
So you're all good Mason
But Mason if you're lying the cost will be substantial and the refund policies will be prohibited
It's a joke bro. It's a joke. Yeah, it's a joke. How's it hanging dog? Jay dog
Chillin bro chillin. How about you Sebastian? Yeah, just chillin. Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you, dude
What's up, what's your name at Christine last night? Oh, I didn't see it. I didn't see it
So I was watching baseball yesterday
She called it very mad wait wait Sebastian the only thing I didn't understand if you said that my brain was right on drugs
I never do drugs. So
There's one of the things I asked you didn't you didn't do any hard drugs in your life
No, I know I've never really done drugs that was bad. I tried them before but that was it
Did you smell crack
I can't remember what it was like, but it was something but I don't think it was I wasn't serious about it though
Like I only tried it out and that was all I did like I tried to drugs like I think it was like weed or something
I tried that like before
No, come on hey, bro, hey bash my hey, you know what it's like. Hey, have you ever met flirty diamonds Mason?
Huh?
You're a met flirty diamonds. No, okay. I think you might want to meet her do you do you?
I'll explain who she is I'll explain who she is um
Flirty diamond is a transgender
Worker sex worker
She's been on here before more than a few times
You know, she goes on beta. She goes on a lot of other people's screen. She actually does her own live stream
I believe to so but do you guys hear what happens supposedly with her like the rumor why nobody's heard from her
She's oh, she's she's in she's in Minnesota tricky
Yeah, but but they're saying that she got I guess
It's hot like by a John or something like that. I don't know how true that is. That's just the rumor
I don't know that's what I'm asking you guys. You got tree. Have you heard anything about it?
Okay, so there they're okay then they're okay
Okay, cool. I'm got he's trying to troll hard inside jet. I think you're the one that's gay gotty
I ain't gave us for sure man. I meant the women
You know
Jay dog, this is pillow right here. That's behind my head right here. That's what I'm I know I see it I know I see it
Bro, I see it. I see it. I'm in my bed. I know I know I see we all see it bro
You don't have to prevent anything to nobody we believe you Mason. We believe you
Amazed I want to say you don't need to show your feet man. We don't want to see that we only want to see women's feet
I
Want to see like you want to see my feet and stuff though man. That's what you told me
Yeah, so I close the thing then spike is more than welcome to see whatever he wants to say. That's only psych
That's not the rest of us. You want to be treated like everybody else or do you want to be treated special?
Okay, I want to know that are you talking to me psych are you talking to me?
You want me doing special treatment like like you don't mean to like pretend like, you know, you're not like an adult
Stuff doing it pretend like you're 15 and like, you know, I shouldn't be even talking to you because you're so
childlike or are you
Like what do you feel you feel like
Those like I thought you wanted to see my feet. They said you want to see what?
I'd rather see Hannah's feet
We don't want to see that.
Oh, dude, so what happened with Chris come Marie get psyche what happened what that she came up?
Just was she just plastered and guess. Oh, you don't hear it. I have to show you that
So this is what happened the other day, this is like probably two nights ago and Crystal called it
And this is the x-files they have on it. I see that video. I do that was a funny video
Yeah, I saw that one, but I'm just I'm wondering like what happened with Christine
Why is it just because of the back and forth banter is there more to it than I'm missing?
I looked at the replay your stream yesterday, they were having an argument, huh? Yeah, this is only six minutes
Jay dog, what state you live in? I'm in Kelly. Oh, you're in California. Okay
Here we go. Sebastian. I'm in New Orleans. Oh, you are. That's awesome. Here you go. You're watching this
Christina you're there. Yes, I'm here. Christine. What is that about? Oh, let me tell you what that is about
How dare you. How fucking dare you. You don't see me going other channels talking shit about you, but you have a delusional fucking drunk up there, saying that shit about me, and then you're saying, oh, no, not our Christine, and then, oh, she's a nurse. Fuck you, psych. Fuck you.
Wow.
You don't get to make excuses I said he sat here and I watched the bullshit you've been
doing and I've not said bullshit to you or about you and any of these other chats you
can go straight to hell and you keep your little drunks and your little druggies and
People like me that have supported you for all these months will never support you again ever
Well, you know something you made yourself look
don't make excuses. Don't make excuses. Do not make excuses. You've been going after everybody
saying they're threatening you. They're saying bad things about you. And you're the fucking drunk
up here talking about fagotry and Christine Kim. And he said, I listen to it site. You can go to
No, I don't understand you.
It's like, I understand you.
She's talking about the tree of us slurs.
Yeah, I don't know, I thought it was like,
no, I was like, Chris is so like, ridiculous
because I thought she was,
and I thought nobody like believed it,
but it's like, Christine, I was like,
I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't tell if it comes
out of her mouth, you know?
I was like, actually, I was at her top
because it makes her look weird, whatever.
Burping so much, sir.
Come on, give me, she don't give me.
And it's already been a long time ago, so it's like, I know it's assy, but it was like, I was like, exposing all the crystals I've been mad at me.
You wouldn't believe it.
I didn't say shit.
Why are you mad at me for people saying stuff?
It's like, am I supposed to be mad at people saying something?
Be this channel about me?
Like, which they do all day.
Oh, God.
And how I eat it.
I'm just like this trash human being.
And it was gross.
It was gross on me.
That was ridiculous.
You scared me Mason, and I think I will take away her lunch because she's
Guys
Sassy, I got oh she might go
Like she really scared me
Oh, please
I
Told her it was the car that did it
I remember being really mean to me one time. I know it was crossing the line, but I don't
I want to control crystals about I don't know what you're saying. All I know is that it was a funny
She's always like really mean I will I will I will proceed
Okay, so anyway, that's that basically she's got very mad that shoot on the chat. She was saying oh well you have HIV and stuff like that
Which is her? Oh, it's like I know she ran me away though
What's up?
I know she ran me away though because you disappeared as soon as she came up
No, I was there when she was there remember you said like this is who she was and stuff like that
Then where were you then because you just appeared off the panel, so she must have like
I know I know
It was just too, but she was being too funny though
It was like no, but I was there. No, it's like I was there the whole time almost when I was talking to you like when I was talking to
Like I didn't really leave until the end
Hey, John. I mean, uh, okay
Thank you. Can I ask you a question, bro? Um, it's Christine over there on
Beta's channel. Yeah, is she a mod over there?
I think so and I haven't seen her since the whole beta stuff happened. I haven't she's like she hasn't been my chat at all
Okay, I have a complete this this might sound crazy as shit, but this gets kind of you know, like an epiphany kind of thing
What if
Beta's rallying up all like the women's supporters like these guys. Have you noticed page hasn't been around?
Have you noticed certain players haven't been around and then she was on betas and she didn't come back to mine
Yeah
Yeah, like a lot of people like I like that. It's of course there to take me aside, but it's like
But why are they taking my crazy local side like that girl is crazy
How are they gonna take her side when they see the way that girl acts on live?
Dude, look what she said about clumsy's, you know, I'm not even saying but look what she said about look what she said about you, bro
Like she said she fucking when you ask for help
You know when people call a friend in need and need help because something's not right
You don't tell them. Oh, just fucking do it. Why are you calling me like who the fuck does that only a crazy person does like that?
She didn't do it that night when I texted her, but it was later on the show when she
was talking to Sig and Rando, she said, she was telling what I said, or exaggerating because
she said I sent 65 messages and all this stuff, and then she was like saying...
You know, she said exactly what I said
Just do it, you know, just do it, you know, so which is not very nice. No, it's not at all
Man, that's like calling 9-1-1 and the operator says oh figure it out yourself, and you're like
Well, you know, so what do you think what do you think about like what would happen to stuff like that? Was it wrong?
What do you mean? Well, what part was wrong?
What they decided to tell ya a hundred percent the way they treated psyche the way psyche was abused by that big fuck
Yeah, hundred percent. Yeah
I'll talk about the stuff that happened with the psyche. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it was wrong a hundred percent
And you know, it was you know, what's the most fucked up part about this entire thing
She made she drew a line in the sand when they're getting half to be a lying drawn
There's never had to be a good mate
Like she's like
You know, she said anybody that's like has you on the show she's not gonna talk to me more and all this kind of stuff
That's ridiculous. That's like little behavior. No, but J dog
I can't help it though, man
I might have brain damage or something because I'm not as smart as I mean I could be smart
But I mean there's some times where my you know when I talk I like social skills still
Yeah, no, that's cool, man. You're you good. I got people to make you I got no be put you at all man
I got no big
Yeah, I got no beef with you either
Yeah, we're cool. We're good
Thank you, man. Sebastian. I can't really help like the way I talk sometimes. That's just the way I talk
You talk good you talk real good
You'd I talk worse than you bro, cuz I'm high all the time when I slur
You good bro, you're good like there's no issues with you. You're good
But psyche haven't you noticed that bro like you just noticed all that that I just brought up like all that shit is like conjuring
It's been and it's like little kid behavior like, oh, I'm not going to be cool with you because you're cool with that person.
Or you let that person on the panel. You let that person in the chat.
It's like, okay, you can have mutual friends. I'm pretty sure there's mutual friends that you and Bita have.
that you don't like or necessarily, you know, get away with it.
No, it's like everybody takes, everybody's like, well not everybody, like there's people here of
course, but it's like, yeah, most people I see like a lot of my mods over that like are full
of mods, like, you know, it's like, soul to me saying bad stuff about me, like just leaving
everything that's said in chat and everything. I think he's got the cats and it's like-
It's really annoying. It's like people that know me know that I've been on every single day for like except for like two days this whole year
And so if I life is pretty much out like after like everyone can see everything, you know, it's like I don't
You came on panel while you were sick
Yeah, you were sick. Do you remember that you were you were you know, you weren't feeling well
You were under the weather you had like the flu or something and like you literally ran like a 24 hour stream that time
That was like a lot of people can't don't do that and can't do that. It's like you did that
while you were you know you
The show must go on and you prove that and you met the show went on even though you weren't feeling
You know your best you weren't up for it necessarily or you know
You're physically you were ill. Yeah, you weren't
Yeah, he did that's why that's why a lot of people are still around the ones that are around are the ones that that really
I'm day ones those are the ones that are you'll see the loyalist ones and the ones that got your back and the ones that you know
Stick up for you and fight for you like how come other how come when you go another out chat
Let's say if you go and beat us how come these mods don't stick up for you when you're over there
But they'll stick up for somebody else, but anybody else is cool, but psyche that they're just completely just pretend like you're not there
That's true
I lurk because you have to bro you have to sometimes because you got to see it's kind
of like putting your your ear against like the you know the the wall you have to because
you got to hear what they're going to say about you but I don't go in there to like
stay there and like listen but as soon as I get in there most of the time there's talk
about me and something so
And it's always negative stuff. It's never positive. It's always negative. It's always he get that broke. Tell me this
Have I ever said anything about?
Sexual that beta goes with her cats or anything animals beside the black RG crap
Okay
But she also she like here's things like how she wants to hear that like my song and the beat is biscuit song
They say it's insulting Iran
She was saying it's a talk about her cousin and it said that she broke her teeth out of her mouth
But you didn't say any of that. There's like that's not one of those
AI song
She she got all that from a from a song bro. She she picked all that up from she is nuts
She's fucking maybe she's Josie. Oh, yeah, 100% she is
Well, I'm the bad boy in town. Yes
You tell me what you doing
You listen to this dick suck a J-dog, right? No, you know, ain't nobody
Don't talk to me nigga. You don't hear talking to me. No, no, no
Slendering not gonna slander me. What's me slander?
You up here saying dick sucker
Okay, okay, that's Lander we're going back to that. All right, that's Lander though
That I was a slander that happened. Okay, that's don't get me cooking nigga
Maybe you could cook all you want and nobody's stopping to lay me up if you want
So what up site? What was the problem? What's up?
I'm talking to site
I'm totally I'm totally cool. I'm just so what's up? Well, what it is?
What's up? What's up with you and beat up miss?
Don't hold on hold on site the tattoo you got in your chest the person you still represent right you still got kitty gang on your chest
That's the nor and that's you now stands for Burger King
Bro, no you kitty gang until you remove that
Yeah, oh, yeah, you kitty gang until you
Hey sassy go ahead psych I'm gonna let you talk
Okay, well, yeah, whatever I
It's not about that. I didn't know it was actual like I was it was an actual street gang
You know, it's like that she's like, you know, it's not a street gang site. Come on
Like a Mexican, you know, getting her to like go beat up women. So who who who? Who's he sending?
clumsy
What do you mean you believe that?
Who's trying you to chat clumsy are you in the chat clumsy was talking about it last night on the show
He said he said yo, it's like shut the fuck up. You believe in clumsy
Oh, yeah, I smacked the shit out of you, but you're leaving clumsy. Oh, you for real
Yo, yo, just like hold on just like hold on psych
You know I got eyes everywhere, right? Just like how Gotti and JT and
Spunky were jumping you in that panel last night, right?
It's two nights ago or two nights ago. Oh, yeah, I got that live
Well, it's a way it's like spunky is live. I mean, I'm sure sure y'all eyes everywhere
But people are saying oh look what's like is I have eyes everywhere too people all the time. Yeah, all right
So but I don't understand you believe in clumsy you let people jump on you with these shake people. What's the same energy Papa?
What's up? What's the same energy?
Well, of course, I'm friends with Alexandra and then to hear even clumsy. So you believe in clumsy
I was well clumsy, and I made up a man in a massacre a Mexican gang members so beaters in the game
Like you believe beaters in again. She's a bit. She's the head of the game. She's again. We're getting we're getting kitty gang
So kitty game so we going down for Rico
Yeah
So you are you stupid?
Yeah, well, yeah, actually you're in the same clown posse, which actually the government actually considers that at the juggalo is a gang
I see and you know what the problem is be the defendant you
No, no, not when when you with you and his cats when the cats going missing with the little box
She defended you when I told her full screen
The crib she said no when I needed it or cook you she's she stopped me from cooking
But you know what you did you backstabbed the fool
How about a back step you right now?
Bro, he's just up there trying to guess. That's right there, that motherfucker is a straight
Potster
Like a motherfucker
Bro Potster, bro. He just what he just came up here. So he has a clip for his show, bro. That's why I did
That's the only reason he came up here just to come up here and say that he talked to you and got a clip for a show
That's all he did
Yeah, whatever it's like, you know, oh
Yeah, he had all through your motives
Bro, he was up here trying to say he was gonna fill it. Oh, let's see. Let's go for it. Sam it
Yeah, what damn what what motives do I have nigga? You just came up here
Jdo one thing about me. I don't need suck psych dick
I want to talk to you. So what's the problem? It's the beef. How the beef started like makes
Hold on Alex told you I thought Alex said stop talking about beta right right around. I'm just asking questions. Bye. Bye
Okay, what happened with Bita is like I have no idea. I was I was on great terms with there
I was having fun going on our show and then it's like
And her cats started going crazy like Elzo came in say oh my god. I saw your I saw your floor
There's you know, your floor is dirty. It was does not be this fall. That's not
Yeah, but I know it's not be this fall
but then I eventually like you know everyone was like attacking me in the room and I texted her a few times that I
sent us some pictures of like the house and stuff and
but and then she like
You know I got all mad at me for something because I was bad. I don't know is it's like so stupid
It's like she's been mad at me since May like it's just been constantly angry at me
But she was like before that you just got upset that you want you don't have no little box and you want people to defend that
I don't know she can't defend that site. I don't need her to defend it
I'm fine with like no little boxes. Did you did did you get a little box?
Yeah, me when the cats go outside there. You still haven't got one
J-doll J-doll hold on can I ask you a hold on site? Hold on. Give me let me
J-doll you fuck yo you fuck with psych that much, right?
What do you mean fuck with him that much?
Can you please donate some money so you could get a letter box?
You don't need one the cats are inside outside cats. I've had cats. They don't go inside they go outside the house
So you got two people with no little box
This shit crazy
Crazy
No little bucks
Anyway, we having fun sipping for beta today. I'm not simple. I'm just asking you questions
Bro, I guess an indoor cat
You don't crazy bro, why why do you sit for betas and they don't fucking
She makes up shit, you know, she lies, you know, she makes up crap
That's not right
But you gonna sit there he's gonna back her up anyway, I'm not a Sam, bro
Gotta watch over some of these women on YouTube and they lie
I'm just asking questions simple is that it's like simple
Is that you talking in the chat? You're typing in the chat. No, that's not you gonna be mosque a check. That's not me
You could tell I don't write that smart come on
But you know what I never did anything to beat us like I never did anything like what did I do to her?
She's mad cuz I wrote it a I saw okay, or like what is the ace?
I'm just, oopy, what up?
I'm just asking questions.
Like, I don't know why you're getting mad at me.
I'm not getting mad.
I'm just, I'm asking questions too.
I'm like, why is she mad?
Well, you can't.
I'm just mad at her.
She's still mad that Arthur said something about her uncle
like, you know, six months ago.
I mean, that's what she keeps bringing up.
No, you can't.
No, and she told you to stop.
She told you to stop talking shit and you kept going.
No, I did. I did that what she saw was a clip of the night before that. No, and you you start to
Papa papa papa when I came on this panel you was talking about
UNJ though would just talk about being a yes or no
Well, I'm done. We're talking about be that well now we can because she she took the gloves off by calling me like the bottom feeder and saying like
She's called him a grifter she called him a scammer, bro
And Sam and you know how that feels to be called a scammer that shit hurts to the court
You know that shit's wrong. Hey, right man definition of character
Let me talk to you. You see what the wrong is cooking. Hold on. How many times I had to tell you don't be greedy psych. Listen
Okay, um, no, it's a prank. I'm sorry you can get me good. What's your name? Thank you
That's how you J though, but you got to be careful what you believe on here. There's lots of defamations
Talking about J though. That's my J though. How's it me? I've been right here the whole time
I've been here for the last time. You know some of these people they believe definition of character man many things said
People say many why it's sometimes on the internet you can't just believe anything people see
What so much lying and slandering on the
Somebody somebody did a prank. It's talking to someone right now
No, I don't order it me no order. It's like that's not Spanish
What's your name Sam man? You can't believe anything that you hear man
There's lots of defamation of character going on. Yeah, you don't know me, bro
Well, I'm telling you I'm telling you there's
Definition of character and you can't just believe anything you hear man. I don't believe nobody. I know site man
Yeah, you can't believe anyone. I like I said, I know site shut the fuck up bro. Yeah, I didn't order
I ain't your bro, man. I'm just telling you that you can't believe what happened here
There's definition of character going on. I'm hearing it. I can't believe what you hear man. I know site. Are you are you listening?
I know I don't say to you idiot. I've seen him for a few months. All right few months
I've been seeing say for a year now
Few months
I'm a good guy. So I'm a good guy man. Shut up. Are you keep talking?
You won't as bad as they make him out to be oh my god
You only knew him for a few months. He's still talking pop. Oh, you don't know the Lord
Oh, yeah, I've seen this beat a man. He's some of these people man
You want to know his dick in his mouth when his dick in your mouth
Don't think so bell
But I think that beat it man
Who's beat it man, tell me who's beat it
How can you trust this person?
I'm just I think who the heck is beat it man
Well, what makes you trust her more than you can trust someone else look at mr. White knight himself
Suck a nigga. I've seen this beat it man. I'm not too impressed. I'll tell you that okay
I don't care though man. I don't know these people that much like you care seem like you can I'll tell you who beat us
She's a 50 year old person spoiled brat drunk
See that's what that's what I believe you did Jay dog. She gets drunk. She's on pills. She's crazy crazy cat lady
That's what she is
She doesn't seem too smart. She didn't seem too credible
And that's what be it was talking about you guys J. Don't talk always share you who this nigga
Just know your few months and you know be the support of you from up and down
Because when you need a hold on like like what you need to help and you need to help you need to tell these people
Yeah, but be be to also backstab like you she also told him some shit
Be taken back
You cool with Jimmy, what about Jimmy? What about Jimmy mute?
What about Jimmy?
There are no issues with Jimmy you got Jimmy not me Jimmy's my homie. Yeah, I know
Okay
Just saying that you sound stupid
Lungs is the homie to
So, what's up? Losers, nigga, imagine. I'm shaking something. What are you
thinking? Why are you sad? What are you shaking? There's alliances being formed here. Don't you see the
paddles? Alliances, you see? Yeah, alliances. Alliances. Don't you understand? Groovy, groovy
You ready
The war's been green it's ready to overflow, you know
There's nothing cooking there we're gonna spill everything all the all the
Clumsies already crying you don't see clumsy already crying was he crying? Yeah, clumsy already crying crying what?
Yeah, okay
These people
This is my favorite yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, okay
No, no, no
Jimmy come from
We don't play by your rules. We don't play by your rules. Are you finding out the hard way?
We don't play by your rules. Tell about black dragon
What about black dragon? I haven't talked about for one over a year. What are you talking about? You was cool. No, over. Yeah, no impossible
When did I talk to him last on your show?
Last august six months
At the we found out that this
Six months
That was your best friend
That was more than six months ago, bro. That was like a year ago. Yeah, you gotta do the math
Write it down. Write it down. That's so cool. Right. Yeah
Well, you got your lackeys fighting your battles. You can't even answer questions like look you just sit in there
You you think you you think you're on me. You talk to you talk to like you think you're joining cage
Hey saman, how much better been you man? How much is she paying you for that?
Shout out to yeah, man. You got a bunch of dick suckers man. I'm just better being you to come here man. I do her work a little box
Little box. Yes. Well, you know, I got a little box. No, no, I'm not a psych
Or J dogs, I got a little box. Look at that. So it's like get one
You want to talk to psyche while work work quiet so you talk to psyche so I get one
I mean, I need to lay out that lean bro lean a little too strong for it. What time is it over there right there?
I do this 430 in the afternoon over there, bro
I'm out of here. It's a loose one too much lean
too much what you dig suckers for psych me no dick sucker
Someone a dick sucker
Someone wants to know in the site. Yeah, do you need liposuction surgery alliance by the way, yeah
Yeah, stay tuned stay tuned. What about that better person if you need liposuction surgery?
Yeah, stay tuned
They do
Remember, we don't play by your rules that man. We don't play by your
That's that's the whole thing about it, there is no you're trying to mean out you
That's how the restrict is down from
So you made a lot of hope yes or no you made their lines, right?
There's alliances. So when shit happens to me, I could blame the whole
If something happens to you
I guess that aligns with the sport
So who's the Mexican in charge now?
I don't know message
You fucking crazy
He's crazy Samman, you crazy
Hey German lady
German lady, I've been looking for you
I want you to cook
Come on
I got a lepo session for you
German lady
Is it too early to cook right now?
It's 441 over there
You're killing my high 40% off your next life search determined lady. What do you think of that?
J-dog is a dick sucker psych likes to put his dick in J-dog's mouth. No, J-dog's a good guy
It seems like you got all dick suckers psych. You just can't take heat you bitch in because you ruin your own channel
Sam and don't you got some story got a loot man get out of here man. Go do your stuff
The site ruin his own channel
like people try to give you a bite
I don't need a fly monkey
I need a mosquito, okay?
Whoa, whoa, you trying to say I'm a monkey?
Fly monkey, which is a nice one
Go bring the queen bee herself
Bring the queen bee herself
Bring the queen bee over here
I let the door hit you
Well, you go on the Instagram salmon go on the store man. That's what you guys are good for me
Go to the store man. Go rob some people
You guys are good for that
What the racist remarks wow
Maybe I still deport you man if we're looking
Maybe I still deport you man get you out of here get you out of the USA
The forum wow
I I feel uncomfortable because I'm getting
Man, go back to bed. It's dream. Yeah, we don't need you. We're back to bed. We don't need you here. Thank you
We've seen enough of you man. Wow
Homosexuals panel Wow, that's crazy. I really don't care about the word, but it's like I don't care about psych secures sexual orientation
Man, that's not my business. I don't care about that. You calling me a you calling me a faggot though
Man, you're a faggot. I don't care about it. It's like it's a good faggot
Wow, that's that's that why I don't mind psych man, but you man. I'm not too fun to you man
Say it again. Say it again then say it again for you. Don't care. I don't care about you much man
So it's a good guy. So say it
Hello
He's like
Didn't you say you're leaving man? What are you still doing here, man? What are you waiting for and out saying the word he's
He called me that site
We're waiting for a handout man. You're not getting a discount for liposuction surgery
He said that site not me. He disrespected
About a few cans short of a six pack
Dude Sam I'm around. He's I try to be cool with this guy, but this guy he follows the you know what salmon does
He follows the fucking whatever
Wagon is on you just on the bandwagon
He's gonna go on the bandwagon say yeah, but yeah, even though he don't even know
He's gonna go and do it. It seems like
He followed the
Not cool with a child doctor. I'm sorry. Who do I what child get our dogs?
Boss and Bridget how old is the child? How old is that child? He a grown fucking man. So go don't get
Don't get it twisted I didn't dodge no child or her kid
Right her child her son. That's already been a that's already been how long ago was that December?
What month are we dude? We're almost in December again. That's what you know
Yeah, I was yes, it was
It was on KK's time
I just want nobody I just want anybody who like what who do I spot?
I just want nobody don't don't don't get me and get whatever Jimmy did and I do is two different things
Me Jimmy is two different animals. Don't get the shit that Jimmy doesn't I mean you try me with this
And you said there you party alliance like you part of this alliance and I said are you
Don't me. Are you ready for war?
I'm actually hold on. Let me ask site site you party there's alliance
I'm on my own, you know, it's like if everyone's like, you know
Show there's a poor for me. It's fine, but it's like, I'm you know, I'm
I'm on my own man
You're against the world, right?
Cool, baby go to bed Nicole
I salute somebody here. Okay. Bye. I say man. Wow. That's why I get greeted
I
Think everybody on the show
J-Dog is laughing he's just using you just like JT and Gotti once again nobody using anybody
What's the one? What am I gaining? Tell me what am I gaining moniker?
What we use it for what I don't know you just weird
Well, yeah, because you can't figure me out. That's why everybody call me weird because they can't figure out what my motives are
You don't know what my motives are. I don't have any motives
Said someone Sam and Karin Zaya drove by a kid school in Doc's a school website
You won't cross his big home
That's it got nothing to do with me. I don't know you don't say me. No
That's all you know, that's all you need to know. There it is. Hey, just the problem is J. Don't can't say that about everybody else
He can't come down to support that
He doesn't know because I've done shit like that. I've done shit like that. I don't fuck up shit in my life
He's like there's a difference. No, but see I admit to my wrongs. I'm not doing that anymore
Who I don't I don't I could say I could
Who who who I'm doing nothing you everything is from my past you guys are all bringing shit up from fucking almost a year
You know and I know who beta needs a aid is I know who's on our up
Shout out to you
Yeah, I don't know who like hit a bunch of people but there's like a lot of people like look
I think low key was hidden like I'm scum was hidden
That was jade dog. That was jade dog. That's your name. Yeah. How can you see it? You can see who gonna
Those you know wasn't
It's like you can see who did it.
Bitchass.
Okay, stay on the fucking web brain.
No, but you get sad, what?
Cause you can't figure me out, what?
Can't say what cuz I'm not over there sucking up to you and saying, ah, Sam and this
No, I don't say nobody there. I'm just cool
Shit
Calling you names J-Dog. She's let you cook it up RG. I'll let you cook it up
Oh, here's psyche. I've come up, you know, you're trying to get your channel off the ground and I've tried the
to help you uh figure out like who is a complete scumbag who is in kz was one of those people
there's a few of them and j dog is one of those people uh he has a history in the past on here
and here's the thing i'm done trying to give you advice it's your channel let you run it the way
you want to but this little douchebag uh below me he will show his true colors he always does
Every time you you show your true self
Encyclopedia to and so will Alex. It's just a matter of time. Well, it's just a matter of time
You have no problem doxing a kid. No problem at all
Doxing a kid. What's your problem? What you see people like Jimmy, right?
Who's the worst of the worst and you you sit there and you
You gave me that even in Barrisom, that's all you got, I was friends with Jimmy at one time, until I saw his true color, you sit there, you open your mouth, and you say, please come down my throat Jimmy, please come down my throat, that's how people see you J-Dog, you get sucked getting aroused by this, talking about J-Dog swallowing loads and psychs just rocking back and forth, well J-Dog you're not even in Barris about how much you suck Bangkok.
According to you, I was friends with Jimmy until he started talking about lolliporn and
reaping women and all the awful things that he said over the past year and a half.
I was a good friend to Jimmy.
I pretty much had the only moderate range, I ran that show for a little while until he
started showing.
Yeah, you had the God Ranch.
I remember that.
Yeah, I was the only one with that.
And the good
Pick me out of it personally yourself a couple of times
Where have I got kicked out of everywhere you got you need this board. Can you get kicked off a discord for harassing women?
No, I'm not making too many calls. I was making too many calls to people
Too many calls he says who are you calling?
harassing and stalking
I said calling I never said who I was calling said calling making calls to people who didn't want to receive the calls
Cycle see it all by themselves Alex. So everyone else J dog. You're a scumbag you've always been
And I've already repented for all the things I've already done
So my cheeks is in chat
Saying he harassed me over 15 calls back-to-back
Are you denied? It's just a few days ago. I
Called it 15 times
Yeah, back-to-back
Why would she lie? Why would she lie?
No, I probably did. I probably get called by Bobby. I was on the guest call when I was talking to him.
How do you know who you're asking?
That was just talking to him.
That was calling a number.
It wasn't a number.
You feel that defensive? You got to just talk over it.
Okay, okay. You were on Jimmy's a few days ago.
What was the first sentence that came out of your mouth, Jay Dog?
The first sentence. Who did it have to do with?
Who didn't have to do it a very first sentence beat up the very first thing that came out of your mouth
Why J-Doc you're obsessed with her and you're stalking harass women. That's why all my stalking harassing women
You're a fucking retard. Well, I can't believe this shit
Psych of course not paying attention. Well, you sleep. Okay. Well, we'll see we shall see I haven't done anything
J J dog. This is your YouTube legacy yours. You're known as a liar
You told everyone that you were in protective custody and you had you got Rico charges
What else do you shove cell phones up in your ass? No, I never shoved
You allowed people to pay you so you could they could rape each other. There's so much shit. It's unbelievable
Yeah, okay
What's I'm not lying
Stocking harass females are you done and you and you fetishize the low cows not in the fantasize
You were in Cyraxes DMs
I never was a cyrat. You had totally black dragon jerk off for you in a private vc
Why?
Well, no, Marty covered an entire stream with Tony about you jerking off for you.
Can you produce that stream? Can you produce that stream?
Most of Marty passed away unfortunately, but a lot of the streams went in with him.
He knows that this court is alive and well. I know there's a lot of people that watch that stream. How are you going to deny it?
Jesus Christ
Proof that's the worst part
It was very graphic in the story he told
Okay, well, I would like to see this because I haven't seen
I have not seen this said live stream well a thousand other people have it and you know what happens
I don't know why you're denying it, but that's a lie. It's a lie
Why can't you go to different panels and be like oh Tony's black dragon is my friend you want me to bring him over
He's my friend. That's what you do
Yeah, I did bring with Sam and yeah, I did bring with Sam you did
He was a pedophile
And who else brought him over there, too?
And you forgot to mention the fact that he ejaculated and a bunch of peanut butter.
And you said it to this young buddy without telling him.
Don't say it was just-
No, you did the same thing with Jimmy.
No, I could bring Jimmy over to Sam there.
Yes, I did.
And to be no, you know, oh, oh Sam and I'm my buddy my locale buddy, Jimmy
Never get say that you've finished eyes locale you did it was
You're in sirens
You stalking the rest women and you finish
You're foolish
No, now you're calling my friend a locale that's fucked up
Fuck off dude, you're so transparent. Yeah
What are you 20 years younger than your wife?
It's something like that. You like them all, huh? Whatever. You like them old old Mary. Oh
Right
And we got coffee Maserad, okay, well come on up and show this picture you're talking about a
Chunky white dude. I've never been fat in my life. You dumb fuck
I mean, he's got a rich to
I do call women sweetie because I think it's funny. I called Alex sweet. It's just the other day
Why did you say that or do you like what do you think that's funny?
Why why why do you think you're trying by saying that like that just makes me
When I was going for a J dog
What but why are you actually gonna have a conversation? Is that what you're trying to do? Go ahead good cook away J dog floor is yours, sir
Why would you say that to Alex? Why?
I just answered your question because you thought it was funny.
And you think that ain't going to piss her off.
You think that ain't going to piss her off and make her just completely
just not anything you just say, no credibility behind it.
You didn't care about any of that.
You just want thought about just saying.
Oh, Ron, I don't think it is.
He's still mad that I call him a fairy with his little pink and leopard shoes.
because god damn they were they were just 150 but them shoes cost and they're rare they're
rare you can sell them try to sell it to you for $200 would you buy it i'm buying no fucking hacks
a shit if i shit in it i don't care what the price my point is who gives a fuck when it costs
it was pink and leopard you're a fucking fruit
You know whatever that doesn't matter that doesn't matter
I'm not cooking nothing. I have nothing to cook. No, could you got nothing you bring nothing know why I'm not up here
I'm not up here to fight with nobody. I'm up her chilling with psych
You I'm gonna read time in time. You know, he watch he's a good friend of psych. He's a great mod
He says Alex was accusing RG of all sorts of things RG was being very patient patient until then and I would agree with you
I would absolutely you were trying you were trying to bullshit her and she saw
That's all it was
It's so hard. It's hilarious
Yes
I yeah, exactly. You got me
Margie
Did a whole stream about Tony jerking off in a vc for jade
Never happened to me ever because it didn't happen at all
They keep keep reaching. I'm enjoying your comments. I want to see where I want to see where it's at. Show me the stream
There's a huge audience, okay? Well, I would agree with them Alex is insane
It is hilariously insane by the way the look in her eyes
Respect Alex like that
When you suck a dick you sure love to suck it. Oh, yeah, you're horrible. You're such a horrible
Alex's insane honestly
I don't have no beef with Alex
I think I said wonderful person. I have no beef. Did you believe that she's insane is what I asked?
No, I do not believe she's insane already was a buddy of mine. So I don't really give a fuck what these people say
You're trying to be the next music big Marty and it's fucking horrible
You have to come up in order to be
Come on
Yeah, okay
Marty did not like J dog specifically because he allowed Tony to jack off for him. I've actually had
I don't see where this
How long would you say that happened that screen if you had to guess educated guess
fucking this person in jazz, no idea what the fuck they're talking about, that's fine
how long ago was that stream?
if you say that stream happened
I know exactly what it was, it was right around the time of the movie
what are you fucking talking about that stream you dumbass
you're fucking lying, you're just making shit up out your ass trying to make me look bad
dude
Everyone, there was a thousand people that saw this stream.
Where is this stream? Where is it?
One of them thousand people got it.
It's all over the fucking place.
Well, someone's got to bring it up.
So I can see it because I've never seen it myself.
So bring this stream up.
You fucking lying cocksucker.
All right, dude, it's out there.
Well, bring it. I want to see it.
I want to see it myself. And Psyche can see it, too. Everybody can see it.
Cuz we have yet to see this
See how that works, I play you you don't play
Stream covering of the fact where it's out there, you know, we're sure we've seen it where
Not there you lie
You're trying to play a competitive game with me.
Dude, this is like well known.
This part of the J-Dog lore, and you know it, dude.
You can say it lying all you want.
Well, well, well.
But how come nobody can show proof of this?
How come nobody can bring this fucking thing?
The fact that you're calling your raxation, Ron,
tells me you have no idea what the fuck you're talking about.
So go fuck yourself.
All right, get over it, man.
You've been talking about this for 15 minutes now.
Dude, this is what he does.
He's talking about everybody's panel, and this is what he does.
This is his shit.
Who are you?
What are you listening to talk man for 15 minutes you get it you done done talking about that already or what man talking about which part
I find it intriguing if you had a disabled man in the wheelchair jacking off for your sexual pleasure
I think that's pretty fascinating. It says a lot about someone's character
Yeah, Tony's in a wheelchair. That's correct. No, he's thinking about two different Tony's he's thinking Tony the conductor
No, no, not that Tony. This is a different
This one is way more disabled than the Tony you're thinking about like like this guy is you look at him
You know, like he can't poop on his own like
There's a lot of lots of lore with Tony's black dragon
But part of that lore is him jerking off in a discord with J-Dog
No, no
I want to see this live stream because they say that it happened to just go to your research
Why what you really pretend it didn't happen. We've got to bring it where the hell's art at where's that little
The J dog did not eat the peanut butter and jelly sandwich that was uh, oh shit the fuck was his
Randy Randy was Tony's fucking that was his roommate
Yeah, he was very very disabled God knows what you would have done to him. You pervert degenerate fuck
God thank God Randy was too disabled to use discord because J dog would have had him do it all types of
Exaggerating a bit
I don't want it's all right
Man
Making crap up he's making
A disabled man to jack off for you in a private call for your own sexual pleasure. I would call that not a good guy
I don't know the guy
This is part of Jay Dogg's lore like this is well-known
Music Bees Bismarie was a pretty big streamer in these low-cow sectors did a whole entire stream about it
Yeah, it looks like it's gotty. I wonder if Goddy saw that video. I bet he did what's up Goddy bud. Yo, what's good?
What's happening? Hey, Jay dog. Did you tell your wife you're leaving her for a psyche yet?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
We all know you're your wife. What are you gonna tell your wife?
When are you gonna tell your wife got it my wife left me my wife are you
Now you're just one psyche like this. No, you just want to be
Yeah, you need liposuction too, bro
Like post section. No, God, I'm asking you when are you getting your session for life?
interest gross on
The other one who's five foot forward fucking 200 pounds. I don't need that
250 I'm 250 6 to I'm fine pal. Don't worry about me. Yeah, 6 to Goddy. Come on. You're about 5 8
Oh, I'm not 6 to fuck out of you. There's no way you're 6 to your 5
You wish you was next to Roddy. If you want the 40% liposuction surgery
You're gonna clean my toilet too. Oh good. Come on down
Who's gonna clean your toilet? I just took a big shit. It's all ready for you. Oh
That's disgusting. Got it. It's life pal
We're one disgusting man. Yeah, I've seen your place. I wouldn't talk
By please clean man look at it
Very clean man, go show the toilet right now that show the fuck
Look at the litter box I keep it clean I see a little box. Is that what you use as a toilet is that yours?
No, that's my cat's the idiot. Yeah, both shit. Show the toilet. That's my cat's litter box
Sebastian we all know you're full of shit, all right
Gaudi, we know that you're full of crap. No, no, we know we know that you're sucking up the JT and Raymond that
Everybody how you cheated that woman out of ten grand. I don't think so man
She helped me out of that when I was going through hard times. He's lying about that. Did you pay her back? Did you pay her back then?
As you was paid back man, don't worry about it. It's not your business. You don't need to worry about it
Pay her back. You're full of shit. You didn't pay her back. Don't worry about it. It's none of your business
Don't worry about it. Don't worry about it. Don't worry about it. Don't worry about it
He cheated a woman out of ten you want to you want to get the life post such a surgery discount, man
You're not gonna get it like that. You you're the paragon. You're not gonna get it like that gotty, man
You need to you're a great Christian Sebastian. You know that
The next one Christian man, man, you're lying about me. That's definitely meaning women. Listen guy. That's definition
For a second man, let me tell you that's
You're listening to people that are saying lies and you're believing them you're very bad
I even talked you on the phone guy. What's wrong with you?
I talked you in person on the phone once with Justin
I explained to you man. She held me out when I went through hard times. Why are you saying lies man?
That's definition. You didn't pay her back. Why didn't you pay her back?
Hey, what the heck man?
Don't worry about it. That's none of your business
She was able to help me out man
Listen to me God if she helped me out. She was able to afford to help me out. It's none of your business
Don't worry about worry about your little pathetic life
Worry about your pathetic life
JC give me a donation man. Don't worry about that. That's none of your business
Don't worry about it
Jay, Gotti, why are you doing like JT, man? Why are you acting like an idiot like that?
Gotti, don't worry about it, Gotti, don't worry about it. I took the money, it's okay.
Hey, Gotti, why are you acting like a punk like JT, right?
What are you trying to do like that?
I cheated this woman out of money and promised to love her, but I'm really gay, so I didn't tell her that part.
I don't think so man. I don't think so man. Listen to me man. You don't know anything about my life in my situation
You just want to say crap like these other
Why'd you laugh about it?
It's definitely a character, Goddy, and you know it man. You don't know what's going on. You don't know anything about it
What happened on the phone to me when you said it all, huh? Why'd you laugh about it?
What about you? You lied about it. Hey listen to me man. You lied about being in a wheelchair
I cheated that bitch out of me
Are these guys not going to shut up? You're just going to talk over people
Listen to me Goddy. What about you? You lied about being in a wheelchair
You're pissing me off with your lies right now. You're pissing me off
in a wheelchair you told me you were in a wheelchair man you had my sympathy man I gave you my sympathy
you told me you're in a wheelchair what about that man you lied about being in a wheelchair
for two years now stop fucking lying Sebastian you don't you lied about being in a wheelchair for
years man for two years you told everyone you're in a wheelchair no what about that we call that
Oh
What's your name, man? What's your name Lee Roy? What's your name punk prove it prove? I'm not you're a weasel
Are you kidding me? You're a weasel man? That sucks up the GT. You're another faggot. You're a weasel man
Maybe you told people you're in a wheelchair for two years, man
You told everyone you're in a wheelchair for two years man, and you had everyone sympathy you lie about everything man
You're lying right now about my life. What the heck are you man?
You're a fucking cheater you cheat. No, no, God, you go on other panels man sucking up the
Faggots like GT and rain and you come on
You got no credibility. Come on
Listen to you yell like a girl man. Are you gonna cry some more?
Got you man. You talk over people. That's the only thing you can do man
Listen to this guy this guy's an idiot this guy's a total
Hypocrite this guy lied about being in a wheelchair for two years, and he's
About being in a wheelchair for two years man and wants to judge other people
I don't know you tell me man. You've been
Seven years you told people you're in a wheelchair and you lie about it
And then you say you drive a car and you're out there working
Listen to me God here, whatever your name is you are the biggest liars. I've ever seen in my life on these YouTube
It's pathetic, man.
You tell people you have people crying
because you're in a wheelchair
and then you find out you're not in a wheelchair.
I didn't get any money off that, pal.
How much did you get?
We find out you're not even in a wheelchair, man. I actually believed you when you said that, you know
I'm not worried about it. I believed you Gotti. Why'd you lie to me man? You told me in a wheelchair told me your suicidal
I try to give you some of my friendship. I try to give you some help and support and then you'll find out it's a lie
You're laughing about it when you say you're in a wheelchair
The heck man, you got no credibility Gotti. You have soccer man. You got no respect. No, no credibility man
This guy's not about a clown. Listen to him. You're a shitty Christian
You're a clown man. You're a total clown
Hey, go suck up the JT and rain some more
Go suck up to them some more Agadia
What are you doing here, man? Why don't you go suck up the JT some more? He needs you to work for man
You only came here because of me
Doesn't
A minute I actually cared about you before I thought you were in a wheelchair, but not anymore man
On the phone God, I thought you were serious guy. You're not serious man. You're not serious guy whatsoever
I'll tell you something else. You're not getting the 40% off like
I don't know you're not getting the biscuit on garden
So do expect me to remember a name of a stream is pretty outrageous, but it is part of j-dollars lore
You know what I absolutely never have
Lots of rocks universe coffee you're on you're fucking people talking
You're done with me by the way. I'm done with you. You're out of a circle of trust. I'm done with you. You're out of the circle of trust. You're not getting into heaven. You're done, man. You're not getting the discount. You're not getting anything. You're not getting into heaven. You're not getting the Christmas dinner. You're not getting anything.
Don't put your toilet down.
God, you go pretend to be in a wheelchair to some other people. Get their sympathy man. You're done with me, I tell you.
Don't beg for money from some homeless fucking girl.
Go tell people you're in a wheelchair, man.
Go pretend to be in a wheelchair again.
How fat are you? 250 pounds?
Oh, Christy, Christy, I need money, Christy.
250 pounds? You're not getting life or second surgery, man.
You're gonna need to take some supplements
and do some work and out, man.
I've got the money to eat, Christy, I have,
I'm starving, Christy, I haven't eaten in five days.
Maybe you're starving, man.
Christy, I have no money, Christy, I have no money.
How much you get for your SI, man?
How much you, you're not starving, that's for sure, man.
You're fat.
You're fat, that's the fastest thing you've ever seen, God.
Please, Christy, Christy, Christy, Christy,
send me money.
Bunch of lies man
Bunch of lies. You cried on the phone remember that never cried on nothing. What are you talking about?
You're the one crying dude. You're crying. You told me you were suicide
I remember told you God you told me you were suicidal the other time and I had sympathy for you
Told me you're in a wheelchair and you couldn't take it anymore. Remember you like about that
Yeah, you told me you're a wheelchair. You said you were crying and you said you couldn't take anymore
I tried to help you out man. I gave you something like some friendship
I talked to you and then that's what you do. I found out it's a lie
your friendship made me I found out it was a lie. I was so disappointed. I really thought you were in a wheelchair
man. I thought you were really worse with slander.
I thought you were stupid enough to fall for his trove.
Yo, your friendship made me fall for his slander.
I know man, he's an idiot, but I thought it was a lie.
I thought it was a lie.
Jaydon hates Asians, and that's not cool.
He lies about everything.
You hate the Asians, Jaydon? That's even worse.
I can't have any Asian slander.
That's worse than being gay on here.
What kind of Asians East Asians West Asians
No, no, no, no, no, the only one motherfucker that I hate that is Asian next art Vandal is that's the only one that I hate
Art Vietnamese girl from Asian people. They're good people Vietnamese people Japanese
Yeah, Art Vandal that's the only Asian guy that I hate
Everybody why do you dislike him J dawg cuz he he knows the truth about you and shares it just like I still get in these people
No, I hate art manually because of his stupid name, and he knows the reason I hate him because he
Harass females
You're one of the worst of the worst your lives are g
Reaction, which is the gayest shit I ever heard and I left before I got that gay there fella
You say the same sir probably not fucking weirdo
Only weirdo here is you are gay
Well, maybe I think I don't think anyone in these communities are normal, but I don't like have fucking disabled degenerates jerk off for me in VC
Like that's a whole different step. You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, you do
That is something you did.
And J-Daw, you talked about doing shit,
but why was somebody complaining about it?
Yes, a response for J-Daw.
You have to say it.
You have to say I got to complain about you, J-Daw.
Oh, Excel, do tell.
Do tell, sir.
Oh, there's another female he was fucking harassing.
Oh, shit.
And people, he's trying to say I make this shit up.
I don't know who this motherfucker is.
Do tell the story yourself.
Go back to the toilet, man, the toilet.
better yet how about I just go get the fuck psyche don't let us really play shit over
actually put Sebastian on the big screen I want to see his toilet
if I go get this stream can you play a psyche
yeah that's his toilet everybody there's his toilet
that's a clean litter box
yeah change it
it's a clean litter box
you take a dump in there Sebastian you sick fuck
you're jealous of my cat man he's got a clean litter box
I'm jealous of my cat
your clean box there
Yeah, I can't believe you're calling our
Ethnic slurs Jada your piece of shit apparently you're stalking more women
One just
I'm just gonna go grab that live stream and play it for you. So you can't get it
You you're just saying this one no proof I want to see the proof you guys are just
For if I bring that shit over here will he
Put your white one.
I've never proved that J-Dog's a scumbag.
I love it.
Put your white part.
You'll prove the whole thing wrong.
H1 doesn't have anything in this game, right?
Why would he make that up, J-Dog?
Why?
Because now there's a hot wife.
You ever see Zyle's wife?
She's fucking hot.
Have that I've seen J dogs wife. She's a fucking pig
Hey dogs. Yeah, you did not talk to my wife. You did not talk to my wife.
So, are you lying? You talked to a female. You talked to a female, but it wasn't my wife.
You didn't talk to nobody on camera. I have all of Mary Salana's information, including her age.
Oh, you can just stand up, Docs, right here on the panel.
I guess that's...
You can just stand up, Docs, right here.
I'm going to leave him a blank.
Yeah, I'm leaving. He's Docs'ing.
Oh, please leave. Oh, he lit a pussy. He he what he left had nothing to do with what I said
He left because the exile one has come out with proof that he stalks and harasses. That's why he left
Yeah, I know you took him off the panel man, I think that's what happened
Chibi chibi. He does have a wife. I know that's surprising because he's uh, oh, he's on panel
You know sucking off fucking low cows or you know harassing and stalking women
That's why it's very surprising that he is a wife
But that's why he only streams from that one little room or in the tent outside because his wife wants nothing to do with it
I'll give you an example man. There's so much slander and lies. I look at that guy earlier
He was lying about me man. I got guys about everything
It's hard to believe it's hard to know you can believe in these streams
Yeah, I agree. I agree and I don't got he's ever lied to me. He seems like all right, dude
But he's right there. Trust me man. He's lying about me man
This one person help people watch the stream right of J dog of Tony talking telling everyone about how J dog
Made him jerk off in BC and he's gonna deny it like it never happened. That's un-fucking real to me
I think it really shows his delusions
Goddy guy, man. He was lying this one person held me out three years ago, man
I was going through hard times gave me a donation because he lies about it
Because he listens to lies he hears stuff and then he lies about it
He goes from he's sucking up the jt and rain these people
Anyways, it's a bunch of lies and defamation I care around these streams. You half of this stuff. It's lies
You got to be careful what you believe, you know
No, I had some asshole tell me that fuck
Call it rax nation and tell me that I'm new which is pretty funny because just it is
I bet you love CVG. No, you know you fag
I was 40 funny funny funny, so what's your little cat's name?
I don't know him personally. He seems like a nice guy. So I'm for the first time
Who J dog now he's a complete scumbag piece of shit, dude. Yeah, we're psyche. We're psyche. I
Took everyone off the panel. Yeah, I know you love me up for some strange fucker reason
But it's I think it's hilarious that a J dog ran as
Excel woman's getting proof of him
Stalking harassing yet another female
An exiled one has no game in this. Why would he lie? There he is
I spoke too soon, but I'm gonna get in contact with my brother Bronzeberg because it happened on his panel and
To get that live stream as soon as I get a hold of
No reason to lie either. He has no reason to lie. I like bronze. I've liked him since we first talked on this
He doesn't like J. Dogg either for the same exact right. It's like I'm gonna go. Thanks, Ramya
Yeah, thank you. I guess he put that on private until he fucking edits it and shit
So I'm gonna get a copy of it from a grumble for me
Well, you made J-Dog run sir. So congratulations on that
He knew that you had evidence about his activities his scub bag activities. He fucking ran
I don't even know the dude and I got motherfuckers coming to me complaining about this dude
I'm not surprised. I'm really not
Like he went on to groovy Jimmy's the other day the first sentence out of his mouth wasn't hell yeah
I grew a Jimmy which is what he normally says because he sucks locale dick
But it was talking shit about beta and how beta did this and how beta did that he's obsessed and honestly like
He's the one that started this riff between you and her
It I think a lot of people feel that to be honest with you
I think it was be that they hit the panel and was talking about J-Doc harassers a matter of fact RG
Well, it was it actually goes before that. But yeah, J-Doc's trying to play a little game
Just don't fall for it. And if you want to you see him as a friend that that's cool
But he will show his true colors eventually
that's all we got. No, I don't, I don't have people that like try to buddy troll locales that have uh
how can I say it weirdo tendencies. Well, he sexualizes him dude. He did it to Syrace. He did it to
fucking uh black Tony the black dragon and he did it to Jimmy. He's doing the Jimmy now
and psych your mic is really low by the way. Okay, thank you. Yep. J-Dog's wife know he's gay.
Don't know but the guy is definitely he has a homo tendencies
I don't know what the fuck
Well, you know, I was coming back up to I don't know now now that you you couldn't get the video because it was privated now
He's gonna come up and defend it
Ross Byrd will be off work here soon. And I don't turn back to the same places. So we'll revisit
So that's why my accounts banned site cuz J. Dogg has a wrench
Any mods with his feelings he doesn't give a fuck about your channel, sir. He just does it
I'll make sure that you're not hit
I appreciate that
I do he's good. He's interesting. He's not gay. I'm not sure I believe that honestly. I don't think his wife believes that
I've talked
My gay daughter has never been wrong and I don't think it's gonna start being wrong today
I knew psyche was gay before psyche even said anything
Well, I mean he doesn't scream like I'm a gay man like you don't have the gay
Infliction in your voice. So the gay accent like the I don't know. I can't even do it
But so yeah, I wouldn't know unless he told you I guess I don't know
To me he's that closeted homo. I've been around enough for them being locked up that I know a closeted homo when I see
How long were you closeted a force like how long did you did it take you to come out?
I thought we still taught my J dog my bad site
No, he's a closet homo for sure. It's like season two. Don't you?
I
Know you have no comment
Sorry, he's your buddy. You don't want to out him as being gay, but I know you see it, sir
I know you see it
You ain't got to us he's gay, but how many times has he tried to fap it with you backstage psyche plenty of times
I've invited him and he keeps telling him to go into rub maps with me on a rub map so he keeps saying no
I've got a friend, he's in the middle of a fight.
You jerks it off to your voice, I guarantee it, I fucking guarantee it.
This guy's writing the same stupid shit over and over again.
No one hangs out with Boy Blue, the guys are fucking weirdo.
Jesus Christ
Jesus Christ throwing out fucking names like you know shit fuck out of here dude
I mean at the end of the day, you know, I am friends with one of Marty's locales tonic. So there is that
You're part of the whole drama community shit
Fags that's for you guys sent burdo over here. So that's not cool. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, we set that up with Marty though Marty was for that
I actually I talked to I know you I talked to the bird over the day before Marty had a one battle
He used in the tortures audience
He told me that chatting was like exile one. This is what you guys deal with on a regular. I'm sorry, man
I told him I love it
I'm a big old bird old fan
All right, are you a
Chat saying that you have a juggler roots. Is that true? No, no, no
I think the juggalo shit is weird and I've told my juggalo
Associates whatever you want to call them or people that I hit the panel that I think that juggalo shit's where personally I
In real life don't get along with Joe and Joey. So fuck them fuck their music fuck their record label
It's a weirdos name the Ruby red guy Ruby Ridge guy
You know, it's actually normal if you'd like go to like the black sector like the good pussy show or whatever
Like I went over there. He was in there and like everyone there is like talking like him
They all sound like him. They're all they're all just like loud and like they won't stop
If you get birdo one-on-one and birdo's cool with you
But you get birdo around somebody you don't like and it's an on switch and that motherfucker does not shut off
He went
Oh, yeah fat ass. Oh, yeah, he's definitely aware. Oh, I want to drop since J. Dogg is too scared to come back up here
Yeah, I'm glad to know that J. Dogg was stalking harassing yet another woman that has nothing to do with this section
It just really shows his character. So it's like I hope you're taking notes
Alex if you're watching, I hope you're taking new notes to their sweet tits. All right. See you later
I will be clipping clipping that when Bronzeberg sends it to me and we will have clips of it. So you can't lie and deflect from the bullshit man.
You got to own up to your bullshit out here. That's how you get past the bullshit.
Yeah.
If someone would like a reading I have a new deck that I will open and then
You'll be the first one to get a reading and then what kind of deck is it?
It's called. It's really cool. It's called. It's called the
Secret dream or something like that and it's a
Hard it's got like she's a ghost, but it's like a face to see yeah, I ain't even seen that one
German is a German artist
Pretty cool. I can't wait to open it. So what's the description on the back of the box? I read the description
Okay, hold on. I just need to take off the plastic, but I won't open it yet. Okay, let me see. So
Maybe you can see that it went in the plastic box. Okay, it says
It says gallery of hallucinations oracle by Felix not knocked and it's a
Deviant moon, which I don't know. Deviant moon is a really good author, but there's the author's illustration, so
I need you to pop some shrooms and read these cards. Yeah, these are gonna be hallucinogenic
This is like I called the gallery hallucinations
And I think it's by the deviant authorism is Patrick Bolland. So I think it says
German artist Felix not
Who
Something I mean my oh here I mean my my glasses
It says, German artist Felix Knox, who toiled in obscurity during the 1920s and 1930s, has
finally gained the recognition he deserved.
His masterwork salvaged from an estate sale by Fenwood Bureau of Artifacts are now showcasing
this now new comprehensive oracle.
And then, yeah, so, but it says Deviant Moon.
This should be a cool deck. You know what it just did. If not, then I'll just I'm always, you know, until like it does get sponsored to
Some of the old cars tell you like get on an acid trip or a shroom trip and use those cars for the first time off the trip
I think that'll be dope
Yeah, I mean, I mean, yeah, I need some mushrooms first of all. Yeah, I'll just about say donate to psyche y'all so we can make this happen
Yeah, thank you guys, and yeah, I appreciate you know anything. It's appreciated, but I would yeah, but I I do uh
you know want to
Do some readings because I do
think that
First of all, I am I'm very good at it
But second of actually and if you do want to take out private readings, you know, I check on my website
There's looking in there
Or you can, I don't see Link is on there too.
Are they not having a hard to grow?
Yeah, thank you, Charisma.
Yeah, you can go to Etsy too.
I do have like a lot of readings from like,
I think like they're all 50% off.
So I think like the least expensive one is $5
and that goes like to 10, 15, 20, 25.
I also have like an astrology reports available,
like music and art and stuff.
And yeah, just go ahead and contact me.
Alright, I'll be listening in psyche. I've got to hit the dispensary and in here in a half an hour
I got a hit bronze bird up to get that you have a great day. Thank you for being here. Yeah, I'll be listening in though, bro
Yeah, so yeah, I broke my black glasses. Unfortunately, I might have to exchange
But uh
Yeah, I'm these are my thick glasses, but these are so thick that it's like I can't be more than
RG's back to see how long it's mature. It's a real RG
Cuz I
Don't know
Okay, it's me. It's me
So I have a few questions and first of all, I like the green glasses. I think they're nice
Secondly, people in chat are concerned that you were okay with promoting racism, and please
don't get upset, but it's a genuine question, and I think you need to clear there a little
bit.
You know, Chris K. did say some wild shit, talking about so much about it, he was being
racist.
Well, you had that Chris K guy talking about making soap out of Jews.
Dang, it's like I want to I want people to I want people to show the real self
Be it like you know good or bad and then just like you know, but he revealed himself
He's comfortable enough to reveal himself felt comfortable enough to say that of course. I don't agree with it
I think it's reprehensible racism, but it's like so you don't you don't ride
Correct
Okay, so you don't
Now, what about J-Dog in his Asian hate? He hates the Asians. He was dried with that.
No, I don't I mean, I don't I think we're one race the human race and then there's like a little very
You know, you know, we're humans are such complicated creatures that it's a lot more fun to hate people individually
Especially when they show their true selves like J-Daw does on a daily basis
But he really has a thing for the Asian people. He said he's part of like an Asian KKK
where they like do motherfucking...
I don't like it troll, I don't even...
Maybe he is trolling, I don't understand what the troll is.
This is what he's saying, he said he burns Asians in effugee.
Like it's really sick shit.
I didn't even hear, I didn't hear him say any of that so far.
He just, he was just talking about it in chat.
There he is.
Okay, no, no, no, I'll take this shit out, no, no, no.
Okay, first of all, someone said, you hate Asian people.
I said, no, I do not hate Asian people.
There's only one Asian person.
Oh, I can start again this time.
Your Lisp is kind of getting away
with what you're trying to say that you're looking at.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, you faggot.
Listen
Okay, my bad my back psyche my bad, okay
Argy don't try to manipulate
My hatred for art van
Who is holding a mirror up to your own behavior?
Art Vandalay is the only guy. I hate who happens to be Asian. That is the only guy I dislike
Do not try to call, but don't try, don't twist this into, J-Dog hates Asian people because that is a lie.
See, do not...
Apothecary J in chess is, he's lying, J-Dog is...
Apothecary J is fucking Tony the conductor. Do not listen to Apothecary J.
Yes, it is.
I've known him for years, it's definitely not Tony.
You and TZ really suck at your detective work.
Really, you're really bad at it. Both of you.
It was wrong boxes wrong on this person
KZ was trying to tell everyone that EY person was me and Jimmy's you're both idiots is my point
Read arts comment. Let me see if I get fine arts comment. Oh, I don't see it. God damn it
Well, anyways, you're awful for hating Asians, and I don't think I don't
It's like he you see what he's doing. He's saying that I hate Asian
I'm holding a mirror to your own actions. You're lying. You're lying
Psyche he's up here trying to manipulate you dude. He's up here trying to say I hate
No, no, you lie. I hate art vandal. I hate art vandal
It was because of his name art vandal
Yes, yes, and that's why I hate I hated that show. That's where the beef were mean art vandal a half
Has nothing to do with asian has nothing to do is not an asian name. It's not so what is
Action director an asian guy. Oh, no, no, no, no
I have no idea John was the kung fu guy. That's all I know
So yeah, you you can't endorse
Don't idiot RG
Man he's up here trying to manipulate since the guy with the mutilated lips
Look at your face
Sector you dumb fuck why would I show myself on these people who've seen me it's gonna fuck is it gonna be you?
Like I said, kick talk. It's out there. I know COVID night. I know COVID brought a lot of
Asian hate out there and we just we can't have that. Nobody hates Asians. You're the only one
bringing that up. Are you? No, I hate art vandalism. I hate art vandalism and nothing to do with
him being Asian either. You idiot. Well, you've said it many things. You've called him a chink.
I
Got a clip I got a clip goddammit give me a second
Okay, well if I said and I apologize psyche if I said that on your show
No, no, you apologize to our vandal a sir
Well, they are if I said it to you. I apologize. You're not take this out on psyche. There's nothing to do with psyche
Yeah
The clips in the back psyche go ahead give that a roll
Why I just said it I just admitted
On your channel psyche
Yeah
Done it's already done
Can I speak without you interrupting, please? I'm getting word out there on the YouTube streets saying that either
Jdogg apologizes or your channel burns. Oh, this is a position that Jdogg
I just apologize. I said I apologize
I honestly play the clip in this band needs to apologize
Trying to manipulate these psyches trying to manipulate you and you're trying to make it and do what you want
You need to come up and apologize to our Vandalay.
I'm not apologizing.
Let's see what kind of friend you are, G-Dog.
I already apologized, though.
We're done with that.
Let's see what kind of friend you are.
You need to come up and apologize.
We're done with it, dude.
I already apologized.
I already did it.
It's done.
Art Vandalay, with your cam on, and you bust through it sincerely.
I already did it.
It's already done.
Triple sips says a J-dog do it with a camera on and apologize like a man
A good friend would do it. Do you hear me apologize to him already? I already apologized
They're trying to make me
Holds no way. There was no half ass. I admitted to what I did. I said
Wow, this this is the behavior
That I expect would you just say only thing wow is Ivana's face
You are deplorable. I agree with Ivana. You're a piece of shit and you're a horrible friend
Jay dog. Can you put that clip for me? Please?
Yeah, just drop it you keep wanting to
Why are you harping on this RG? Why?
You it's a great word. It's already gone. It's already we were
Worse her people's feelings J-Dog, you know that and I already apologized so we're so we're
Arras you sexualized low cows and now you're spreading hate on a psychs fucking on his platform
Since I said the F word so I since I said the effort that say I I hate
Um homosexual people too see chibi chibi and chat says you're as bad as the people you say you hate J dog
Lies absolute war lies like psyches this guy's just trying to appear just
Turn the cam on apologize safe Sykes channel
I already apologize
Yes, yeah, what you've been told but you're part of that's your crew art part of your crew
So you're gonna partake in doing whatever you want to do
J-Dog docks his children chat
Dude he keeps saying the same shit over and over and over dude, I'm just like I can't believe him man
It's like what I apologize, bro. If I said things in the heat of the moment, you know, like when I'm arguing with them or whatever like that
I apologize if I said on your show, right? I apologize. I'm gonna send you a donation just for that for that
Thanks for that for that fuck up. I'm gonna I'm gonna so be on look out for that
And you know what? Hey, what's up? What's up roguenomad?
Hey, bonna. Hey guys in the chat. Hey, Sebastian says the Reds versus the Padres 940 p.m. Tonight
Yeah, well, yeah, it's okay. I mean RG you mean you said enough
I don't want I don't want harping on me threatening my channel and stuff like that. Yeah
And then I already apologize, but he's still saying that's not good enough do this do this do this do this do this do this
So the problem with how I'm in the show. I mean, you don't have to be here. I don't like I don't like to be threatened on my show
Okay, so this he already apologized
That's what they do man, that's what they do it's never enough for them
It's never enough and then they only is enough for when they say it's enough
Otherwise they threaten you and that's what they get would be to and that's what they're trying to do to you
We get good. I want to see whatever video exile the house because I don't know what he's talking about
So and I would like to see that. Well, I know but I mean, it's a key
It was half hour on the show. I don't know what he's talking about either. I he said it has a word CH
I and K which I don't look there. It looks bad. Okay, so anyone that's gonna like
Harp on me about this. I'm gonna be hidden right now. So just so you know
Okay, so
Anybody who type some shit like that, okay. Okay, so fine. Okay. Yeah, anybody else?
Okay, if you have a problem with me
Write to or call 1-800 nobody cares
It's like you they tried to say I hikes people and I was doing stuff, bro
You can see on your end who did what?
Yeah, you could see and I haven't get anything to anybody. I know you
They just trying to say oh J-dog did this. Jesus. I'm gonna do that and do anything
I don't even touch the wrench. I just say hi, and then I come up on the panel
Yeah, you know, yeah, it's like, you know, as long as you're as long as people I didn't hear anything disrespect
Yeah, I'm not picking up
There there you go, man. These motherfuckers. That's what they do. You're threatening. Okay, what's good?
Yeah, if anybody like is gonna threaten then they are bad
Anyone I
Can't in all these people you see this is a sock puppet army. I go over this in my book
These sock puppet armies
Okay, there you go. Is that the level they're on the sock puppet ones?
Yeah, it's just a bunch of it's like all the same people because it's like how would they did all come here and start saying the same thing when it's like
Turned off my ringer, hold on
Dude it's fucking Tony, man. It's fucking what's in the tone of the conductor. Okay. Hey German lady
Yeah, I apologize on behalf for your show because I don't want anything to happen
I don't want my beef or art Vandalay to affect you. So that's why I apologize to him
I know but it's like it's like a no win situation where they keep saying oh well this person said they didn't say the same thing about
Crystal Marie they can say the same thing about
Ruby Jimmy or
Whoever they whoever they don't like it's like. Oh, they've been this person. I got threatened Janic on the show
I get threatened. It's like
Let me just remember my show like I want to it's like what happened with Christine just yesterday
Like yeah, she was all mad because of crystal Marie like all the shit like saying oh, I'm never gonna do this
I'm never gonna be on here again
You know mad at you and like that's crazy man. Yeah
Um, yeah, but I didn't hear him say it
I mean, it's like he can, and he's apologizing if he didn't say it
Like, what other...
And then look at it, I'll say it again right here
I apologize if I've been any racial slur in the heat of the moment
I don't hate anybody, I don't hate anybody
I don't hate no race when they were like they're saying like you meet them they're saying oh you meet but I never hear them say
Oh my gosh, you know
SIG is being racist or I never hear them say all these being racist. They never care about those people being racist
It's always like, you know anybody that like supports me. It's like, oh my gosh, you know, they're trying to like say I'm racist
I said people are loud but I said it in the middle of the moment not because I'm legit that way
Like it's you know, you're saying it because you're mad just like if I say the F word or if I say
You know the C word or whatever word I may use
It's like okay. It's not because you really mean that because you're just saying it like as a bad word
Yeah
Okay, and so I think like also I think
Exiles a good guy, right
Like I'm cool, but I just want to see what he's talking about. I really do want to see that whatever clip or bronze bird because I never been
Posted or something. I don't know like in that entire tag Jay dog in that because you have the actual thing
Yeah, I don't need to consult the troll PD. I wrote the troll PD. So I know it's a sock puppet army
Oh, yeah, Sebastian. Oh, yeah, not not excel. What's the bashing's good guy, but exhale. Oh, the best is a good guy
Yeah, so that's what I didn't mean to do that special
Like this I need to hide you. I'm sorry. There you go. Does that work Sebastian?
I think that works.
Well, yeah, I mean, they're our friends.
Okay, so, there we go.
Yeah, okay, are we okay, Sebastian?
There we go.
I didn't mean to, it was an accident.
There was an accident, Spunky.
Yeah.
Yeah, I wrote the book on trolling, but the thing is it's like I did write it from the perspective of me as a troll
but I'm not really a bad troll like I'm like there's a whole chapter on the people at Docs and
You know people that do illegal things that is like beyond trolling. That's just illegal activity
It's like not just trolling and it's like supposed to be like kind of funny
Or sometimes a disturbing thing, whatever, but there's a point that even trolls don't
go, right?
It goes beyond trolling, it goes to psychopathy and stuff.
So anyway, yeah, well, okay, well, hey, Spunky.
Yeah, you're welcome. You're welcome. So what happened there with what he was saying that what was Sam and saying earlier?
I mean, I don't want to open up
On sponkeys show, you know, what happened there? I wasn't there. I don't was gaudy
Rain and JT and then rain like really started going and on me like she started saying oh you have AIDS
You have AIDS you have it over over you're disgusting. You're like I just like in this thing really bad stuff
And then Gotti put up a dumb picture of me and like then went full screen and I just got really irritated and then like I left but
It's not spunky spot necessarily. I mean, it's like, you know, I won't blame her. You know, even though it's like
Was she laughing about it? Like was she like like like
Well, I don't I mean was she playing into it or was she just like letting it roll
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. I know it's hard to do a show and this sometimes
It's like I would do the same thing where I just be like, well, yeah
No, nobody's saying like like she did anything wrong. We're just saying like what was she laughing about it?
Just kind of tripping out like it was all happening too fast too much. Yeah, well, you know how it is how to run a show man, you know
How should happen it's not I know it's not true. That's why it's not like a big deal
But that's what yeah, it was just like kind of like a
Little bit like I was like I like to you know, I I feel like
If I go on a show I'd like to be treated like a guest on this show
Like I treat people like yeah, and I'm trying to like have people treat it better and sometimes look they will fight and stuff
Like that like the other day, but it's like guess it's like I'm not gonna like I'm trying not to like that the guest be like
demeaned or disrespected like I'm trying to like have everyone at least be on a respectful level or even if they are arguing
But uh, like and I feel like you know Alexandra has had me on her show like recently a few times
And this like has been really just like gracious and it's like that's I appreciate like just being like
She so it's just respectful
I feel like I should at least like if I'm gonna go to another show and like come on and like, you know
It's like I'm trying to like
Bring joy and happiness and like you know smiles and the laughter and stuff like that and then it's like sometimes I feel like
you know, it's like
the opposite happens sometimes but um, so I
Like to yeah, I don't know. I just like
There's some chance that just hate me. You know, it's like and so I have to like
Were they were they kind to you when you went over there to spunkies chat like or were they kind of like beat us chat
I'll make you a panel verse. I'll make you one too, huh? Oh
Sebastian's in trouble
Oh, what's wrong with panel verse? Okay, I Sebastian be nice to panel verse. Oh, I'm
Hold on
He might I'm not sure but panel verse
Syndicate to show on pan on the panel verse and so don't don't time enough. Okay. Thank you. Yeah, I thought panel verse was tripp cake
I thought that was the same person like this same two different name, but it's the same person look at that account
I'll mod the panel verse, and hey, Sebastian,
he lied about you.
Well, it's not supposed to be personal vendettas,
or else I can't have you as a mod,
because it's like, I have to,
You know, it's a second person he blocked. Yeah, so it's Sebastian. Maybe not the right. It's already been I just I just made you a
Ma okay, so I'm sorry Sebastian. I like you you're you're I mean, that's like I have people pointing out like you're just already
Missed using it. Okay, so I have to like just like keep it in a panel verse. I'll uh, I
Will mod you for
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, but it's no no offense. Uh, no offense, dude
I heard someone's gonna be me for Halloween
They're gonna be psyche for Halloween
Yeah, I think someone said they're gonna be me there. You know, they're gonna have a fish taco. They're gonna have flannel shirt
They're gonna have a beer
Yeah
I mean, but yeah, guys, if I, but I do see you guys like bad mouthing me in like other chats, especially with mod, like it can't, can't be mod, okay?
Trippin simple, I just modded you, so stop cringing, okay?
Just, just enjoy your thing safe.
Okay?
You're welcome. But, but yeah, but like I said, if I, if I see you people in other chats like bad mouthing me, like in mods, it's like a
It's not it's a no-no, okay
Yeah, I don't I guess that's like the people will say oh my god look at his mods even hate him and stuff like that
And it's like that's a bad look that's about yeah
I have to have like at least my mods like my mods not like arguing
I
Know it's a bastion, but it's like it's okay. I mean is
I don't know it's okay. I've had my rent taken a couple of times. It's no big deal
You know you earn it back you earn it back
Because it's like I can't have modding with feelings because it has to be like modding just predict the channel
I don't know. I hit the people that I had a problem with what they're saying, you know
I hit them right and RG come on. Stop it. I don't want to ban YouTube. Come on RG stop
Are you threatening now? He's just he's harping on it. He's harping on the Asian stuff and it's like
He's gonna harp on that now for
He's gonna add that to the lore and so that's part of the gay dog lore like like they think stupid little things
You know how they try to say about the kitty litter about you how they said about dude. He came on here talking about
You don't have a kitty litter box. Hey Sebastian. Just uh, I will but Sebastian
If like you can't if I if I hear about you like modding with your feelings like I have to um, I
Can't have that. Okay, so but I will I will pre-protection right now, but where do I see you hold on?
but yeah, but
Just don't don't know if you time people out to it for like five minutes
but uh
Okay
Okay, and then pit sage, you're gone.
Cause I mean, a lot of people here are just
beta butt kissers, let me see.
So pit sage is gone, yeah.
I told you to stop, I told you
everyone to stop harping on me.
And so.
Lackard you either harping on scale even though it's already been done. Yeah
I
Apologize two times three times like I don't know what more they want me what get on my knees and came up
But what that's what they can make a video clip of it like that's what they want
Yeah, and then they threaten you and say oh well if you don't comply with our demands
We're gonna do such and such
Was like oh you me said um you you me said the word black or something like oh she's so racist and everything and then it's like
We have Aldi and like saying and other people saying the n-word all the time like every other
Word all the time
He's Puerto Rican Dominican Puerto Rican. Yeah, what do you mean wrong?
The second one or the first one
There's multiple that's a good count so it's like fourth stage, but say they're all like
Alts like public counseling. I didn't say anything bad that you saw. Well, I don't we see if the clip
Oh, I just saw the name of sage. He said what and then he said
from before that said
Psyche's nothing but bad looks
LMAO
What the fuck?
There's those fifth this age and there's fifth stage the second one. Okay wrong one. Okay, so
Okay, I got you. I think there you go
Okay, I fixed it
Yeah, I mean I'm against hate the guy I'm a I'm considered a minority. I received like a lot of like racial not racial but you know
Hey based on in like a lot of hidden like a lot of like and if we're like people
But it's like there's a lot of and so I I sympathize with people that are discriminated against for like, you know
It's for like reasons. They can't help like right. There's the sexual orientation or the
You know looks or their race or anything. I don't like
I think it's like dumb. I think no, but uh, so does that mean they were trying to say it was wheelchair?
Hey our handicap pay earlier because we were asking about Mason if he was
Like yeah, I'm trying to twist that they may try to push that
It's like the people that would like have the people you know in the PT Barnum used to have this like he would employ these people that were called freaks
Right, they would but they were these basically outcast of their society living in the middle of the woods
Like not doing anything like you know kept away from everybody and he gave him like made him celebrities
How are certain similar thing? He made him home. He fed them. He made him. He made him somebody
He gave them fame as actually, he gave them like a little life and like a little bit of fame and like a, you know, they were, you know, they were marvelous.
He gave them a reason, he gave them purpose, yeah.
Yeah, and also expose people to like different kind of people and like, so it's not such a shameful thing to be different or whatever.
It may turn their disability into like an asset for them, right?
Yeah, but, you know, and so it's like...
I'm like really for treating people like everybody else.
I'm not for treating like little like, you know,
like treating them different because of perceived something.
Mason was here earlier.
Mason was on earlier and he was showing his feet
and all kinds of stuff.
It was really funny.
But yeah, but he's a sweet guy and it's like,
and I don't want to,
I would never want to hurt his feelings and everything.
I know, but it's just like, so yeah.
It's like some guys, it's like intelligence.
It's like, like, he obviously, he is.
He can read he has he played the drums. I mean, so there's high intelligence there
So it's like it's not like it's just like people weren't saying Benny's retarded because he's like a little bit autistic
Then he's been he's a cool guy. Yeah
Then he actually he had a Trevor Lesnick called and that he has been a job, you know work in and so
Oh, really that's cool. So what's up?
And he was on the show before but yeah people were saying oh my god, you're taking me like no, it's like
You're not taking side. You're just letting it roll. That's all you do. Yeah, and I believe in stopping it
So what's everyone doing the ones and choose for what is the what are the ones and choose me?
I don't know what they're talking about. I can't see the chat
Okay, oh, yeah Mason. Oh, yeah, I mean I can have a talk with him. Yeah, he likes but he likes I think he likes
The he's into this panel but I don't know how he found it, but you know, I think people find it for a reason
to be here and hopefully people can be respectful and everything. Yeah we're good to say and this is
not a hateful panel and so it's like if there is hate expressed by somebody it's basically to like
you know to showcase how people shouldn't hate right maybe it's like a little yeah that has nothing
to do with you like that was and I really apologize for that like I don't know why they keep yeah I
mean it's like and then people are like oh well you know white the only people that can be racist
are the only people that can be racist are white people I don't agree with that I think like
How come they brought up the Chris K scale? What was he talking about? What racist was he talking about?
Oh, yeah, I'll show you what Chris K was doing, hold on.
Um, video file. Let's see if I have this one. I think I do. Okay. Um, I think it's going to be the bigger file.
Let's see. Sort by size. Okay, do I have this one?
Yeah, well he was on the show. I can actually, I didn't know where it is. I can get it off
the stream yard. Because this is kind of funny. It was not funny, but it was like it was a little
bit shocking. You didn't see what Chris K said the other day? No, no, I didn't see it. I guess I
heard about it, but I didn't see what he said. I heard he was like doing like
Yeah.
I'm putting crazy things, yeah.
I'll show you.
Watch.
Let's do it for a minute.
Oh, here we go.
Ready, guys?
Okay, here.
Watch this.
This was the other day.
Share screen.
Actually, no, it's okay.
Yeah, Mary is Mary's famous on YouTube. Hey, brood
Yeah
I see somebody I know hold on
I'm not mad at me. Oh
What you doing? What's up? What's up? Hey, what's up, bro? What's up? How are you?
I'm good, man. I'm just talking uh, you know, I got a story
Listen bro fucking up. I'm getting drunk dude. Who else is getting drunk?
What's up
All right, you guys don't even see me with the fucking you know
What are you talking about?
Are you bald? What's going on? Do you have hair? Yeah, I must get my skin head. I'm a fucking. I'm a fucking peckerwood, dude
What are you talking about fucking I eat all day San Bernardino peckerwoods?
I dated a pecker wood when I was in LA County jail.
I know, you told me about it.
I know, hey, here's the thing.
Psych, I love you, dog.
Hey, man, listen, I'm being serious right now, dog.
Like, fucking, I have to move out of here
where I live right now.
Fucking, hey, I might come through.
Can I chill?
Yeah.
Where you were doing like a Santa Monica or a sense was on a beach you're on a beach
Like fucking here's the thing bro fucking. Yeah, I'll come to dude type shit. You know I mean like fucking
Yeah, you're cool dude like you know, fuck hey, you think I fucking uh
No, I'm not gonna say down on the internet, you know, okay, okay, what's up privately, okay? Oh, yeah, but like here's things like
Yeah, it's like I'll hit you up like you have an Instagram or something like fucking a don't leak your shit don't leak your shit, but I
Fucking I'll come through it listen. I'll have money. I'll have hella money
I'll have like fucking a hundred thousand dollars doc when I would have to leave this house
I'll have a hundred thousand dollars in my bank come on type shit, but you know me so
Come on through. I got you
Yeah, we'll fucking a we'll listen
Hey, money talks broke. You guys want to see me in psych fucking on chatterbait?
How much? How much? How much? You know what I mean? Like I'm down. I'm do you know what I mean?
So anyway, nice. Okay, here's the kitty cat
Yeah, I was like, you know, I mean I was like have my hat. I was on my hat
I'm like, hey, hey, it's like, hey bro, hey bro, you know what I mean?
But yeah, he's like, fuck, I shave my head all day long, I'm a fucking Aryan brother,
dude.
You know what I mean?
So that's it.
Well, you know, it's like a, I don't know, like white power, dude.
Do me a favor don't meet up with this guy. Well, I'm not like I haven't feeling his bad intentions
You know just like I think J-Dog has bad intention intentions, and I would ask you not to meet up with my god meet up
I've never met up with psych you're crazy
What's what you always you try to like, you know talk sexually with him to try to turn like
sexually
You know you do with your voice. We have rub maps, but that was the only thing we talked about was rub maps
Yeah, we're talking about massage party. That was the only thing we had talked about other than that
We all know what that means. I J dog. I know your game
I know your game. You don't know anything, RG. You're full of shit.
10 degree straight, turn psych on, we all know your game is.
Okay, okay, okay.
Now, now, now that I'm a gamer.
I'll tell you how you say it was not important anyways.
I only got to, can we go back to the part where you said you did a peck of wood in the LA County Jail?
Yeah. That's a good question.
Yeah, well, why were you in the LA County Jail?
I was it full that was because I had like just a done like you know, the endless crime charge, you know
What was it? It was a drug charge, but
Possession of a miniscule amount that I forgot I even had
Bangin' dudes in the prison, that sounds safe.
Did you hide anything up your ass?
I wasn't banging anybody in the prison, but I did.
He was really nice.
He took me to the refrigerator, gave me Jell-O and cheese.
I'm gonna give you Jell-O, alright?
Alright, very good.
Was it cocaine or weed?
I think it was, it was, it was, it was cocaine.
Was it meth?
Okay, yeah, I just wanted to be clear.
I didn't want anybody jumping to conclusions.
Yeah, but you know what?
It was like a victim, it was just there for three days.
And so it wasn't like I was like in jail.
Three days, Jesus, that's like a marriage.
Yeah, but I was in the straight jail too because they actually LA they have a prison time. It is a marriage
Well, J-Dog was in jail, too. Did you get banged in jail day to J-Dog? Where's where's camp ever?
You're foolish it never
Rocking over people J-Dog in this room a little bit argue you love it
Yeah, I don't think the Chris K situation is a bright idea. I don't know go along with it. If you want you're an adult, but
People don't like gays either
Half of them are gay anyway
Yeah
Well, so are the Mexican motorcycle guys that we're here and have on your lips. They're normally gay, too
Why why do you think I make moves on guys, who do I make a move on time?
Who are you a fucking liar liar?
I want to know this everyone sees it. You know what you're doing
You're arguing you're trying to spread false information. You're up your game. You're trying to slander. That's all you do
All right, whatever dude. We all know you're here
First you say I'm gay and then you say I'm gay. Hey, which is it RG? Which is it?
Why can't it be both you ever met you ever met chris hanson j doc?
Apologize our vandal a with your camera and god damn it. You know for spike. No, I really apologize. It's not happening
Think you have
I really did it like already
We already did
He's the denial he tries to suppress his urges. I mean Jeff
Yeah, okay, because if I was gay, I would have hit on site. Yeah, okay looking good today Jimmy J
Don I said that I said that show proof show proof. I've never said that never said that to Jimmy never
How does it how do you not see this?
You're not being for real that's okay
Hey dog, you're a gay man. You're a gay man. It's so obvious
Whatever you say arguing whatever you say
sexual lanes fight you just repeat yourself over and over and over
Say yeah
It's amazing what is funky say what is funky come in here saying that I was crazy on her stream
She's breaking her. She's going to her breaking point
She says it's funky do you have a do you have something to like uh?
I don't know. I think I think she's just kidding. I think she's just kidding. I don't know
Is she in the chat you see funky? I think it's like what happened? I don't know
If we're all good skunk here, you're still here. I don't think she's you maybe she should talk to me from clear up the air
Yeah
Like I don't get it though
I've never said anything inappropriate though. I'll always tell us I would like to be with her if she didn't have a boy for them
She has a boy. Oh, you bet. You know what? She's like a little she has a very serious. She's getting married, bro
She's a gauge. You can lay off. She's engaged
So, uh, you know what? You know what? If you want to date me, you can hit on me all you want
There you go, Mason. There you go. Yeah, but say
So can I ask you a question? I'm sorry to interrupt
So this guy Sebastian comes up and have my
Me for like fucking five days you give him a wrench right off the bat, huh? That's how it works
No, no, I gave you a wrench to gaudy
You notice yeah, but that doesn't guy explain why you gave him a wrench for bad mouth with me
Remember that you bad mouth me for five days
No, no, no because you bad mouthed me
Why did you want my me explain that
Was it after you no, no, no, no, you know can't even explain why you don't even know why you don't even know why you just follow the crowd
Don't I know exactly why it's funny that you showed some disgusting photo of you know doctored photo or something
I mean, I don't know hey spunky
You're making up stories now you're making up stories. I don't want to wrench
I don't want around I'm just asking you why you mod this guy after he badmouthed me just bad
He can't hide you you can't hide him you're even it's fine. You're just neutral
Well, he's gonna block he's gonna block me and then it's gonna become an issue and then you know
I'm just letting you know this is how it's gonna go. Hey Mason. You know what?
Spunky says Spunky says you asked her too many times like about
Wanting to date her and stuff. Okay, so it's like you know how I ask you too many times you can say
You can tell me to leave you alone, and then you know if you say it too many times I'm
I know just be happy
Yeah, I know you like to ask a lot
You know, I don't think I'll prove your chance. Why don't you fly him out?
Why don't you fly him out to see you?
Mason, can you drive out here? I thought you said you're gonna drive out of here visiting me. Give a car
You don't want to fly him out, huh?
I
Like I thought you knew that I like women though. Well, it's funky's not available. He'll dress up for you mason
He'll dress up for you
Big time said that would work for him
This whole the innocent thing is creepy. I'm out of here
What's up Mason? Wow guys, what do you think? What do you think?
What do you think should go on though? Hey dog like which what should happen?
Like what do you mean with what?
With me and psych though cuz psych says he wants to be with me
But I mean, I'm not really gay person. I like I never being really a person. That's gay
Well, have you ever been one? Okay. Well, listen J dogs is denial too. I think
You see him you don't know what the perfect guy would be RG he completely loves the cock
Yeah, yeah, you gotta come. Yeah, you do have a voice changer. You do 100% percent have a voice changer
Yeah, Mason J dog is married to what they call a beard. She's about six years old. She can't
You know
he has a dog named Pickles
you know nothing about me except I have a dog
that's all he loves
that's all he loves, his girl
I know you got failed relationships and your girl left you
who doesn't have
that's all he loves
no, I get what it is
you know nothing about me
that's why you hate women
you're up here telling everybody about homosexual
yes you do, you hate women
I call you a homosexual
And you hit on Jimmy you hit on Tony you had a mastery for you
Have I ever hit on you psych have I ever hit on you ever ever ever
see like you know you feel the vibes you know you feel those vibes no if i can just my friend
my home that's why psych's smiling right now he feels those gay vibes for me to do okay yeah okay
oh dude he's laughing because you're just full of shit argue he's just running around you should
you should take a look at j-dogg i think you guys he has a lot of repressed homosexual feelings
I
Would you make a splunky feel uncomfortable you said the same
Mason this is honest question. Why would you make Splunkie?
Mason I'm asking you a question Mason. Why would you say that to Splunkie if you said the same exact thing to beta three days ago?
What are you talking about?
You said the same thing to Splunkie that you said the beta so be that you want to be with
Yes, he did
You want apparently you've been making a splunky very uncomfortable
Coming on to her asking her to be your girlfriend and you did the same thing to beat up three days ago because I was listening
Why are you cheating on me Mason with all these?
uh-ohs
Mason I don't there's other sites that are better to me woman Mason. I don't think YouTube's a place like you hold on
It's like you hold on man. It's like I was trying to say like
Well, why would you want to be gay if you're a guy like me though? I thought you go for women, too
He does but he finds you very attractive Mason. He just can't help himself
Mason but it's a natural thing our G to go for women even if they have somebody because they look you know
He thinks a guy but sex is natural to him. So I
Like what do you mean our G? See I ask him he's the expert
you. Amazing. Are you top or
bottom? I guess that's the only
question. Definitely a bottom.
Uh-huh. Definitely a bottom.
RG, what is he talking about?
He wants to know if you take it
up the ass like J dog.
Well, I'm the only one who takes it up the ashes RG RG loves taking a doggy stop
This is about Mason
Bridging my name up thinking is you're a fucking lunatic cut it out you attention
Oh lunatic
I'm trying to have a conversation with me
Okay, so again, you said the same thing to be to just a few days ago basic
So, how do you want them both RJ? What did I say to her to be there?
You said you wanted her to be your girlfriend apparently the same exact thing. You did this plunky
Yeah, what's wrong with that door do that's normal for a guy to say stuff like that
How could you have feelings for two people at the same exact time, right? You don't find that a little weird
Yeah
Tinky-fella aren't you there
You know who's single is crystal I think crystal signal okay. Oh, yeah. Yeah, crystal. I love him
Marie Mason, she's pretty hot
What was that?
This poor guy wouldn't know what to do with a Chris Moray.
She's a nutcase.
I think Alex is single, too.
Do you have Ellie in the video with me?
They're showing our bellies.
No, it's not nice to hit on people.
Jesus Christ, Mason.
Jesus.
It's not nice to hit on someone who's engaged,
who's told you once that they're not interested.
It's not nice to keep asking.
And apparently it's made Slunky feel very uncomfortable,
so it's not appreciated.
Our G. I didn't really do anything to make her uncomfortable. I was just telling her what I felt like
I'm just gonna show you real quick Mason look look here. Here's that here's um, well
She just said that she feels uncomfortable. She likes you, but you're a quote-unquote
Exhausting to make a woman feel exhausting is not very nice. I
Wasn't trying to do anything wrong
Okay, maybe you just didn't understand but now you do so you won't do it again, right?
Okay good to know. J-Dog is at Oompa Loompa. It's fucking hilarious.
You're lying. Keep the shit on you.
Why?
You've seen it already there.
Yes, I've seen it.
This was the wrong one.
You've seen it. What is that about?
Oh, let me tell you what that is about.
How dare you.
J-Dog makes a perfect Oompa Loompa.
How fucking dare you.
Hold on. Let's do the wrong one.
There's the other one.
Oh, wow. I have to read this.
Okay
Stop for a minute. All right in the back arc says stop the Asian hatred
It says I will be protests protesting psych and Jamie Ruiz juniors hatred of Asians and redondo
Dude he does my name and doctor your house bro
So he dropped down though, like why is it why is he not there anymore? Why did he drop down?
Yeah, he's been he's being stupid
Here Mason, this is the
Oh, so I got to know who the person is that you're talking about though
Is this lady right here? Oh, I'm gonna take it here. Do you see on screen yet?
Yeah
He was in the white that white currency game that did hurt me I was trying to kill me
I guess she she's like a lot of criminal record and she's trying to cover it up. So
We're just gonna break it
Yeah, yeah, she's got a big criminal record. She's got to get talk
She do like who's that talk it is that it kills kids. It's me. Oh my god, please don't no no no no
She's hot, but you know some people are like really mean and that's gonna be okay
And you know like that first thing I told you these people like that the fucking I told you like that the same people
Or the same like you wouldn't even believe that they're age. You know what I mean? It's like
Like over a hundred years old
Well, I'm saying that
That I wouldn't understand that a bitch
That would act like that like that is like I guess she she's like a lot of you know record
And she's trying to cover it up. So
We're just gonna break it
Christina we not the first thing we all know. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, she's got a big criminal record. She's got to get fucked
No.
Aaron, you've got friends.
No, no, no.
Yep.
Why?
What'd she do?
She was a sick criminal?
Yeah.
She was a bad criminal.
What'd she do?
She killed kids.
Oh my god.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm not a sick person.
We are my goats. I think Sykes on this is something here
Her soul would be perfect for you
They put him in these sex trafficking rings and her burn her friend probably fucking
And we're gonna get them all fucking caught real quick
J dog. Yeah, they're not trying to help people. They're trying to get people. What's that Mason?
No, no, no, no, don't listen to Argie Argie's a piece of shit. He's a liar. Please
What's up, man? Why are they saying why are they saying hateful stuff towards me though?
They're lying their pieces of shit. They're just haters. Don't listen to them. You suck
Listen, you don't want to make people feel uncomfortable
It's one thing to joke around and have fun
But there are lines, you know, and you don't want to cross those lines, you know, you want to
You want to be friends with people you don't want to make people feel uncomfortable like Jay dog does no
I already make people feel very uncomfortable. He's a very weird person. He stalks people everywhere. He goes
He tries to make everybody a little cow. He loves it. That's what Argie loves to get you gotta respect a groupie Jenner
Try to do two you know, but Jimmy was smart and he wasn't stupid
So he saw a pasture game and he played you and that's why you hate him so much
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
You know, and YouTube isn't really a dating site. Maybe you should go somewhere where like-minded people are also looking like I don't know plenty of fish or
Tinder or whatever the fuck they are now. I don't even know
On Facebook, I don't talk to nobody. I don't have Facebook
Except that he's gay
Lies
But anyways, no Facebook isn't a dating site either and neither is YouTube Mason and you need to spend respect people people's boundaries honest
Actually, the deal honestly my rule with women is let them hit on you first
That that way no, so we don't use Instagram either though
I don't have any of those sites none of them you didn't hear a fucking word I said did you Mason?
Because you're
RG said YouTube's not a dating website, Facebook's not a dating website, I can understand that.
There's plenty of fish is, and there's other sites like that, you may have better luck there.
Yeah, I just don't really get on to that because I usually use time on YouTube, that's why I
get on YouTube.
Well, I get that, but YouTube isn't the place on that, and you don't want to make people
feel uncomfortable at all.
No, I get that RG. I'm not I'm not trying to do that stuff on purpose though
It just seemed to come off that way. Do you not do you have no control over your own behavior? I mean, it's not by accident
It's okay. You know you learn to lesson just learn from it and move on
In other words
Yes, that's all I can do RG
Okay, we'll move on from it, you know, and maybe let women hit on you instead of you hitting on that, you know
That might be a safer. Yeah
Yeah, okay, so go get a fucking tender account or whatever the fuck
Grindr if you're J dog
Yeah, that's you are G. That's all you
Yeah, just reading chat, I don't they're being mean at all Mason, but there's some good advice
Someone says you should could you come on too strong which might be the case
Other people say tried to try to one site
So what are you doing site am I doing what do you mean?
Yeah, what are you up to?
He's masturbating thinking a J-dog. Oh, please
You like that one didn't you Mason you got a laugh
Rg you're just disgusting. Why do you think about sex everywhere you go a homosexual sex any type of sex?
That's all you think about
I'll say it's not right to talk about like that stuff
What stuff sex?
No, yeah, like stuff like
Giants
Jada they're supposed to happen behind closed doors though. Yeah, you know what you know what makes you come I'm jacking off
Before him Mason
Talking trying to get disabled people to go to massage parlors again. No, I'm asking him if you ever been
I asked him it has he ever been to one before that's all I
A massage parlor where they give you a massage like a back rub where they get like a chiropractor
No, I've never done that. Hop your back or stuff like that. What about an acupuncture? No acupuncture
What is acupuncture? I don't know what that is what where you lay down like a massage cable
They think like an aroma massage therapy. They put like stone rocks on your back
You know I didn't say anything about a rubber. I said a massage parlor. There's all kinds of them
You took it the wrong way are you
You have a disgusting mind.
You have a disgusting mind, R.G.
Yeah, it's me.
It's me.
Yes, it is me.
Yes, it is.
You're bringing it up.
Me and she's talking officially.
Can you stop, J-Dog, please?
Mason, can you tell us the type of women you're looking for?
Maybe we can help you out, Mason.
I thought Syc was trying to help me out with that.
R.G., he said he was trying to help me out with that.
What features do you like in a woman, sir?
I just like right. I don't know it whatever comes to my like whatever's available
Well, yeah, but there's got to be certain qualities that you like maybe you know shared hobbies or features or are you a butt guy?
Are you a boob guy like what's your deal? What do you still like any woman that talks to you? Alright?
You're gonna be like so I you know that I like
Sikes like she's in his head. Are you a foot guy Mason?
Dick
You like speed
Rg there's certain things I like about women. Yeah, that's what I just fucking asked you. What are they?
This is like I'm like Senate though
Yeah, yeah, really you're a feet. Yeah
Yeah, are you the trans at all?
Huh
Sexuals
No, I'm like I'm not gay, but he wants me to be gay though RG. So I'm trying not to be I know he does
Yeah, but some people what buddy of my name bill he doesn't see trainees as being gay. Maybe you feel the same. I don't know
He loves feet
Tits is it okay if they have a dick Mason
I don't think that's what I would be used to I'm saying I don't think that's what I would be used to though
It's okay. If you're not used to it, but would you consider?
You know a woman with a little extra little hog
Well dainty penis if you will yeah, okay, so Mason so flurry the flurry diamonds. I said there you go
It's a big burn on psych
But she's a beautiful woman. So is that okay?
Gorgeous woman, but it has a penis
You don't know
Aren't you I'd never really see women look have that that's why it's hard to say
Well, yeah, just imagine a chick with a dick. So you're gonna just stop you're not good at this. Just mute please no bitch
No bitch right here
Just thinking of a very infeminine man kind of like J-Dog just you know
Feminine okay. Yeah, it masculated man. He masculated by the way you think you actually
I do
Yeah, I'm married
Yes, I'm married you little cuckboy. Let me talk to Mason fucksakes. All right, Mason
So all right, so you're iffy on the dick, right? They could maybe have a dick. You just don't know because you haven't tried it
Yeah, I've said I'm not used to that stuff
So I don't think I would like it because I'm not really used to seeing that when I see women
Mason you want to vagina you want to vagina or penis?
What do you mean? I don't understand
Have you ever felt the warmth of a vagina Mason? Have you ever been inside a woman before?
Oh, I've tried it before but I really didn't do it that much though in my life, too
Just once or twice
I've been inside a woman
I've done it a couple times. Yeah, but that was it
Did you pay for it?
No, I just happened naturally when I was with the person
Oh, was it someone you were dating or did you meet him at the bar? How did that happen?
There's somebody I met. Yeah, we started, you know talking and seeing each other and that this became yeah more than that
Yeah, okay, so it happened a few times it was hot, you know
I'm talking to a new friend. What do you
What do you mean?
I'm trying to jerk off for me like you would.
No, that's not me.
That's all you know.
Alright, so you met Akuzai.
Right?
It's like Akuzai Ivano.
Ivano punch you? I don't know.
Someone who would just rip your head off
and give him a chance.
Yeah, I think she's a little...
It's like Ivano was coming at you, sir.
She was in a tent?
Yeah, so she was in your cat. Are you interested I've on are you interested in?
No, I don't know her name is Ivana
Love funny
Yeah
Amazing, I buy one of our team. What kind of women are you?
J don't you stop it comes off
There's no try hard here. Let me try it with you. What are you trying to make some right here? What are you trying to do?
You're trying to pull a music biz Marty you think this guy is slow
So you're up here trying to conversate with him like a normal person like yeah, that's what you're doing
You're not figured it out yet. You dumb fuck
There's nothing about
Talking about
Shut up. You're a dumbass
This is why no one likes you. Cuck is you and only cuck is no one
Cuck is you are you continue to speak to my new friend, please?
So you gotta keep your new friend by the way a new friend by the way attention whore. Yeah, he's my new buddy
Your new locale. Yeah, we see that
This is why no one like
what's up mason so what so what do you have you have a woman though or do you have a girlfriend
or somebody you're dating yeah i got women i got very unsatisfied wife straight he goes to
massage parlor mason have you ever been to a massage parlor they gave you a happy ending
have you heard of that yeah they have they have straight ones they have they have gay ones they
have multiple different ones for different people trying to get a disabled man into a robin telling
I see what your attentions are J-Dog. I don't like it. What intention? He asked a question and then I answered a question
About a Rubin tongue. What is it with you in getting the master bait or special people?
What is your pre Jesus you can't even help yourself. Can you bro? I don't know what the fuck you talking about
J-Dog J-Dog I never been to a massage. I never been to massage parlor before
Tell all about it. This is this is your question. You think from here
Bro, I'm actually a story from another time. I can't really speak on all that right now
But just know you don't have a problem speaking with it to Tony the black dragon or Jimmy
When
Tell me all about it
For is your sir?
Well, what's going on?
Okay, okay, what kind of women do you like?
Like what kind do you have a preference or do you have like no preference I?
Have like a I mean anyone like like I'm gonna crush who would be your Hollywood crush
You had to say dog anyone any woman that looks interested to me is the one I go for though no matter
Oh, that's bad bro. That's low-scangers. You don't want that you got to have some type of you got to have some type of
Measuring stick like who's your favorite crush like a any kind of crush like
J dog, I like the singer from evanescence her name's Amy Lee. She's a singer for the band evanescence. Okay. Okay. She like rocker
Okay, okay
Do that lady's like that's my kind of type J dog. Okay. I like
Yeah, I like gothic women, okay
Then you're supposed to close your mouth like the weirdo you are just the fuck up argue I'm talking with them
This is how you do it
He did so okay, so we like that kind so
Very cool groupie Jimmy, I guess the ones that look kind of like
You don't argue. Are you done? No, I'm not. You're fucking pathetic. You're pathetic, Argie. You're so pathetic.
Am I? Am I? Yes, you're very pathetic. You're so jealous. I can't believe how jealous you are, Argie.
Oh, it's pathetic, man. Jealous of what? You know what you're jealous of.
You know what you're jealous of, Argie? You know what you're jealous of? You know what you're jealous of?
She's so unsatisfied with your wife. She's so unhappy. She told us what we talked to her.
Yeah, okay. Yeah, I mean you talk to my wife. Yeah, okay
Somebody you talk to somebody but you wasn't my wife. I'm up here. Uh, so art will be protesting psych and Jamie
Again man, he's doctrine
Hey dog, what's up? What's up mate? You see what he does now when you're gone? That's what he does man
I want to say that the kind of women the kind of woman I like J dog are kind of like I guess you can say got the key
But the ones that look like maybe like Avril Lavigne, you know the singer named Avril Lavigne
Yeah, yeah, like skater like skater got the type. Okay. Okay. Yeah, like it's like a girl that yeah
Like a woman it looks kind of like a skater woman or a rocker woman or like maybe like you like red hair
Are you do you like red hair brown hair or it doesn't really matter? He like belongs or it doesn't matter
Well, blonde is my favorite, but I could go for any other kind of hair colors too. Okay. Well here
Well, don't don't shorts, you know, don't sell yourself short. Let's go for a blonde
You know aim for the stars and see what you get
Do what you do
You're about what 35 do you ever go out to like bars or clubs or anything?
I don't even know if there's exist any more clubs. That's you know way
Don't jade dog. I used to go to bars and stuff like that, but not as much anymore
It's like
Okay, it's like I didn't sit on a score earlier man
There's some this one punk started lying about me and saying stuff that wasn't true
That's why I timed them out. All right, can you give me back the rents cuz that I got back at that punk specifically for that reason
Well, I was getting back at him because the guy lied to me the guy lied about me because I was sticking up for Jay dog there
I was saying that a Jay dog seems to be a nice guy. The guy lies about
Well, yeah, Jay dog, they were lying about you
They tried to throw me in that you know, and I don't even know you so I was just saying that he seems to be a nice guy
That's why I do that's what they do. They hate on everybody even though if you're a cool person
They hate on you just for no reason. Oh, yeah
That's what they do. I saw it. I saw what they're doing man. Why do they keep talking about gay stuff and accusing you of stuff, man?
They're closeted homosexuals. They keep saying
First they said I sexualized locales
Then they say
I'm a local groupie and then they say I'm gay like they just make up stuff like random stuff
Then they said I had a voice chat with Tony
The peanut butter guy in a wheelchair and you're right
Which never happened. That's why I want to see what stream that is. Yeah, it ain't right man and many of these things are lies
I don't even believe
That's one of my good liposuction surgery clients
Yeah, by the way, Sebastian is a very good liposuction, dude, so
You know just throwing it out there
By you psych I live in Redondo Beach
Very good client
Do you shop at Trader Joe's
What was that
Oh, you're in north. Oh my gosh. You're down. You're so you're down by artesia and stuff. Oh, wow
I don't believe what they say man. I think many people lie and they exaggerate
I don't know you but you seem to be a nice guy
Yeah, that's what they do man. They like to make things bigger than what they are
Just like if I say a mistake like if I say a slur or if I say like the F word or you know
Oh, he said this he said that and they'll stick it with you for years and years and years
I know it's been done to me too man. Trust me. I've people have done that to me. They lied about me for years
Defamation a character. I know what that's like. That's why I don't know you be a senior be a good guy. That's guy black RG
I've been battling with him for four years four years different communities in the music biz Marty groovy Jimmy
He's followed me everywhere. I went ever. Yeah, he's annoying man. He seems annoying
Yeah, the same shit over and over he says the same shit over and over and over. Yeah, maybe he's the one that's pervert minded
Oh, no, he is he's definitely a pervert. He definitely is he's closeted homosexual
He's just mad because he's gay and he doesn't know how to come out with the failed relationships. He's just a loser
completely he seems to be pervert mind I keep hearing I keep listening I'm talking it's all he's talking about these
Discussing things man. Maybe he's one of my gay stuff and and well not just gay stuff of sexual stuff
He talks about sexual stuff. Yeah, he's perverted minded man. Yeah, you listen to him talk. He sounds perverted minded
About what type of women he likes
Well, what were you eating like just a while ago?
Paul, how'd you find my show and like are you friends with Seb or what?
No, you're you know you popped up because like
I don't know if I like all these other streamers are I walk
Up one day because I guess I guess you're kind of related to other streamers
So I guess you popped you know you popped up and
And I saw God God and all these guys on your inside your show and I was like wow who's this guy
Yeah, yeah, it's a pretty crazy show. Well, he's a good guy psych that back to the Paul guy
He's a good life with such a surgery client. Oh, that's why
Good client he paid his bills on time man. He's a good
I need you to suck my fat dude. Well, yeah, we gave him a good. So here's surgery there. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
That was a long time ago. I need another I need another session, you know, how you regain the weight. Did you?
Put the pounds back on yeah, I know a Mason I know him from another stream
He's a good guy Paul, but he put some pounds back on we'll give you another liposuction surgery procedure Paul don't worry about that
No, I do push-ups all I've been doing push-ups like tons of push-ups every day like hundreds and hundreds and like
Well, I've been trying to I don't want to waste my whole day doing push-ups, but I've been doing a lot
Now that's gonna help you to a certain point
But still if you can't lose stubborn fat like that the best thing it's lipo sections, sir. That's your best option
Yeah, it's the best
And you know what else that Paul we got the new lipo sections machine zapper 8,000
Dr. Steve
State of the art technology Paul you you work out Sebastian. I don't work out right now
When we work out, I got too much back problems. I got too many back problems right now. So I had a nerve. I don't work out
Let's see, okay. Wow, we have 76 people in chat right now. That's awesome. Thank you guys
Anyway psych did you hear what I told you earlier?
What'd you say? I was telling you that I had to get back at someone man
They they started something with me and they lied about me when they don't even know me
That's why I timed it out
But you can give me back the wrench for protection man because some of the weasels I had to deal with them
That's that's what happened. But the he-man's already saying that you already started hiding people again
I timed out a few people because I told you they were they were trying to lie about me because I stuck up for that J dog
That's why people will this like but now they'll just like
Do it now to annoy you and stuff like that. Yeah, no more wrench. I think I know I just try it out
That's like I need like good loyal people, but I can't have people modding with feelings
I'm not modding with feels I told you it's like I had to get back at someone cuz they were lying and flat out lying about me
Because I stuck up for that J dog guy. That's what that's what happened there. Okay. Well, you give me back the wrench
Don't worry about I don't misuse a wrench. I simply have to get back at someone. I feel like it
that's why I did because you got a bunch of lip-tards there and they're lying about people
I don't like it that Jake dog guy seems to be a nice guy that they're gonna slander the guy
I don't like it and then he lied about me because I defended the guy you know
Sebastian what is the rich do anyway, so like what is the rich about though like what people have wrenches it's to wrench you
No, thank you. Thank you, Sebastian. I appreciate you man. Oh, yeah, gee doggies. I see something in a right sometimes man
Yeah, that's what they do any time that they see anybody you think somebody next next, you know
Hi, I don't want to go with the crowd man. I don't need to follow the crowd man like I use my
Crowd that's the whole issue. I don't follow the crowd so they know that's what they love to do
I see someone that seems to be a good person like I don't I don't need to follow the crowd like I don't
I don't cave to peer pressure like most people. Yeah, you argue is just gonna come up doxing again
That's gonna come up doxing again
Two times
We understand that you hid someone because they were saying something about bad about J-Dog
but it's not your chat to be hiding people they could say something bad about me
they could say something bad they could say whatever they want it's not
no man they were lying about me that's why they were flat out lying about me
you can't have a fucking wrench and the fact that you keep asking for one just
means you don't get it and you shouldn't have one sir
Jesus Christ a fucking wrench and no no i sell the score man because someone
lied about me because i stuck up for that you said all the score means you
shouldn't have a fucking wrench
Now let me ask you man. Why you keep putting that j-dog guy down there?
What's what he says you've been following for years dude? He just
Guides a piece of crap argues a piece of shit. Isn't what he does
What are you pervert minded RG man?
He's a hundred percent per man
Control himself and his feelings
Right you can't control yourself seby seby boy
No, man, you got to get over the guy. You've been you've been after this guy would for you
You got a life man, you got a life your owner what you know
I don't know about your life, but I can find out in harassing it fuck with you for a few years
How do you like that sub Sebastian? No, you'll never find anything about my life
You don't know you don't know me as much as you don't know that other guy
I fuck with J-Dog for a reason. I was having a nice conversation with Basin and it could have
Oh, yeah, well don't judge me man. I'll try to throw me under the bus. The timing out is none of your business
He just told you you couldn't have a wrench because you bought it with your feelings
Then you know I wasn't I wasn't with my feelings. I just told you man this guy wrong mean I got him back
Man, it's not with my feelings mind your business. I don't mind my business back
It's not your check man. If you want to you want to mess with me mind your business, and I won't mess with you
Feelings what feelings man, there's no feelings about it. You just said you had to get them back, dude
Well, yeah, I had to get them back. That's not my feelings man. I made it right. I made it right
That's what that means. I corrected it wrong. I made it right
Mason is that your type?
That's that's that.
Yeah, she's beautiful.
Yeah, her name is Emma Leviathan.
So go to her chat and
She's like you that's evil.
You gonna put Mason on her?
Oh wait, Vanna that RG is overrated.
Like what is your
I'm not a fan of that one.
I like this Paul fellow though.
Hey, how you doing, buddy?
RG, is that you?
Yes, sir, how are you?
Oh, OK, hey, hi.
I'm good.
You're on my team, right?
You're going to be playing dodgeball, right?
We're playing faggot dodgeball.
You're on my team, Paul.
We're against Jay Dog and Sebastian, two homos.
We're going to get them.
You ready?
Maybe you're the homo.
You're always talking about gay perverted stuff, man.
You're a national, your mom joke.
You're giving your boys your best one, Paul.
My I don't what the more listen to the one that you're the one that's game and the more I think about it the more
Sebastian's mother, please Paul. Will you
What is this guy? How old is this guy like ten years old? What is this guy?
Strongest guy Jay Dogg for like like five years and he blocked me for no reason
Dirty horse Sebastian
I
G you talk like a kid man, you don't even know me. This is how you talk to people. You don't know
You're the guy has to get
Sounds much of a nicer guy
So you get someone back in chat just shut your mouth
Yeah, you don't mind your business man. Don't talk about me man. You don't know you don't talk about me
Just like I did my balls on Jay dogs forehead almost every day. Just to make a mind
Good guy Sebastian doesn't have a wrench or you know, no one will get blocked now
I know you're not rentable sir
I don't even know why you blocked me though, that's the weird thing about that
I blocked the guy a long time ago and I didn't know him, that guy was acting like a jerk
but now he's a nice guy, but now he wasn't like that before though
No, I've always been like that
That's before we got to know each other
You know your problem is RG, I notice the thing with you man, you're fast and just people you don't know
I don't know you're pretty fast to judge people man. I mean who the heck are you a good summary?
I don't even know that you are man. You don't even know me and you talk about me like you know me. What the heck?
I just called your mother a whore. That's okay
You got no class man. I don't waste my time with low-class people like you man. First you say gay stuff and you accuse Jay Dogg of being gay. Maybe you're the one that's gay man, cuz you're always talking about gay stuff.
I saw what you're about you show me how much you got no glass man. You show me kind of person you are
I like this guy Jay dog, but I don't like you. I don't like you man. I'm glad. I won't even call you sir
You don't deserve because I'll call you punk. Oh
No, not a punk
Yeah
You come at Jay dog man leave the guy alone man
Modding with your feelings. You're pathetic man. I'm just trying to live a life with someone
And even talk about rent. She's just fucking gay
Asking sorry, she's just fucking a site. Maybe you ought to get out there man. Yeah, try to live a bit
I don't even get out the internet man. It's not good for you. It's turning into a gay faggot
Can Mason talk please go ahead?
Like that's Emma that's Emma Mason he wants you he wants to hook you up
Yeah, not too bright man. I'll tell you that
Can you send me the way hard so that's how are you Paul I heard a dog talking
I heard you talking I can tell Jay dogs a better person than you man
Why not be educated but darn he's a nice person than you man much nicer
Did you get the guy back in chat there?
But you don't live with your feelings. Oh, I got him. I got him back, but he on back
I mean he on time that guy you sure showed him
Oh, yeah, I showed them then
Yeah, and you lost your wrench for it
Man, I don't care
You'll stop asking for one day
I can make a difference in my life
Is there a way is there way for me to check her out though, so how much you wait right now
Uh, me? Oh, I don't know, maybe two, two fifteen, maybe?
No, you left to the right to it.
Two fifty?
Two fifteen, what? Two and five.
Oh, two, two fifteen, okay.
I got muscles now, look at my, look at my, I got, I got chest muscles now, look.
Can you take off your shirt?
I got my shirt. Hey, why'd you try to throw me on the bus just a minute ago, man?
Then I had your back and I didn't give you the discount man for liposuggest surgery
He was just being honest. You don't sound like a little discount ball
I'll be a ball we know each other from another student, but when I didn't know when I didn't I blocked me even when I didn't know
Are you a Bible guy Sebastian?
Yeah, I'm a Christian man. Why oh you just you had the little Bible thing in your little name there
So it must be in a lot. Yeah. Yeah, I'm a Christian. I'm in the church of Jesus Christ
Jesus you're a fucking morning
What do you want me to do?
What do you want me to check her out?
Not Mormons, man.
LDS members of the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints.
No, you guys like little girls.
That's all I know.
No, man.
She's more lies, man.
Yeah, she's more lies.
You're going to stop lying about people then.
You know what?
No, man.
It's a pattern.
It's a pattern that you should go through.
You know what I said?
It's a pattern.
Not why are you lying about people that you don't know man. Come on
You just told me you're sure how many people are gonna take I gonna keep believing when you believe in you when you keep lying about people
You don't know we're not real Christians anyways
You don't know anything you don't know anything you like to talk many things, but you don't know anything
Okay, I know that you know more you don't want me to look man get educated
David I'm not gonna waste too much time talking to you man. It's a waste of time
They have a checkered past. What do you say? Anyways, I don't care about you, man. I'm not here for you
I'm here for you cult
You know, you wouldn't say that they're checking they have a checkered past a little bit multiple wives a little girl
Sebastian, it's not true man. That's a bunch of life. That stuff's not true
What's that
You're here for somebody special likes and you're here for you Mason to give you a life with such a search discount
No, we're all too old for Sebastian him just like his church. I like him really young
really really young
Is that all right, man?
Like the light people you like the lion slander people man. See how that turns out for you
Are you gonna come back on you?
Now it's now it's now I know for sure man that you're lying about a J-dog if you're lying
Definitely lying about J-dog now
Girls Sebastian are you a poster boy for Scientology like Tom Cruise?
No, man. No, I told him I'm in the church of Jesus Christ Larry Saints. LDS is worse in Scientology if you ask me. That's even worse
Oh, come on, then you don't know you're talking about. No, it really is worse. I don't know you're ignorant
RG you're ignorant. Don't talk about stuff that you don't know
You know you don't need to lie about slander that's definitely
Slander when you don't know someone
I heard you I heard you slandering this jay dog
I listen to
Jay dog guy for an hour slandering lying about him and you don't need to lie about stuff
You don't know I know all about it
I've seen a few documentaries in a couple of movies, so I know I know about it as much as
Well, you got that thing on the screen there
You like little girls. You like
Sebastian what is this going on like on the screen, I don't know I ask him that's what I'm asking him
He's like he's bringing up little kids. What he does man. Don't let that pull up. I know I see that J dog
I've seen it now
What he does all the time
Know the guy doesn't even know me now. He starts talking about my church, and he says a bunch of
The mentality of a child he slanders. He says I'm gay says this he says all kinds of shit. I'll tell them
Man, it's perversions and slandering
Well, he says well, what do you say Tony wheelchair? I had a VC. Well, whatever chat all kind of life. I
Don't know. I see it. Then I see Jay dog. I see that
Let's see, let's see what's going on here. Okay. Put the picture of the tranny, please.
Psych, let me see what's going on. Show me what's going on.
Yes, yes. There you go. There you go. Thank you.
Paul I want to tell you I want to clear that up with you Paul that when I blocked you that was like from years ago
I thought you were trolling me. I thought you were just a troll. So I didn't want to waste time energy on you
That's why I blocked you like three years ago
I know why do you bring that up now? Why do you bring that to a guy that doesn't know me?
Don't bring it up. You're gonna cause confusion of people. You know what I mean?
No, I just say what did he Sebastian when do you bring up that was wrong?
Yeah, now I got to know that Paul Paul seems to be a nice guy
But before I knew my I blocked man
I thought the guy was wasting my time and I don't I couldn't be bothered by it
It's that's why I block I got many people black man. That's why I don't waste time with people. I
Always time with dumb people. I gotta talk to good people intelligent people dumb people. I block them. I don't waste time
Just YouTube relax, dude
Know it's just you too, but even then like he's still he you can only take so much nonsense and and childish stuff, man
You know
I mean you can only take so much crap and nonsense me it gets annoying
You know like you say what the heck I can't I couldn't be bothered by this nonsense
You block the person you block the idiot. You know what I mean? Yeah, I'm gonna go smoke a cigarette, bro
I gotta
Okay, so here's what I got
Take it easy, Jayden
You see the screen, Mesa?
That's Flirty Diamonds
Sike, who is that, though?
Is that the one you're trying to tell me about?
Like, the woman that you want me to talk to?
No, that's Emma, but Flirty Diamonds is another person
I've got the baseball game that's going to start
Is that that one?
Is that that one Latina that was on, uh, Latina transsexual that was on?
No, that doesn't look like a, wait
It's like is she straight though, or is she like transgender though like what is she?
She's transgender
It's like so which woman is not it's like so which woman is not a transgender though that you tell me about though straight. Oh
You watch baseball
You like her right there
You like baseball ball, what do you think me son, so like what is she though? She's straight
Yeah, she looked like a dude though. That's kind of
Disappointing
Probably a guy
So I tell me is that a woman. No, it's like tell me is that a woman or is that a guy though?
It's a woman
No, it's like she looks like you said
Tracy like you said it looks like she's a transgender though, right? Oh, it looks like it
So does she have guy parts though Cyker does she just have women's part is guy parts
So she's not all women's psych is what you're telling me she actually has guy parts, too she has boobs
Yeah, you can lactate but what what about the rest of those like what about the rest for body though
Is it still like a woman's or is it guys parts, too?
I haven't seen but I think I saw like a inflatable balloon animal under her under her
What happened to the other one you had another picture of you don't have other do you have other ones, too?
Are you an Emma? Hold on
No, I have this one
So this lady right here, let me see.
You can go see posts, is there a post?
Let's see how this goes.
Hello.
So here, this is Emma, let me see.
Oh yeah, that was the one that you were showing earlier.
Yeah, okay, here we go.
Did you like her, Mesa?
So I guess she's single?
Yes, she is, she's absolutely single.
But she's looking for a millionaire, I think.
She's a sucky bitch.
Oh wow.
This one's more, this one looks more my type right here.
You like her?
Yeah, go ahead, she's a, she's not a fan of mine anymore,
but we used to be friends, but yeah.
She's like, does she live stream though?
Does she live stream almost every night?
You can go.
She's the same as, she's the same as.
Okay, there we go.
She actually is Satan's ex-wife.
So you pay with your soul.com and so keep that in mind.
What did you think?
She sold her soul?
No, she says pay with your soul. That's her. That's the name of her. What's your Satan's ex-wife?
Emma Levi's
It's like what I'd be able to talk to her though. What was she let me talk?
Yeah, you can talk to her in their chat, but not on not on a not on live, but on the chat
You can like she doesn't go she doesn't she doesn't do like a stream yard or anything like that
Just choose a panel. So this is she does it's just her and then like the chat
He he wants to know if she's on Facebook or something like that
I mean, you can buy a reading and then she'll talk to you and stuff, right?
So you have to give her money for her to be with you though
She doesn't want to be with somebody without money though. Like you have to have money
But it's a prostitute
she's a succubus
so like is she a prostitute
no she's not but she used to do before
when you gotta pay a woman money that's a prostitute
oh come on
you don't have to pay her I mean it's like it's called a wife
hey Paul
oh hey what's up
Paul do you watch baseball
no I don't why is there something going on right now
Paul there's baseball games but you're not a baseball fan
I'm not I'm not a big sports guy. I like I'm into a lot of a lot of stuff like music and
Like ghost shows like ghost adventures, you know, Zach Bagan like a jazz
off-born show and
You know, you know like
wrestling I used to be I used to like wrestling but it's not it's not fun
anymore I don't know so like what do you think about wrestling man you like
wrestling you want to wrestle Mason I'll wrestle with you I only like baseball and
hockey these days
does anyone want to wrestle with me Paul those are my sports baseball and hockey
on a diaper a sumo wrestler he wants to sumo wrestle you I don't want to wear a
diaper I can't wear a mosquito
And
Mason is it true that you don't got a drumming set
Hey Paul, so what do you what do you think about a skateboard?
Are you skateboarder Finn or just a wrestling fan or what?
Wait, what was that skateboarding are you a threat? Are you wrestling fan Paul skateboarding fan or what are you?
I'm not really no, I'm not I'm not a skateboarder fan not a skater fan Mason. Did you hear what I said?
You said something about a drum set right so bad. Yeah Mason
Someone said that you don't want you don't get a drummer said is that true?
No, no Sebastian. I used to but yeah, it's like said a drum in the store now
That's like wish I could go to play drums without having to buy a whole another one
Spunky says that you're asking always a hundred questions man. Why so many questions there?
Me by Sebastian
Wait Sebastian who me
Yeah, she's saying that you you asked so many questions and that's a thing
That's what another thing. I can't figure out with you, man
Yeah, you you're either like you're playing a game or you're you know that don't like you seem like a smart guy
Are you playing a game?
You know those people that are that work in like Macy's at spray perfume and stuff
That's what you should be doing right now. You can like talk somebody's head off to buy it. You know what I mean? Yeah
You're like a good salesman
intracable
You
Hey, I'm trying to I want to ask you something
Yes, go ahead. Is it truly you know Dave Riyad is
You're gonna have to repeat that I said Dave Riyad someone said that that's your father. That's your your father. Is that true?
I'm not exactly sure what that means
Dave Rioto the guy called Dave Rioto. Is that your father? I
Know I don't believe so. There's some of those things in your family. I was just wondering I
Have not heard such things you never heard of Dave Rio, okay, I guess that person wasn't saying the truth
Psych yes, hey site. Yes
I try not to ask too many I try not to ask too many questions, man. I'm not trying to do that on purpose
But you got a bunch of lip-dark trolls there in the side chat it's ridiculous
Where are we looking at?
Anyone's a darts you a low rider
Low rider faggot
I got a bunch of lip-dark faggot
Paul, what are you drinking, man?
What is that?
It's just water, seltzer water.
A seltzer.
Paul, a seltzer water.
Yes, like lime, right?
Is that lime, seltzer water?
Yeah, lime, right, yep.
Is it pretty good?
It tastes good?
Yeah, I mean.
I was drinking soda, but you know, I can't be drinking soda like 24 hours a day. So
It's not good for you Paul. Yeah, it's not good for you to drink too much soda
Yeah, well, yeah, I mean it's diet, but still I mean, you know coffee soda tea, you know, I need some little water
You know once in a while
Yeah, whatever once who was good for you. Yeah
Yeah, I'm trying I'm trying to lose my you know, I got a little beer belly, right and I got a I got a fat neck
I'm like I'm doing yoga. I'm doing push-ups. I'm doing stomach exercises. So yeah, I'm trying to yeah
I'm trying to I'm working on it. It's really it's hard dude
Are you saying that you're fat Paul? Like you're fat, right? Like a fat person. No, I'm not I'm not really fat
It's just that it's just that like in the dating scene down here in Redondo Beach
I mean, you know, basically LA area is really rough, right? The dating scene is really really horrible
So I got I got to lose a lot of weight dude. It's hard, you know
Well, I think you're fine. I mean, it's like there's a lot. Yeah, it's a lot of street people here. It's really hard for a gay guy
No, I'm looking for girls. I know I know but I'm saying for me. I'm good. But uh, yeah, but there's one gay bar
Yeah, are you are you? Oh, so I thought you had a don't you ever like a dude like you have a boyfriend, don't you?
Well may some kind of but I think he's confused about us. So
So I can't confused about that. Yeah, that's why I don't know
I'm confused too, so.
Well, we have a kind of long-distance thing going on,
so it's called like a.
It's like, so you got somebody, or is it me, Sy?
They have what?
No, I, yeah.
You have somebody, Sy?
Is it me?
You, you.
We're dating, right?
I thought that's what you want, Sy.
Yeah, that's what I want, yeah.
You want that too, right?
If, I mean, that's up to you, I mean, like.
Well, you have to, yeah.
I know it has to be both. It has to be up to both of us. Yeah, I mean, I don't know what to say about that. It's like
Just say yes
But what would I have to do it's like to make that happen
You have to come out here to LA you have to get a job and I'll start paying for this apartment and
You know, basically just live with me and be my slave. I'm just
I gotta give it some time. It's like still, I don't know if you
Will decide
It's like who's this other guy that's hit the panel though. I've never seen him before
Untrackable they had a he had a Mason the the drummer untrackable
Yeah, it's nice to meet new people all the time
So intractable do you actually do you actually like the drums man? Are you not a play the drums?
Yeah, I'm not an instrumental kind of guy
I do
I don't I don't put me shit man
Yeah, but intractable the reason I said that I played drums
I'm a drummer, but people don't like that. I got rid of my drum set, but I needed food and stuff
I didn't have any food
You know so you
Like did you pawn it or sell it or something?
Yeah, it's had to sell it to get money for it. So that's why I did just drum and release an album of you drumming
So like that's why you saw me play in a store when I was on the drums because I had to go to store to play on stuff
No, it's like they never told me to leave that what I went there to play
Hey, no shit. That's me of being a kid and like
You can't get the newest video games, but you go to GameStop in the mall
And they got the the display where you can like play the sample
Yes, like it's like going to game stop and you can't get the system
But you can play the system they have in the store, right?
Yeah
Paul. Hey Paul. Yeah. So do you really have to get some weight loss though? Like
you said you're not a fat person so why would you have to lose weight though?
That's only if you're fat. Oh I mean I got like a I got like a little beer belly
thing going.
I want to get back to normal like you know, I'm trying I'm trying to look youthful
Okay, I don't want I don't really want I don't want to have like a beer belly and people
You know girls girls are kind of ruthless and mean, okay. Yeah. Yeah
Hey, so I do it's like you don't look like you're fed it's like you look like you're not fed at all, man
Like it looks like you take care of yours
There's something to be said about it and
You know you guys can contradict me if if you don't like it, but you look like what you do
So if if you eat good food and
You do high intensity activities
You will eventually look that way
There is no amount of just sit-ups or just walking around the block
Um, you have to eat right and you also have to be very intense with your with your activities
I myself, uh, I have lost I have lost almost all my intensity
I used to be a hell of a thing
I'm not anymore. Um
What happened?
I've got a beer belly as well, because I sit in this chair, I go to work and I come home and I sit in this chair, but you know, they're you know, my family life does not require me to like
do monkey bars and run 10 miles and do all this shit.
It's like, oh no, you gotta go pick up the groceries
and you gotta make sure the kid gets
to where they need to be on time.
And then you're gonna sit and wait for them for two hours
while they go through their class.
And then you're gonna take them home
and make sure they get fed.
And then it's like, oh, well,
I just wanna sit in my fucking chair right now.
Yeah.
And recently there was a couple of girls that came to me,
but one of them, the last one that came up to me
was the worst, was the worst.
She had three kids.
Oh God, she had a fucking, she told me,
the first thing she said to me was like,
I'll kick your ass.
That was the first thing she said to me.
I'm like, who the fuck is this bitch?
She can't even say hi.
And then she comes and tries to talk with me again.
She wants to go out.
She has three kids.
You know basically she's like homeless, you know, she wants to so I'm guessing you know
She wants you know, she's looking for a butler. She's an asshole
You know, she has three kids with some gay dude and now she wants she's looking for the you know
Retard she she's looking for a retard to take care of her kid. I don't want to be I don't want to I don't want to be that guy
Yeah, I don't want you to be that guy
Who is it if you
I like this guy. He talks nice
If you want to change the way you live
It's not gonna work doing it because you want somebody else to accept you
you just have to pick it and do it and
The the people that don't like you now
Are probably hey, there's a chance they might like you once you reach your goals
But by the time you reach your goals, you won't like them
Yeah, well hey, wow, yeah, that's that's really intense. Yeah, that's true Wow
Sight yes, that's true. You never had a beer. You never had a beer belly before site
No, this guy, this guy's been skinny his whole life, dude.
How's that?
Yes, like you never had, like you never had a beer belly before.
It's not really. No, I have a perfectly flat belly.
He's like, he's like my dad, you know, he can eat, he can eat like
fucking 10, you know, Big Macs or whatever, 20 Big Macs.
And don't get fat, you know, they'll stay the same.
I know I eat a Big Mac almost every day. I eat Big Macs, bagels,
Subway sandwiches is probably like the healthiest thing I eat, but
They're pretty good too. Yeah, be careful eating out though because there's a lot of like
You know, there's a lot of viruses going around dude and people are not that clean
Like, they step on, they fucking step on food and shit and, you know, they're spit everywhere
and their hands are dirty as fuck.
It's okay, I don't mind a little bit of...
No, I'm just saying, you know, you might get sick once in a while, that's what I'm just
saying.
But yeah, I'm pretty careful, I don't really get sick that often, but yeah.
So, did you ever get to coronavirus before?
No.
It's a very careful saying, I don't know how to say that word, but I never got that one.
You never had, you never caught any kind of virus, like before.
I mean, I got the flu and the cold, the thickenedpox and stuff, and I was younger, but I don't
really get to see that often.
I'm not yelling, can you?
What are you saying?
Stop, just chill a little bit, stop yelling, say.
Stop yelling, say.
The numbers are going up, guys.
Wait, what?
70 to people
Get up on the panel dude. Why'd you leave?
Who's easy easy? Oh, it's all on their shins. I'm okay. I don't know
Hold on. Who's this? Hello?
Hello, who are you home? Who's that?
Who is that the Nick says Compton?
Oh, it's Nick. I think it's easy easy. What is that? Is that a dildo? What's he doing?
You're 33. What's going on? Oh
It's easy
Defros he froze. Oh
There you go. Oh the Raiders LA. So you love Los Angeles. Do you have HIV like easy you have?
Oh, okay. So now he's like pouring LV. Okay, Las Vegas
Is that
Somewhere he's this guy's in Ohio or Oklahoma or something a big red thing on his lap
It's like is that a bomb that he actually has that's he has a bomb that he has
Okay
There we go
It's a feather duster
Guys we do it the numbers are going up today and so guys again
I have a new deck and whoever wants the first reading from the deck and I'll do a bonus review for some of your choice
You can catch that $10
and the catch up it on the
banner on the screen if you're interested
and
I'll see a little as long as I can you know yeah
Paul. Oh, hey, thank you, Kellogg's. What's up, Kellogg's? Thank you for knowing your membership. Thank you, Kell.
That's up, Kellogg. I've been seeing you for a while. Good to see you.
Paul, what is the difference?
Paul, what's the difference between like a beer felling and then like a gut or like being fed? Like are they all the same?
No, like I'm like I don't I'm not really fat everywhere
I just like I got a little beer belly kind of thing and it's just kind of embarrassing to you know
Like you know girls are kind of mean dude, so like when you go yeah, they're gonna say hey fuck you
You know, I don't like you or whatever
Yeah, there's women that like like everything there's even women that like small penises like there's like a there's like a whole like so
There's women that like a belly something
They're like attracted to like George to stand so from sign bells type
They're like signs George to stand without the glasses though, right
Maybe not let's see
Uh, hey Sebastian, what's wrong with Sebastian? Uh oh, Sebastian's saying something in the chat.
Sebastian, stop right here. Get up here.
Dude, get up here.
It's like, are you gonna see Sebastian?
Sebastian's going nuts in the chat.
I don't know.
Sebastian's always crying, dude. He goes to JC and he's like crying. What's the problem, dude? Stop crying.
It's like they're going to bring him back up, man?
I mean, he's not in the back chat, so I can't. I mean, he has to come up in order to find back up.
Just like you know when you use that language it automatically like will take the video to like limited monetization and stuff like that
And so it does like hurt the bottom line over time especially because it's like
Monetizing my old videos and stuff so I
Prefer people do not use some of those harsh swears
Thank you. Oh, thank you. Oh, thank you, Cal. I love you. Oh, you're welcome. You're welcome
Yeah, the fashion is here here. Hello. Oh, I never left man
You took me off earlier man, because I still I was telling you that these lying hypocrites men in the chat
They're they're lying weasels. I told you that and you took me off for that. No, I do said the f-a-g-g-o-t
Well, yeah, if you don't want me saying they're faggots, okay?
Sebastian relax dude relax
Bastion what's wrong with you? I
Don't yeah, it's like a little bit like I'm just telling you don't say that and you keep saying it
So it's like that's why I have to
I mean, it's like I have to force the rules, you know, get back in the chat Sebastian. It's talking to chat
That should just be a regular chatter, okay?
The panelists for people that can control
If I suddenly leave then my phone is you know, okay
Make sure you come back to like, you know, I hope you found like in that if you like the show and you're like
Oh, yeah, okay. Yeah, I'm on one percent, but I'm here
But thank you so much for being here and come back again, okay
yeah yeah okay I'm gonna play a little song I'll just go because it's gonna turn
off any minute okay I don't want you to I don't want you to like just go blank on
that so bye have a great day thank you I'm gonna play a song now real quick and
then I see you this is a song that got saved by somebody in my my new have a
good one intractable you have a policy later man
Oh, see ya, dude. Have a good one, guys.
Okay.
How do I make this?
Mix...
Or actually, what is it?
Tracks.
Hey, Syke, so what are you going to do now, Syke?
I'm going to play a song real quick,
and then I will start talking to you guys again,
but I'm just going to play a song real quick.
Okay.
Where is it?
Okay, it's the dark side of the panel, here we go.
Tell me how you like this guys. Tell me if it's good
There
I thought that I could win, but the chat just sighed.
Won't you banish me?
They said I wasn't me.
Hey, Sy.
Did you see my video, Sy?
Did you see my video?
What, Rando?
What do you want?
Did you see my video, Sy?
What?
What is it?
What are you doing?
You're in favor of the song.
What's up, Rando?
Where are you? Now you can see your video. No, I didn't see your video. Nobody cares.
Okay
It's like it's like who was that person who was that person I was just talking in here. That was a rando
Was he was he just
Was he just playing around though? He was just joking around in here like not being serious. He's hilarious. He's very hilarious
Yeah
I'm gonna try one more time, but I don't know if that's the one
of the version I'm wanting.
Okay.
Well, how are we doing? Okay.
Yeah, yeah. Sorry.
Um, mix.
Okay, you guys keep talking.
I have um I fell on Saturday. You fell? Yeah I uh I tripped in my garage and landed on a
a metal piece of patio furniture.
Uh so I have bruised ribs.
Yeah, so it hurts to breathe it hurts to twist it hurts to stand up it hurts to sit down
Hurts to lift my left arm. Oh
I'm sorry. Oh, okay. Oh, I think contact animals. Oh my gosh
Well, you know what the people that lose the animal I always like to read the this is like what I rainbow bridge
I don't you ever heard of it here. There's a really nice home
Cal, I'll read it to you. It's called the Rainbow Bridge and it says, and now I'll do a private reading with you for this
And if it says just this side of heaven is a place called Rainbow Bridge
When an animal dies that has been especially close to someone here, that pet goes to Rainbow
Bridge.
There are meadows and hills for our special friends so they can run and play together.
There is plenty of food, water, and sunshine and our friends are warm and comfortable.
All the animals who had been ill and old are restored to health and vigor.
Those who are maimed are made whole and strong again, just as we remember them in our dreams
the animals are happy and content except for one small thing. They each miss someone very
special to them who would be left behind. They all run and play together, but the day comes
when one suddenly stops and looks into the distance. His bright eyes are in tent,
his eager body quivers. Suddenly he begins to run from the group, flying over the green grass,
his legs carry him faster and faster. You have been spotted and when you and your special friend
never to be hard to get.
The happy kisses rain upon your face,
your hands again caress the beloved head,
and you look once more into the trusting eyes of your pal,
so long gone from your life,
but never absent from your heart.
Then you cross rainbow bridge together.
That's a little, little story.
But yeah, I definitely, I'll talk to you,
I don't want to do that for you, okay?
Uh-oh, Ashish and the shish?
Uh-oh, like I'm meaning Ashish and the shish
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. Yeah. I know it's so sad. I'm sorry. I have Rudy. Rudy
is like, Rudy's right here. Rudy's getting old though. He's like 16 or 17 years old.
Oh, thank you. Cancel in very well. You're sitting on the front, so you're Rudy here.
He'll live some fast 20 years old, I don't think, but here. How can you get in touch?
Or unless you want to come on the panel or I can do it from the from here, too
But I'm on your discord still you think that's Amida the real beta. Yeah, yeah, Amida. Amida. Is that you?
Amida has my phone number. So can I have a talk to Amida in a long time?
You guys remember Amida? She called them like the 4th of July, I think.
No, I'm sorry Kelly.
How are we doing guys in the chat guys? We have eighty or seventy six people. Wow really really soaked. I guess we have a
some
Some interesting people on today, and I'm done to hang out for some for longer. I have some tequila to drink
But so intractable how's it been going haven't seen you for a while what's been going on
You so there there you are
You get you all the good untrackable your beards your beard's grown back
How'd it go back?
Everyday is a miracle
It is
You know what Michael liquid leguisi Mon used to say he said every day above ground is a good day
Yeah
It's
You know Michael
It's it's gonna be painful for a while, but
What is it? Oh, yeah
Well, are you hurt like what's what's wrong with you like uh, I
Have bruised rips bruised ribs
So he's hard to move himself
Hope you I hope they unbrews very fast at least that they're not broken
Oh, yeah, not not seems to be disfigured or anything like that, but
But it hurts I'm sorry all the same
But also, um, you know, there's a work situation
Okay, I work in a in a three-man team so that way, you know, we have a rotation of
When two of us work one of us is off and two of us work and then one of us is off like that
Can you work now and
can't work and
No, it's got nothing to do with that
When when I was off and they were working together
Um, they they got into a fight
They need you there now
And now both of them have been terminated. Oh shit
So now no one's there does you have the job at all they need you now
So my supervisor called me and said hey
Can we talk about your availability
because of said situation which I already knew about,
but I thought it was squashed.
I thought it was water under the bridge,
but apparently it is not and it will not be.
Okay, well, good luck with that.
I hope that you're able to find some replacements
and I know you can't do it right now, right?
Is it hurt I can do my job even in even under my condition. I've been doing it
They have to do it alone now or
Or you can pass the way man or somebody passed away site somebody told like you that something passed away in their underarms
Oh, they heard her pet. I'm yeah Kelly's Kelly's for a baby
Whatever y'all is excuse me. It's like I don't mean to interrupt y'all real quick. I just had it couldn't even ask you something real quick
Hey, what's up? What's your mods? How come they're batting people for no reason?
I'm not too sure I was just asking because I just said I love my
Just be just be careful psyche with the people who you mod bro. You're doing good, man
Can Mons keep out, like a look on the chat for anybody
like hiding people that should be doing it.
Thank you so much.
Thanks, Lindsay.
Ooh, I got, just coming, Mr. Rudy.
Rudy, you guys remember the Rudy 2D Fresh and Fruity
Breakfast from my house?
Nope.
No, it's not.
Seb.
You can't come back except I had to kick you off several times and I had to like unmod you several times today already
I think what's like you have to like behave yourself, and it's like they're not
They're making everyone upset including me
So I think I might just wrap up, but I won't play the song before I go
Well, I a clumsy. Yeah, somebody timed out clumsy. I mean, it's what's going on guys
Can you tell me who timed him out and
You're in trouble. Okay. Oh, there we go. I'm gonna play a song real quick, and then we'll see
If uh, I feel like hanging out. So let's see share
Hi, Lunar, there we go
I feel like I've been locked out
Spend my soul in a way, I shouldn't have thought out
A part of my brain was fried
i thought that i could win but the chat just sighed won't you banish me they said i wasn't reasonable
nothing was debatable with me i tried to flood and pull one over all the mods who fed me but what
Taxi to the troll side of the live stream
Don't tell your mind, team, your admin will need me
On the corner with emojis
Didn't you know that he was lonely?
You got me feeling muted
I'm about to get booted
Drama's over-computed
Asking me to give it a rest
Do you see the yes I'm gonna take a taxi to the troll side of the
Because you promised me a-
Why are there only two people? Oh, three people. Oh, look, Nick and Mason!
Untrackable to go off with.
Si. Si. Yes.
That was a song that you like. That's why you put that on?
I made that song.
Who made that song? You did?
I did, yes.
What was it about? It's just about people on the chat and stuff like that?
Yeah.
It's actually based on an Elisa Giordano song called
Dark Side of the City, that I call a troll side of the panel,
and it's based on that song.
But, Sike, why are people like that other person told you earlier, though, Sike?
Why was people timing each other out and stuff like that?
I have no idea. It's very... It's very hard to understand.
Some things don't have an easy answer to them, but just...
Some people are just nuts.
Yeah?
Is that what that song had to do with though?
It's like kind of similar to the what's happening and stuff and it's yeah
It does that's why I wrote it because like because I live on the troll side of the panel burst
I think it you live on a troll side
yeah, the troll side of the panel and
Don't tell your module admins
They'll mute me on the corner with emojis. You know that I was alone
Hey, I can vacuum like real quick.
Can you see my vacuum?
I got this vacuum on Timu.
Like, even a vacuum on Timu.
Okay, so it's a little bit small.
I mean, it's good for like just like the cat hair and stuff.
But I got this, oh shit, I got this little vacuum on Timu.
See, look at it, it's like really cute though.
It's like there's like 20 something bucks.
But it works.
Okay, see I do that. Okay, how's the chat doing? Jim Nick is awesome. I love Jim Nick
too. He's dumber than M. Let's see. Yeah, where is Jim? I saw Jim Nick last night on
Corner on the what what did that song say? It said
troll side of the panel
Or the live stream the troll side of the live stream
I thought there's I thought there's a song. I thought it was a woman singing a song
He said you've made the song. I made the song, but it's a woman singing, right? I love you. Yeah
um yeah it's a woman it's a woman singing but it's like I um it's my
concept and everything I do the parody of it was a parody but it turned into its
own good song you like it Mesa yeah it was like something like unique that I
heard of that before I made it I have like 30 songs I have them on my I'll
post my um this is my shit this is my um my mix cloud link guys and if you can
And then you can like also listen to all the songs that are on the show and stuff if you're interested
And I'll put like what is it?
It's like what does it say though again?
It says the corner of the live stream or something or what did it say? The troll side of the live stream
The troll side of the live stream. Yeah, the troll side of the live stream
She's gonna take a taxi to the troll side of the live stream, right?
Okay, so anyway, here's here's a list of my
Oh, shit, that's not how you do it, okay.
How do I do this?
Share, I, I don't know how I share.
Okay, I'll figure it out.
But anyway, you can just search for
Psyche Awakens on MixCloud.
Oh, here, here, MixCloud, yeah.
I can probably share one of them.
I'll share this one, and then you just,
all I have to do is,
Like I got actually
Can you guys follow me at mix cloud I would appreciate it
Okay, hey, hey, guys, this is Lola. I'm gonna see it may send you met Lola
That's miss Lola. You showed me before did you?
Yeah, you tell me before like maybe it was tricks. Yeah, but you have it at myself. Yeah, they're all my they're all my
creations
So yeah, I'll play another song if you want me to see grab another one
It's like what other song do you have that's like that one that you played you have another one?
Yeah, I have one that's like that. I think this one's good hitting arrows
사이렌스
You love like a pilgrim on paths never known. Seeking the sacred where wild stars are sown.
It's like, is that a picture of you and I together? That's supposed to be us, huh?
It's like, yeah.
Total love that is boundless, a myth on the trail. Hidden arrows of love, they fly.
through the caverns of spirit through the infinite dream every secret devotion every
prayer to the skies venus in the twelfth where the hidden fire lies
the center rides quiet through jungles of night
Hunting for freedom, for truth dressed in light.
Your love is a lantern for souls that are lost.
You pay for your beauty with karmic cost.
they fly unseen through the caverns of spirit through the infinite dream every secret devotion every prayer
Everyone left, was it just you and me, Mesa?
It's like, yeah, I liked it, man, yeah.
No, it's like that was a good one, man.
Thank you.
You know what it means?
Huh?
You know what it means, the song Mesa?
Cause my-
What does it mean?
My penis is in Sagittarius, and so-
It's like, what does that mean, though?
Well, penis in Sagittarius, that means I'll probably fall
in love with somebody that lives far away.
Cause it's like Sagittarius thought about traveling,
So it's like, they probably live far away.
They probably live like a long distance relationship first
and then we'll live together, I think.
Not you and me, but maybe you and me.
So what happened to, like, why did everybody leave you though?
Because they wanted to leave us together
because they thought we needed them alone.
Are you ready to make out?
Sorry, that's what you want to do, right?
Yeah.
Are we going to?
Let me see.
Sight, you got to do, huh?
Is that what you want to do, Sight?
Yeah.
Oh, congratulations, Cal.
I've really cut down to you, Cal.
Remember, I used to just be like, hey, Lenore,
I used to drink a lot, and now I just hardly even do it.
Yeah, well, yeah, guys, let's all be polite and stuff like that.
Oh, yeah, and I don't know.
We're talking about Warren Jeff, and so I mean, I come on
Let's all be like respectful of other beliefs and I
Actually, I got kicked out of a Mormon carpool before
but
And I'm doing my DNA because you know the Mormons are in charge of all the ancestry stuff
They keep track of all the records here. They baptize everybody post humanously so they have all the records of everybody
but I
actually have Joseph Smith in my
In my jean pool. Hi. This is tricks tricks. My little trickster
Mesa like is that your cat. Yeah
Well, it's not like you're with your cat right now. Yeah, there's three cats in front of me on the table
Can he show me psych let me see your cat
Like is that it right there. Hey Sierra, so that's it right there, right? No, or yeah the black cat right there and there's tricks
Yeah
See Trixie? And then Lola's around somewhere, see, but I think she's got down herself.
How many cats do you have total, Syke? Three?
Four.
Oh, we lost Mason. Okay. It's always six or seven now. It's four. No, I got
Okay
He meant he meant so I had like so last year I had like almost 10 cats because
Because a low-legate birth and
I mean, I also had like two leaders before that. So I've had as many as 12.
I gave, you know, some, my neighbors took a couple,
a couple ran away and, you know, magic of course.
I had like probably five or six cats, or probably
four or five cats and then I got Rudy this year, yeah.
So.
I love you, Kel.
Kel and I have known each other since Benny's.
You know, we were both mods over at Benny's.
You know, Kel, Benny's been on the show.
He came on the show for like a couple hours.
And, yeah, Kel's an awesome, awesome person.
Thank you so much for being here.
I miss you too.
Yeah, it's kind of crazy.
It's just all these, you know, it's like, Kel,
you and I are the only ones left because it's like,
well, I'm still kind of friends with Pie, but...
You know, it's like everybody else in our group is you know, Jamie. I don't know if you remember
Yeah, Jamie's Cowboys is like here still and but that's like
We have it just a few people here. Yeah
So after all doing good
So he man said over to him and say I'm publicly like but
Psyche I tripped in
You mean tripped in I tripped in
Shubash in
Muhammad baseball is most interesting
Okay, bye bye. Bye. Yeah. She has been a day one
Yep
I love you guys. Thank you guys and uh, you know, thank you for a gift a favor that get renewing your membership
Guys there are like a lot of videos I do still have on the members only also
You know, I'll do like a more like a long reading for you if you want to do it private
I you know schedule something for you working do like that
You know probably 15 20 minute reading for you for anybody that gets a membership, you know, so it's pretty worth it
Well, very worth it. You know, but uh, you know, I know there's not there's some people that are not into tarot
But remember that's my background and it's my trade itself
I do like to, you know, do things in exchange.
Thank you so much, He-Man.
Yeah, we controlled the streams.
Oh yeah, like we had some fun on, we had some fun.
And, you know, well, Benny's working now, Kelly,
and he, you know, he came on the show once
and he had a good time, it was fun.
I'm talking to a lot of traders, yeah.
Yeah, Jamie the cat was still here, but like everybody like a lot of people are gone, right?
Remember I don't know if you ever went to like clumsy clairvoyance or like Emma's. Oh, yeah
You did go to Emma's before too. She cheats. I'm just not talking anymore. Oh
The door hit you where the good Lord split cheese. Yeah
Oh, I wonder is LD in the LD as I wonder if that makes a bladder day
Um, let's see. Sebastian does not want to leave. Sebastian, come on, get over here, get over here and check.
Sebastian, Sebastian does not want to leave. I, I, aww.
Yeah, I, I, I want to go back to Benny's too, but um, yeah, actually I'm in a band though.
Yeah, he was, he was super nice though when he came on the show and it's like, you know, you can say, I'm kind of like the show's kind of...
Got pretty big, so it's been a
It's been a great it's been a great journey and very you know
Very interesting very interesting. I don't know if I've changed a lot
I remember we were talking in like December and I was just like I just started my channel. Oh, you did you did?
I'll reward you. I've unmodded everybody a few times because
But yeah, of course you can mod it
Yeah, Cal's a great mod. Yeah, I had to unmod everybody, but then I would slowly restarted
Oh, yeah, well, no, no Sebastian was saying he was a Scientologist and now he's saying he's LDA. I mean, it's just like come on
Are you uh, do you wear the magical underwear?
Sebastian they have this magic underwear you wear that
Kind of like old-fashioned. It looks like kind of like
You know those bathing suits and like the 1800s. Oh
Even in Benny's yeah. Oh, okay. Yeah, you got a model. Yeah, I want to make yeah
I just want to make sure you're you're safe here, too
No one's gonna mess with my friend Kellogg's Kellogg's actually she's a scouser. Yeah. Yeah, you've heard of that
There is magic under there's also a genre of gay porn. That is like Mormon gay porn
I don't know if you ever heard it's really strange. They also have me Masonic gay porn too, but where they have like these like I
Don't know this is the same magic underwear always comes off
But yeah, it's interesting. I really don't know why I would ever watch that, but it's kind of interesting.
Yeah, they have some interesting... I don't know. They have everything now. It's like, oh, Masonic or Mormon.
They're very similar actually. They're pretty much the same exact...
Wow, guys. I don't watch porn. By the way, I've never watched porn. I don't even know what it is really.
It's so...
Anyway, hey, 62 people. I don't feel like leaving right now.
Let's stay, let's stick around.
Patrick, you're a member of the Church of Jesus Christ.
But you said you were the Church of Scientology.
You said you were in China promoting Scientology.
And you were very serious about that, too.
And now that you've been on Scientology,
you don't have to know you're just another obscure,
obscure, obscure religion.
Yeah, you know, he's changed it. The story's changed. Is this a Mandela effect of Sebastian? I don't know if I can believe you anymore
Sebastian, are you just a troll?
Well, I mean I can really I've changed my religion bit like you know, I'm basically
Okay, okay. Goodbye liars
And you're the one saying you're a Scientologist Mormon that that will behave yourself with a wrench and you wouldn't twice
Within like 20 minutes of like actually modding you you actually I don't mod you twice. That's crazy
Yeah
Not that was Paul saying that you heard him say that okay Paul said it. Okay. Okay. Oh Paul's a Mormon. Okay. Are you a Scientologist?
Yeah, I know it's like you doesn't like libtards or
F-A-G-G-O-T-S, but then he really wants to come on my chat
Yeah
I've told you that I'm in the Church of Latter-day Saints. Yeah, that is the Mormon Church Sebastian. You said Scientology
I'm sure of it. You didn't say Mormon. You said Scientology
So I remember I was like, did you give personality tests out in China and you're like, oh, no, they didn't let us do that
Yes, okay
He was just lying about the Mormon stuff, so okay guys, I'll do that. Okay. It's been five hours. I've been on
It's now 503. I will give you
12 more minutes. If somebody wants to have me open this deck for the first time and give a reading out of this deck
It's a really cool looking deck. I think you will enjoy it. I've not opened it yet
I'll give I'll do two readings the first one for you and then whoever you would like to gift it to or
Do a wrap or whatever for 10 cash up $10. I
Will do the reading but if no one wants to do that
Then we'll just wrap it up for now, and I'll be back later, but I've had a fun time today.
Like, wow, really nice having over 80 people in the chat that is like, okay, I'm getting
back up there.
Sometimes I got a little bit.
Oh, my gosh, thank you, J-Dog.
Thank you so much.
I really appreciate that, let me give you my other thing.
And I owe you a really, anyway, 2JDog.
If you want to come back on up, I'll do that for you.
Let me see.
Let's see.
Aw.
I don't know if it would, did it go through? Let me see.
Depending, oh, hold on.
I don't think it went through, JDog.
Yeah, I don't see...
Oh, you need your barcode? Okay, I can put it on my screen, do you think?
Yeah, I think they would I mean yeah kelly kelly is a scouser and so she has uh, he's a 4k dog or no
It's just that in a set. That's the name for it. Thank you. We can
That's it. We're okay dogs here at home
Yo, oh, yeah, hey, what's up, psyche? I'm trying to send it through right now
So let me see put yourself full screen because it says again send through unless I have the barcode
That's why I was like what that so put the barcode full screen so I couldn't screenshot it and then I can send a cue
Oh, I got I got to focus it really quite cold
Okay, let me try it again. Okay, I'll be right back. Thank you so much. No problem
So yeah, so Cal was on so Cal and I we would do it. Yeah, man. Awesome. Yeah, Cal and I were we would do these discord chats
And it was sometimes a little bit difficult to understand but I was actually kind of good at it
My brother-in-law was
I'm good at listening to the words, but some people do not.
Yeah, she's a scouser. That means Liverpool.
Hi guys. Oh, thank you so much. I appreciate you guys by the way
I'm also I was I'm streaming to kick today and also like you know
Some people came in that came in the chat and kick and we're like oh join this discord
Or does it kick discord and I did and like there's all this like stuff to
Promote in there. And so I think I'm gonna be growing my kick a little bit. I'm psyche awakens tarot on kick
psyche awakens tarot all three
If you guys are on kick you can join me there. So I'm just a dual streaming there
Yeah, it's chibi oh
Chibi and yeah, I think you'll like Kelly's an awesome person Kelly's awesome
A lot of people but a lot of Kelly Kelly a lot of people that I brought here
It's like I'm like, you know that left me and
But I'm so glad I
Know got to like but I think some people are just better
She and I have always been close. Yeah, I'll post it one second. My kick is...
My kick is gonna be...
Okay.
Well, I think that's the other kick, he-man. I don't know if I have something planned for my kick. This is my kick right there, so.
And it's a
You know, I just, I do a dual stream there, but it's like it's pretty cool, like the chat layout. It's like a, you know,
I'm trying to grow that one too. There's, I might be able to bring some new audience from there too. I'm also,
I'm, I would do rumble more, but
Thank you, Cal. I would do rumble more, but panel versus BODs already
Syndicates my show there. Oh, thank you black RG
Yeah, so
My show syndicated on rumble
So I don't really bother with that because they do put on my like episodes that I
Delete from here like to move legal on there sometimes so you ever want to like find a
episode that's like a little secret but
They also beat his show is on there and
Q45 bloggers on there. Good time is on there
Yeah, I can keep the turtles on there. I think
and
Sandman's on there, of course and
Much of people on the panel verse, right? Oh
So
panel versus pretty
Pretty hoppin. Pretty hoppin. But you know, it is interesting, I love the people, I love the people, no matter what happens.
I had some difficult times, but I do love the people and I'm glad things have worked out.
I think a lot of people are really supportive and even if they don't like me, they like the...
The drama and they like so they you know, I do have some nice crowds in here
So I really thank you guys
For sticking by me. Wow. It's they've been like, you know, I'm a long time
I'm really uh, I'm really
Thank you for being here
We're having fun. I hope I hope yeah, you know, if you ever need anything like, you know, I'm
I do like, you know, I'm consulting. Oh, thank you. Thank you, Kel
Thank you
Yeah, I mean I do and also I on tick-tock and stuff
I do readings because like I just do read I just do readings on there
No, and people really really like them and no, it's like oh I
Get such good feedback and like a lot of a lot of love there
So I just know that about two people are into tarot here
But I would like to at least like you know open your mind to it a little bit even if you don't believe
And something yeah, we like a little drama too, right? I like a little drama too. It's like I get bored
You know, I would just get bored just doing pure tarot. That's why my tiktoks are just like shorter
They're like an hour, and I just do really quick readings
but um, I
Like I like talking to different interesting people and
Some of the some of the
What do they call it? Oh, oh, thank you so much. Thank you, Jay dog
If J-Dog comes back up, he can get three and then he can offer one to somebody else too.
But thank you so much, J-Dog.
Are you gonna go live?
Okay, well, I'm gonna get down in a minute at Sandman, so it's like, you know,
I'll be happy to send my chat there if you, like, start your live,
and then you can post your link in here if you want,
and then people can go over there and say hi.
You know what, Sandman, he might not like me, but it's like, I still want to support you,
and it's like, I'm gonna support Vita, too.
It's a big Sandman, okay?
Fuck
But I do I don't have anything like I don't have animosity to anyone if anyone needs help anyone
Q45 came to me. Yeah, I don't be like
If anyone comes to me and ask for some help. Thank you J-Dog if you want a reading to come on the panel, but are also
Okay, that man is going live in a bit. Okay. Well, you know
Uh, you can go over there. Samman's a fun show. No, I like his show. I think he's funny
He's a good person. He wasn't like that rude to me. He could have been meaner, right? Yeah, that's a fake Samman, but uh
You know
Can't we all just get along I just want to get along
I love you guys. We're having a we're having a nice day though and I really do appreciate
Every everybody well
Should I, should I save this deck for later?
Should I, what do you, what do you feel like,
should I do, I can do a collected out of it.
Really cool deck.
You're gonna kidnap me now?
Yeah, that's a big savings account.
So what is it today?
It is Tuesday.
Well, I'm down.
Guys, you can go to this website called RubMaps,
and it has all the, the, oh, there's a note place,
I can put notes in my chat now.
Oh, here we go.
Hey, yeah, I'll be going for a key. Hey
You like a reading? Yes. Yes, please. I got you
This is the called the gallery of hallucinations oracle. Okay, so let me open this up. It's the first one
And I've read this one. Okay, this looks pretty cool. I mean, so here we go. It's called the
Gallery of hallucinations
That's a cool
Let me just get this this way and the right side up or upside down. Okay. Okay. This is a sideways. Okay. This is pretty cool
Okay, do you have a specific anything you want me to focus on for your reading or just a general?
I'll just general. Okay. I
Haven't I haven't ever used these cards before so just bear with me a little bit. Let me see. Yeah
OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK OK
Okay, so first of all we have this remembrance, okay, and this is also somebody you're remembering somebody
But there's a remembrance that this is also
Okay
So so we have this remembrance. Okay, so this is like it makes me think of like almost like a loved one
But then it says there's that there's this one says dismay. So there's like some kind of sadness in your past
I can see there's been some kind of mourning
Remembering somebody that I think has passed. You're very very sad about okay
But you're going into this period where it's like
Well, right now there's a harvesting, okay?
So you're also able to pick up these fruits of your labor
and you're actually even working really hard at something
and it's been paying off and you're actually able
to enjoy this kind of success in the present moment.
Also, you have your really deeply rooted somewhere.
This is a sky roof and it's like, there's this like,
you know, I think you finally like.
Maybe have like put down some roots somewhere rather than like like moving around so much
And it's also like a time of this is the hysterics card. Oh, thank you. I got you Kelly got you
Thank you so much and so be it the hysterics. I think so it's like it goes from dismay to hysterics like it is
I could start to laugh. I think it's like you're gonna be really happy with something
Okay, what I got for the future
Okay, this one says the reading so this might this one might be very up this reading might be very significant for you
I would just remember this and also like maybe maybe a rewatch over because it's like this significant
Significant mess is coming through for you. Okay, and
Ooh, you get the Voyager, so you might be traveling and also there's some kind of transformation you're making because there's a butterfly
And so it's like there's some transformation. It's like going down a new path
Maybe but being able to fly down it and also taking a voyage taking a
trip rather advice for you
I'll pull one more car for the advice and then I'll go ahead and take care of the advice is
The keeper and there's little black cat. I don't know if you have cats or you like cats
There's the keeper and it's like I think this is just about keeping watch
I have to keep being a guard of something to like I'm just like in protecting what you have okay?
So I think that I think a message for you. There's also the keeper. That's like
Cat might have memories. There's something there's something significant about a little black cat. Okay, so I
hope that
Yeah, dude a lot of that was really really I could relate to a lot of that shit. They'd like that was spot on actually
like
everything like saying
But I was gonna travel it was I am morning, you know, it is a month of a
You know, a lost loved one, so I am morning.
Oh, sorry.
Yeah.
You know, grandmother, I passed away years and years ago, but it's the anniversary.
Uh-huh.
So...
Yeah.
You know, then you said, I am taking a trip, you know, next month.
So...
That's why I'm going to get a bikey spot on.
Yeah, I think that would be like a transformational kind of thing, too.
Like, you know, it's like...
And also, but I also, I think the cats, like, telling you to keep watch and to keep, and
Keep your wits about you. Keep you know keep the focus on what's going on around doing stuff like that. So
Psyche pulls up. Thank you. Yes. Thank you Kelly. Okay, so I'll do Kelly now
Just my card Kelly. I can play a few cards up, but I see what I got for Kell. I'm gonna have young but even
Thanks for the reading man. I appreciate it
Thank you. Bye-bye
Okay
I'll do three for Cal, okay.
Oh, okay.
One.
What did that say?
System kind of, okay.
Kelly, you're a gardener, aren't you?
Aren't you, I'll have to show you this one.
Oh, this looks really, okay, wow.
Okay, you got three for you.
Yeah, I need my glasses a little bit. Okay, got three cards for you
Okay
Yeah, this is the first card this one says snow blossom
Okay, so she's out in the she's in the cold, but it's like there's something keeping her warm
Also, this is like some kind of fire flower
And so it's also
But I got I got the spell blossom and she's like she looks like she's like like a little miracle
She's keeping warm and stuff, but then we have witchcraft. Okay, and so maybe this is like this is maybe this is something
Snowblossom, maybe if you I don't know if you're into gardening or something, but I think there's some kind of significant
Magical property of some kind of plant around you. Okay. I don't know if you're growing something
It doesn't say witchcraft, okay, but it looks like it's some kind of green witchcraft and then
We have the conundrum. Okay, so this guy's in a conundrum, right?
And so it's that's like a really really hard confusing difficult problem
Okay, so it might be like have a lot of different voices or something like that coming at you and
Confusion I'm gonna pull a couple more out of these
Okay, this one says Pursuit.
Okay, so this says they're gonna be going after something.
You're like, or maybe the conundrum in the pursuit
is like, you're wondering, should you go after that?
But I think he will decide to pursue something, okay?
It could get a white rabbit,
be it this one is like a shooting star.
It's like she's chasing after the shooting star, you see.
Okay, and so I say follow the shooting star.
What is that?
You make a wish, right?
So go after, go in pursuit of your wishes and dreams.
and don't be in a state of confusion about it.
Like just go for it.
And then look, we also have connection.
This makes me think of your,
see this is a human calling here,
but I think that there's a connection beyond the grave.
Like, you know, that's still there
and it's like you're still receiving messages,
you're hearing this, you're hearing this,
maybe it's your pet, maybe it's a person,
but there is some kind of connection there.
And finally, if Cal,
Oh, we have the moon girl. We have this moon girl. Okay connection with the moon with your emotions
Also, there's something being like maybe hidden about me even have a hidden about you like mysterious like the moon
Go into different phases, but also this this along with the with the witchcraft makes me also think like some kind of moon magic, too
and the flower too, the flower kind of like the moon
carries like a little bit of a fire of the sun
but it's not fire, it's just like the reflection of the sun.
And so it's like, the moon is, the moon is,
I'm gonna put one more card, word of advice,
advice for Cal, it's just convergence.
I mean, it's coming, convergence,
everything's coming together
and it's like there's gonna be a bunch of opportunities.
And it's like, whatever door you choose,
there's gonna be opportunity behind it, okay?
It's like everything's gonna be coming together for you. Okay, and so it's gonna be easier
It's gonna be easy to make the next move because it'll be like right in front of you. Okay, you know, it'll be it'll be a choice
So just make the right choice. I'm ball your heart. It's very seven of cups energy. Okay, Cal
I hope you like that and you know, I got and if you want to I can talk to you on discord. It's like to
Like the animal card. Yeah, or the stars in the moon. Yeah, it's falling the shooting star and
Also, but it's also that nature magic too. I think there's some kind of like
Flower there's some kind of flower. There's a connection with you know, it was like that a
Beautiful that beautiful fire flower
some kind of
Fire flower you're welcome. Love you. Thank you. And if anybody else I can pull a card for anybody else the discord is
This court is okay. I think I just had a lot of people join it like the month, but it hasn't been really like since
You know, it used to be big like more popular now
It's not really we had the last big problem
We had and there was like during the 40 diamond stuff and no one's really posting in there anymore
But I'm gonna try to get it back
Back on track, right?
Because it is a good website. You love a card spunky. I got you
This is a really I do really really like this deck though. It's what a beautiful deck of like a
Forges are I wonder if this guy's a real real person because it says a deviant moon who's another guy. I know I
Bought a lot of decks from stuff, but
He made this and made up the person because he does sometimes do that
For spunky what do we got for spunky?
Okay
What is this?
What doesn't have it because it usually will have like a
name on it but this one is just like a bunch of this is like all these
completed artworks and so this is this could be possible possible scenes of
the future it also could be like you know saying that you're does you can
design your future also also you know this law of attraction I'm gonna pull
three cards for you law of attraction it's like you know just can create what
you want and sort of attract we have this delirium delirium so it could be
the perception about something might be off a little bit because like you know
these are distorted a little bit might have a distorted perception about
something or I don't know do sleepwalk or something it kind of seems like a
little bit of sleepwalking and you also have this connection to okay you have
the connection to like the past on love one I think there's one trying to send
messages to you talking like there's your ear and like when she's receiving it
Ooh, this one says shelter, okay, I think like they all like you know
See he has fire and she has the umbrella and it's like they can come together and like both enjoy
Both enjoy a like that right it's like two people coming together
They each have something that they can share that will help the other one right and then bringing them both together will
It's just like better for everybody, right? Okay one more
And you got the keeper. So this is the black cat again. You have a keeper. So this guy for you the keeper energy
I see that like those baby
This kind of reminds me of this remind me of a little nor because when we're always guarding the door
But I think this is like a guardian like some kind of kind of guardian of your shelter, right?
You got shelter and then they have the keeper inside
It's like it's like there's something guarding you while you're inside and sharing my flight. Okay. Oh, I'm glad you came to kill
You're awesome
But I feel like it's like really things are going a lot better. Yeah, I feel like things are going a lot better
Oh, yeah, this is really cool. This is called and here's the back of the cars
Really interesting artists. I saw as soon as I saw these are like I have to have those. They're just like beautiful art style
So if anybody else would like a few cards, I got you
Yeah, the cats are your spiritual guardians. Yep
Yeah, I feel like that too. Yep, Jamie would like a card. Hey Trey. Yeah, we got Troy. Oh Troy, Troy is in the kick.
Thank you for being in the kick. Thank you so much. I'll do a reading for you too Troy if you want. So for Jamie
What does this say? Hold on. This says
Enticement, okay, so this is like somebody maybe trying to entice you, someone trying to offer you something
But maybe just like watch their motives
Okay, like someone but someone's trying to like say oh look at this look at this and like maybe distract you or something
So just keep you know just just keep your wits about you and don't let yourself be distracted by like shiny shiny things
Or like you know nice words and stuff like that because you might be trying to like convince you or something like that of something, okay?
I'll almost get some kind of lawyer energy there too, okay?
Jamie.
Okay, two came out.
What does this say?
Okay, this one says the scheme.
I would say watch out for, watch out.
There's many people trying to scheme behind your back, okay?
And I see this, and I also see this stranger.
So maybe somebody you don't even know.
Because there's or maybe it could be either like somebody you don't know is trying to scheme against you or
They're they're gonna be there to help you. Okay
Because you do have this stranger so somebody that maybe it's a stranger to you and you might they might seem like
No, I know that's a kind of like the opposite opposite things like you either there to help you or her to you
Right, but it's like there's I really do see like it could be both like it could be like you know somebody's
That you don't know is trying to scheme on you, but also somebody that you don't know will be there to help you
That's how the feeling I get about that. I have word of advice for Jamie
Well, it says morning. I think I think it's like that there's something that you have to
Mourn for it. There's some kind of ending maybe not
I don't think it's a physical death
But I'd say that there's some kind of like maybe it was a relationship or maybe something that is being buried and late to rest
And it's like it's okay to be it's okay to mourn for it and to be sad
But you want to get past that and everything but just show your respects to and uh, you know
Whatever whatever ended and you know every ending of the new beginning there's gonna be like a
Resurrection, okay, something, okay?
Don't be like that Jamie. He did okay
So, yeah, yeah, so that yeah, and then uh did the water and protector for Jamie, okay?
Yeah
Yeah, I do feel that I feel like that stranger is actually it's like a stranger you might say oh stranger and it's like
Somebody like different, but it's also like
This one looks like a friendly stranger, right?
Right, I know it doesn't but it feels like for me it feels like somebody is
Is is like plotting like it's some kind of like
Figuring out a plan or something like that
Feels more like a washer and protector. Yeah, I got I got that I got that from this one
I don't think this I don't say I don't think oh, thank you Kelly. Oh my god. Thank you so much
Yeah, I feel like this is almost like an owl, which is like a watcher. Yeah, I watch her, right?
So, yeah, and also like time might be significant there, too
Okay
Makes me think of like labyrinth and the clock straight 13. It's almost almost like the phantom toll booth
Remember that phantom toll booth?
Book, you ever hear that book?
It's a book called The Phantom Tollbooth.
It goes a clock on it and I want to look at that book.
The Phantom Tollbooth, if you remember that.
Is Dixon, is that my name Dixon here?
Yeah, I'm happy to read for Dixon.
Dixon, hey, hey Dixon, would you like a reading?
Oh, you love the book?
Yeah, isn't that a cool book?
Okay, I'm gonna pull some for Dixon.
Yeah, thank you so much, Kel.
Oh, this one popped up.
Okay, so first for Dixon, we got Night Drifter.
So this is maybe an astral projection,
or maybe in your dreams going somewhere,
but it seems like you're able to do something
where you leave your body a little bit, right?
Even if it's in your mind, and it's like a meditation or something it seems like you have some kind of good skill and
in your inner self and you know
Either ask for projection or loose lucid dreaming or
You know something like that, but it's like yeah, but in the night time. I think it's caring for others a little boob in that picture
Well, so we have predicts in
Okay, Dixie we have the enigma. Okay, so this is like something that's kind of a mystery
You know, it's a mystery wrapped in a riddle. It's like something you're trying to figure out
But maybe doesn't have a clear answer
There's some maybe something that will be confusing or like maybe kind of a sphinx energy
I might do the sphinx where she has a riddle. It's like
You know sick does the enigma so
Also that these heads, these decapitated heads or something are said to be
like, like, prophatized, especially if they're open and stuff like that, and so it could be like some kind of
kind of riddle, or what does that say on the front of the box though, let me see.
It says, ewig blick. Ewig blick?
Okay, so it's something to figure out. It's like some kind of mystery.
See, because there's a question too. There's a question mark in the corner right there.
It's like what does it mean like you have to maybe think about what that means yourself. There's two candles a book
Bell the I'm thinking the book a movie called the bell the candle
So we've got witches, right?
Start a mod for you
And
We okay for you we have enticement to okay, so you might be being ticed by this by this enigma or it's like the
Are you, like, really attracted to stuff that is, like, um, a mystery?
Heh heh heh, my time.
Ah!
Thank you. Thank you, Kel. Oh, my gosh.
Um...
There's also this enticement. Like, look, there's, like, a little...
The guy's putting a little spider over, like, her head, like, right behind her.
He's putting a little spider.
Watch out for someone trying to distract you from something, okay?
To get you away from something someone's trying to get you away from something. Oh, you got the shelter too, okay?
Enticement a shelter, okay. I would say they're trying to entice you to go someplace, okay?
Like or to stay with them, okay?
Skyroot
Okay, stay in stay like a senior say senior ground, okay, and I would be very careful about letting somebody
Else in or something like that, okay?
Like because you're grounded. You're grounded in and uh, it's what someone's trying to entice you with something. Okay
What does this say?
This one says the odalisk I might need to do it. Let me see if I can
I'm not familiar with that word odalisk. Okay. Like the odalisk? Okay
Figure out what that means. Anybody heard that word before? Odalisk
O-D-A-L-I-S-Q-U-E.
Okay, it says,
a odalisk was historically a member of a harem.
Okay.
A harem, often a slave or concubine
in Ottoman sultan's household,
right from the Turkish word oda, which is a room,
and odalik, which means attendance.
In the 19th century European art, the term also refers to the exoticized depictions of such women who are often portrayed nude or semi-nude pose for the male viewer's pleasure.
Okay?
Yeah, so this is something, I think maybe this is part of the enticement? Watch out for like a nude lady or something like that? Or this harem?
But it's like a concubine, okay, or a room attendant interesting
Because yeah, because this is about your house and your roots and stuff like that. And so
You have you
You have a girlfriend. I think that there's I have to be careful. Yeah. Oh, so how does it kill happen?
Yeah, the mods I think kill drop for another reading. So if you'd like if you'd like a reading today
Think think think how
Thank you so much, Cal. You're awesome. Thank you so much.
Mods? Yeah, mods?
Who's down in a mod? Who wants to read me as a mod?
And also, yeah,
I don't know, I've always got you guys for a need.
If anybody ever wants just a few cards or like a card, I always got you guys for a need, you know.
And for members only, even longer, and then
For donation, I'll I'll do the deluxe. Okay. Okay. Here's for everybody. Look at this one says ephemera
This is for everybody so ephemera, okay, but it
So this is a collection. Okay. This is in a really really nice little old car
I'll get you a reading about ephemera too. I want to get the exact some of these words, okay
Ephemera means things that are exist or are enjoyed for a short time
Okay, so just like I make me think of like just life in general like
We have a limited time in this life and it's like it's like what we're just make sure to enjoy the scenery enjoy the ride
Because it's like go everything is everything is temporary, you know, and so it's just that we go to all these different states of movement and places but just
appreciate your time while you have it because
It's precious and it's like uh, it's it's uh
You get to experience things and go places and
Beware of your surroundings
So, oh, yeah warm me up Cal
Anybody else? Let's see anybody else
Chat oh, thank you guys
48 people
I love you, Cal.
You're a wonderful Cal, thank you so much.
It's so good to see you.
I love the, it's just good to have an old friend,
like, you know, some people that,
you've just been here since the beginning,
and I appreciate you, I love you, it's good to see you.
I'll put another card for the whole chat.
Chat, we got, this one says,
The flea this is like see she's on fire. She's like help me like she's pleading for help her hair is on fire
I remember right. It's like you might have to
If you need help you might have to you might have to you know, please you might have to and it's like you know that might be
Yeah, I mean that her hair be around fire should be like convincing enough
It's like oh my god. I don't want to smell in my house, whatever
But you've been yeah make sure you
If you have a chance to ask for something and it's like somebody else maybe ask ask a little bit strongly
Say please please please always remember say please you're gonna get further along with that
There's a witch. Yeah, okay. We have the connection to I think there's voices like I think everybody has these loved ones coming in
They try and they try to give messages like keep your ears open. Okay. Take it like just realize that it's like
Always we're being communicated with okay, and it's like just because something I thought close to your mind doesn't mean it's your thought it could be
Spirits it could be out things outside of ourselves. It also could be programming playing itself out
I'm gonna pull two more cards for the chat. Ooh, this one says
Ghost lore, okay
So it makes me think about spirit or something like that, those ghosts around.
Maybe do you have a poltergeist or something?
I might want to read some ghost stories. Of course we have these three.
This looks like the three sisters. It could be like Hecate,
like the maiden or the chrome kind of energy.
The Trinities are very powerful. We also got the Charmed Sisters or Trinity, right?
So the power of three. Also the book is seen as on fire.
Finally, ooh, we have the lobby, but look at it,
it's like, give the lobby, okay.
What is the lobby?
The lobby is like, the gathering place inside the hotel
on the first floor, but she's naked,
and she gets off the elevator in the lobby.
Thank you, thank you, Kel, see you soon, okay?
Message me on Discord, I'll talk to you.
And that was for the chat guys. I want to thank you for being here today. Thank you so much for everybody
I've had a fun fun time. I
Was back tonight. Okay, maybe we'll have a little
little party and
Hang out some more. I don't know. I guess Sam-Man might be on soon. So everyone go
up and go say hi to Sam-Man and
The beat is on go say hi to be like, you know, I still love everybody in this community. Yeah, I love you, Kel
Thank you guys
Hey, I hope you had fun today, and I'll be back tonight. Okay? Thank you guys for everything
I'll play a video on the way out, and I'll see you soon. Okay?
Thank you. Love you
temples of night. Golden wings glowed in the candlelight. Crowds came running just to
see the flame, but envy was the price of fame. And now he stands where the echoes fall, with
tarot in hand, hearing every call. From praise to venom, in the same breath said,
burns gold
They stand cra-